Handler One to Undertaker:
Enemy interception forces have been detected at grid points 30 and 504.
Enemy forces are battalion-sized units of tank and close combat types.
All units: Advance and eliminate the threat.
Although, against these odds,
none of you will make it out of this alive!
Hurry the hell up!
Go on, pigs!
Fight to the death, you damned Eighty-Six!
What's this?
Hey, stop it!
Stop it! Stay away!
Shut up! Shut the fuck up!
May 13th, Stellar Year 2148
As you can see, it's another beautiful day across all eighty-five Sectors of the Republic!
Why not go out with your friends and family today?
The weather is expected to worsen tomorrow. However, you won't need an umbrella.
Now then, enjoy your weekend, everyone!
Next up, an update on the war from the San Magnolia Military HQ!
A group of mechanized drones known as the Legion, belonging
to the former Giadian Empire, invaded the seventeenth ward
and sustained heavy losses after engaging with our own unmanned
combat units—the Juggernauts—and were forced to withdraw.
Our forces suffered minimal losses, with no human injuries or deaths!
Defending the nation with our advanced and ethical drones
has resulted in zero Republic casualties!
The day when the righteousness of our nation smashes the evil remnants of the wicked Empire is not far off!
All hail the Republic of San Magnolia!
Glory to the five-colored flag!
San Magnolia Military HQ
Morning, Major!
Those pigs sure were crying their heads off yesterday.
Well, it was a pretty crazy fight. I bet at least fifty of them died.
Not that anyone was on board anyway.
Hey, everybody! The doll-loving princess is glaring at us!
Why the angry look, Major Milizé?
It's just a few busted-up drones!
Listen, you—
Morning.
Morning, Annette.
You're up early. You usually sleep in.
I pulled an all-nighter working last night.
Unlike those morons.
Forget about them!
This isn't the battlefield.
We're inside the Gran Mur,
and the enemy will shut down in two years anyway.
If anything, you're the weirdo for taking it so seriously for the Republic's sake.
I just think this country's conscience has—
Vladilena Milizé
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not awake enough to listen to one of your speeches.
What's that Processor's problem? He's just a part!
No kidding!
We're from the First Sector. Why do we have to put up with those bitching pigs from the Eighty-Sixth Sector?!
Why do you care so much about the drones, Lena?
They're not drones.
I'll put it this way, then.
Why do you care so much about the Eighty-Six?
Looks like the battlefield calls, princess.
Initiate ID confirmation.
Major Vladilena Milizé,
commanding officer for the eastern front's ninth ward's third defensive squadron.
Para-RAID, activate.
Synchronization target: Pleiades Processors.
Synchronization complete.
Handler One to Pleiades:
Pleasure to work with you today.
Pleiades to Handler One:
Synchronization successful.
Be careful. The enemy is entering firing range.
Proceed with caution—
As always, such kind formalities for us subhuman Eighty-Six.
How sweet, Miss Human.
You're reassigning me to a different unit, Brigadier General Karlstahl?
Yes.
The truth is, the previous Handler transferred out of the unit.
As such, we need to find an immediate replacement.
If the unit isn't being withdrawn while we find a replacement,
does that mean it's defending an important base?
Yes, it's the eastern front's first ward's first defensive squadron.
S
Officially called the Spearhead Squadron.
It's comprised of veterans from all across the eastern front.
You could consider them an elite unit.
But...
I've just been commissioned as a major, I don't have the experience for this.
And you're also the youngest person ever to make it to the post of major.
If you try to be too humble,
you'll make unnecessary enemies, Lena.
I'm sorry, Uncle Jérôme.
I'm sure Václav would be proud if he could see his daughter, too.
How is Margareta?
She's the same as ever—pestering me to get married.
Sounds like her.
To be frank, we can't find anyone else who'll accept the position.
Aren't they an elite unit?
Wouldn't it be an honor for a Republic soldier to command them?
Correct, but there are some strings attached.
The unit leader, Personal Name: Undertaker.
S
He's got a bit of a reputation.
A reputation?
S
They call him the Reaper.
He has a tendency to destroy his Handlers.
The Processor destroys the Handler?
Not the other way around?
Correct.
It's not just a ghost story?
I don't have time in my schedule to share ghost stories with my subordinates.
Almost all of the Handlers that have been assigned to Undertaker have either retired or transferred.
Some of them even committed suicide.
I know it's hard to believe,
but they claim to be haunted by the "voices of the dead."
The dead?
You're free to refuse, Lena.
You work too hard, anyway.
A Handler merely needs to monitor their unit and let those on the field take control—
I'll do it.
I'll do my utmost as the Spearhead Squadron's commanding officer.
You only need to do the bare minimum.
And you should try to keep your interactions with them to a minimum.
Knowing one's subordinates is part of a commanding officer's duties.
Well, while I'm lecturing you, let me add one more thing.
Stop putting the number of casualties in your reports.
Officially, there are no humans on the battlefield.
So there are no casualties.
But that doesn't mean we can ignore them.
What we're doing is unforgivable.
Lena.
You really are just like Václav.
All right.
I appoint you, Vladilena Milizé,
as the commanding officer—the Handler—of the eastern front's first ward's first defensive squadron.
Have the paperwork done by the time you get there.
Best of luck to you.
I'll do my best until my final mission.
So you accepted it?
Republic of San Magnolia Military Research Wing
Sheesh...
You're such a weirdo.
It's an honor to command such an elite unit.
Plus, it's worth doing.
And all that stuff about destroying Handlers is a lie, right?
I bet they were slacking and wanted an easy excuse.
It's true that some of them committed suicide.
One of Spearhead's Handlers went crazy and blew his head off with a shotgun.
All right, the checkup's done. No problems, as usual.
Thank you for your cooperation.
But why suicide?
Naturally, we were asked to investigate.
They thought that it might be a problem with the Para-RAID.
Transfers aren't a big deal, but we can't ignore suicides.
What did you find?
Who knows.
You don't know?
The Handler was dead.
How were we supposed to investigate it?
You're the leader of the development team.
Is that really okay?
We did our jobs.
There was nothing wrong with the RAID Device. End of story.
We told them that if they wanted to know more,
they'd have to bring us Undertaker.
But those idiots in Transport said, "This flight has no seats open for pigs!"
So, you didn't talk to Undertaker?
We just read their report.
"No idea," they said.
We told them about the dead Handler,
and all they said was, "I see."
Well, they're Eighty-Six.
It's within the realm of possibility that using a Para-RAID could lead to insanity.
It puts a lot of extra load on the brain to share sensory data with another person.
And even now, we're only sharing the sense of hearing.
If you tried synchronizing vision as well,
your brain just wouldn't hold up.
Put too much load on the brain, and you don't come back.
Using the Para-RAID means accepting those risks.
But your father was one of the pioneers in this field of research.
All of the core principles were developed by someone else.
In truth, there's a lot I still don't understand.
Lena, you really should join us in R&D.
The military's just an unemployment relief right now.
When the Legion shuts down in two years,
"former military personnel" isn't going to mean a thing on your résumé.
Thanks.
But we're at war right now.
Those Processors are crazy!
We don't even know the long-term effects of Para-RAIDs.
The Eighty-Six die quickly,
so the long term doesn't matter.
But I don't want that for you.
Still, it's cowardly.
Right, right.
You really are weird.
I modified the settings.
Thanks.
Oh, Lena! I made chiffon cake.
Want some?
I'll pass for today.
See you later.
I used real eggs.
And real milk.
It's so good!
How's it feel to actually eat the real thing for once?
It's wonderful!
But part of me wonders if this is how it really tasted.
You forget when you eat only artificial stuff.
I've got cream puffs, too.
They don't taste like cheese when they don't have cheese in them,
or look like they're about to spit out black smoke, right?
Are you talking about the cream puffs I made last time?
It'll be fine this time!
I gave some to a potential marriage partner yesterday, and he cried tears of joy.
Sounds like you got a good match for once.
He must've really loved it.
Of course!
I also gave him a card with a lipstick kiss and the words, "To my beloved."
I dropped them off at the place where he's living with his mistress.
May 20th, Stellar Year 2148
What's wrong, Pleiades?
Please respond!
What's wrong?
Handler One to Pleiades!
Enough already.
He's dead!
Pull back! Evasive maneuvers!
Damn it!
Handler One to all members of the third squadron:
Enemy forces have begun their retreat.
The fourth squadron will take over the patrol.
Return to base.
Roger.
Pleiades and the other six who died...
I'm so sorry about them.
Always... Always with the kind words, Handler One.
Just so you're aware,
the third squadron will be assigned a new Handler.
Thank you for everything.
I'm going to be the commanding officer for the Spearhead Squadron.
That's great news.
Eager to see you out, Handler One. My utmost sympathies.
What does that mean—
Give the Reaper my regards.
May 22nd, Stellar Year 2148
Para-RAID, activate.
Synchronization target:
Spearhead Processors.
May 12th, Stellar Year 2148
Nice, man!
Guys, start cleaning already—
Sounds like they're having a good time.
The same goes for them.
Wait! Wait up!
Eggs!
Welcome back.
Huh?
Hey, lend me a hand.
Coming.
And, done!
Thanks for all the hard work, man!
It's "thank you, sir!"
Members of Spearhead, it's breakfast time!
Gather round!
Right, right.
Coming, coming.
Morning! Morning!
Morning.
Let's eat!
There're more omelets.
Seconds!
Calm down.
Can't you savor your food?
Is it good, Kuro?
Very.
Hey, didn't our Handler go crazy again?
The one in the battle yesterday?
He's done for.
Didn't you hear him?
"Stay away! Hey, stop!"
Cut it out, guys.
Those white pigs sure are irredeemable.
It doesn't matter who it is, it's always the same in the end.
Right?
But everyone made it back yesterday, right, Shin?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, if we're going to die anyway,
we'd rather have our Reaper guide us.
What now?
Here.
May 22nd, Stellar Year 2148
Fuck, that hurts...
Damn it!
Damn it all!
I don't want to die.
Shin...
Our promise...
Don't forget...
Has Kujo moved on?
Yeah.
And your brother's voice?
Not yet.
I see.
There's none left.
You suck.
I win!
Handler One to all Spearhead units:
Greetings. I will be serving as your commanding officer.
A woman?
I've contacted you tonight to introduce myself.
Hello, Handler One.
This is the captain of the Spearhead Squadron.
Personal Name: Undertaker.
We've received word of the Handler change.
We look forward to working with you.
As do I.
Nice to meet you, Undertaker.
aigan shitemo kongan shitemo kawaranai ya, mou
No matter how hard I wish, nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo kongan shitemo kawaranai ya, mou
No matter how hard I wish, nothing ever changes
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo kongan shitemo kawaranai ya, mou
No matter how hard I wish, nothing ever changes
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo kongan shitemo kawaranai ya, mou
No matter how hard I wish, nothing ever changes
fuminijirareru dake no hana
fu
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
anata no koe wo, wasure wa shinai darou
No matter what happens, I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo, wasure wa shinai darou
No matter what happens, I'll never forget your voice
kaze ni fukarete, chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete, chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
sono, konkon taru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
kaze ni fukarete, chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
sono, konkon taru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
kaze ni fukarete, chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
sono, konkon taru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
shou
sono, konkon taru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
aigan shitemo kongan shitemo kawaranai ya, mou
No matter how hard I wish, nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo kongan shitemo kawaranai ya, mou
No matter how hard I wish, nothing ever changes
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo kongan shitemo kawaranai ya, mou
No matter how hard I wish, nothing ever changes
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo kongan shitemo kawaranai ya, mou
No matter how hard I wish, nothing ever changes
fuminijirareru dake no hana
fu
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furi, shiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furi, shiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furi, shiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furi, shiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
so
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
anshin shina yo, bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up, why don't you
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
anshin shina yo, bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up, why don't you
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
anshin shina yo, bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up, why don't you
an
shin
anshin shina yo, bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up, why don't you
yaru koto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
anshin shina yo, bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up, why don't you
yaru koto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
anshin shina yo, bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up, why don't you
yaru koto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
yaru koto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
Spearhead.