I heard that Akatsuki Kojou and Vatler fought here before.
So I thought the situation here would be more chaotic.
The electrical and water equipment are still functional.
Thank goodness.
But, that thing just now...
What was that all about?
The thing who sank the cruiser we were on?
That thing is probably the reason for the recent disasters in this sea region.
Kisaki Kiriha.
I'm afraid that is why we cannot afford to not investigate the Oceanus Grave II.
To think we would encounter a hurricane,
and the Yaze Conglomerate's cruiser would be so fragile.
It is beyond my expectation.
So you are saying the ship didn't sink because you three were making a ruckus?
Damn it.
This is why I was strongly opposed to this.
Why does the Lion King Organization have to cooperate with the Taishikyoku in this investigation?
That's right.
For our side, as long the Fourth Progenitor is here, there is no reason for you to be.
What is that man doing?
He said he had something else to do.
We agreed that he will come later tonight.
But in this weather it's probably not possible.
He has something important to do?
Uhh... to him it is.
What is it?
Supplementary... swimming lessons.
Huh?
Oh my...
Senpai, wake up, Senpai!
Himera...gi! Why are you in that outfit?
I'm the one that wanted to ask.
It was like this when I opened my eyes.
Sleeping in the same futon with Senpai.
Sleeping together?
Senpai, what are we going to do?
It looks like I lost something precious.
Something precious...
Wait, Himeragi, I don't recall that at all...
Sekkarou... isn't here!
That's true, the guitar case you always carry is missing.
I should have brought it over yesterday.
And that's your P.E. uniform,
but that type of bloomer should be long extinct.
Is it the Lion King Organization's?
No!
Senpai, what do you imagine the Lion King Organization to be?
Actually, what were we doing in this kind of place?
That and the two of us were sleeping together.
That's, wait, I don't remember anything.
Moreover, it should be a day off from school.
Then why are we still at the school?
Damn it, none of this makes sense.
Hey, Himeragi.
This... is blood!
Then this means...
someone got whacked by this thing?
Damn it, is this for real?
Senpai, what is it?
No, I was looking for my handkerchief. But there's this bulgy thing inside my pocket.
Senpai!
No... no! It's not mine!
Also this bra is huge.
It can't be Himeragi's.
What do you mean!?
It's certainly not mine, but it looks familiar.
It might be Sayaka-san's.
That's right, this smell, I feel like I've smelled it before.
Senpai...
Hang on, I just wanted to confirm... Ahh!
Creating a distraction?
No! I saw a shape on the roof of the building across from us.
These are the infirmary's bedsheets?
Senpai, this is my uniform.
This is Asagi's swimsuit.
So you figured it out through the smell.
No! Her name is written here!
Actually, I remember Asagi's figure in this swimsuit.
Now I remember. Asagi and I were taking supplementary swimming lessons.
So we came to the school.
Such a lewd wind!
That's why I said you didn't have to come.
No way. I am Senpai's observer.
Observe what exactly? It's just supplementary swimming lessons.
Wow, you really are here, Kojou.
Asagi, why are you here? There's no school today.
Actually, I have supplementary lessons today as well.
I didn't want my bangs to get wet so I ditched class but got caught.
Then this is your own fault. It sucks for me. I have no resistance.
No resistance?
Vampires can't deal with water, right?
That's just a superstition.
You didn't know how to swim even before you became a vampire.
Ehh, is that true?
I'm just not that great at it.
And Asagi hurry up and go change.
No need.
I'm wearing my swimsuit underneath. See?
Are you a elementary school kid?
Isn't it more efficient to cut corners?
There is always someone who forgets to bring a change of underwear.
What are you saying? Why would I...
Asagi?
That's no way I would forget hahahaha.
It's coming down hard.
Sigh. Looks like it's not going to stop.
It's a hurricane.
It should keep raining for a while.
Astarte.
Are you here to help Natsuki-chan?
The master is away.
I am here to deliver Miss Sasasaki's message.
Sasasaki-sensei?
Hurricane #31 is approaching Itogami Island. Today's supplementary lesson is suspended.
Also, the monorail stopped running five minutes ago.
Now I remember.
Astarte-san got permission for us to use the school building.
We were waiting out the hurricane inside of the school.
Ko... Kojou!?
Perfect timing, I have something to ask you.
What is it, Asagi?
Wh... what?
Your face is super red.
No... nothing!
So yesterday...
Ahhhhh, forget it!
Even if you tell us to forget, we don't remember anything at all.
Huh, really? That's great.
Just forget it! Absolutely don't remember it! Forget all of it!
You got it?
That Asagi, what?
Why was she panicking?
Senpai, that is near the Home Ec room.
Let's go take a look.
The interior of the ship is huge.
Truely. There isn't much reason to have this huge ship just for some passengers.
What is it hiding?
A cage?
Pochi?
Come.
What is this thing?
I fear it is some kind of magical artefact.
This is getting fishier and fishier.
Nagisa!
Hey, Nagisa, hey!
Wait, Senpai, there's a note.
Look there, it's a dying message.
Looks like she's trying to write Kojou-kun.
Hold on, I'm innocent!
There's more stuff written here.
This...
Seems like it is saying "welcome home". Maybe it is some kind of code?
Oh, it's Kojou-kun and Yukina-chan.
Nagisa, are you alright?
What's with the blood?
Blood?
Ah! The ketchup spilled!
Ketchup?
That's right, last night we ate dinner with everyone.
Yesterday's dinner?
Yea, Senpai.
To avoid the rain, we came from the swimming pool to the school.
Then there...
Right! We ran into Nagisa.
What terrible luck.
I wanted to train by myself but it was raining too hard.
I ran to the monorail stop but the service stopped right in front of me.
My clothes were soaked so I had to change.
Looks like there's no way back today.
Can't help it, we'll prepare to stay at the school.
For us three girls, we can sleep in the infirmary beds.
What about me?
You can go to the gym and find a mat to sleep on.
Those smell really terrible!
That's a small problem.
Compared to that there is a much more urgent problem.
The problem is... what?
Our dinner!
Really? Thanks. Then we'll go ahead.
The guys from the gardening club got a hold of their president.
He said that the hurircane will wreck everything anyways,
so we can have as much of the vegetable in the garden as we like.
But it's weird to be picking vegetables in this weather.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Geez. I though I was going to die in the storm.
Thanks for your hard work, Kojou-kun.
Yukina-chan too.
What happened to you?
She tripped and fell. Lost her footing in the mud.
I was careless.
You'll catch a cold this way. Do you have a change of clothes?
That...
No problem.
Eh?
Astarte, you appeared out of nowhere again.
Received permission to use the master's clothes. Please wear this.
Wait a second. That's...
But you really will catch a cold like this.
Yea, I give up. I'm changing.
Why would Natsuki-chan have bloomers?
That's not important!
Nagisa-chan, have you seen my Sekkarou?
It was still here when we were making dinner.
Perhaps something happened afterwards?
You don't remember either?
I only remember being glad there was something to eat.
Sorry, Yukina-chan.
It's alright. It's my responsibility.
Don't worry. We'll find it for sure.
Nagisa.
Take care of your uniform.
That stain might not come off.
That's right! Sorry, Kojou-kun, Yukina-chan.
I'm going to go wash it.
Now, let's talk about where we should go next.
Himeragi, did you hear that?
Yes.
It came from over there.
I'm sorry! Forgive me for my mistake, Yukina!
Sayaka, your death will not be in vain.
Leave everything to me!
Sayaka-san.
La Folia!
Why are you two here?
Anyways, lets go back to the deck.
The air down here feels stale.
What the?
Merman? Why did you appear here?
What happened?
You lost some magical ingredients
so you'll commit ritual suicide to atone?
It's not that simple.
That is an important product the Japanese government ordered from the Kingdom of Aldegyr.
The princess came to Japan for this.
That's not enough of a reason to die.
La Folia.
You should have stopped her.
But it's a rare opportunity to witness an authentic Japanese ritual suicide. It's a waste to stop it.
Resurrection magic has been prepared.
That's not the problem!
Speaking of which, Sayaka-san, the lost magical ingredient is...
Amanita Phalloides (Death Cap).
Just hearing its name make it sound like some ominous mushroom.
Actually it isn't poisonous or addictive.
But if you eat it by accident,
You'll enter a trance, and feel excitement and joy.
So in other words, just don't eat it, right?
It can also be an ingredient for anesthetics and truth serums.
Ah, I remember now!
Now that you mention it, we put some mushrooms into yesterday's hot pot.
But, I never thought that all of you would come to school as well.
I didn't really want to come.
The princess insisted.
I wanted to see my fiancee in a casual setting, Kojou.
Who are you calling fiancee?
Don't speak so loudly when we are eating dinner.
It's going to burn.
Everyone get your chopsticks ready.
Yukina-chan, this mushroom is done.
Astarte-san, try one.
Accept.
Wow. It's great.
Really? Thank goodness.
Overall, I feel like the flavour isn't strong enough.
Luckily we got these delicious mushrooms.
That's really amazing.
Aside from the vegetable garden, there's also another place that grows mushrooms.
Another place?
Aren't these the ones that Kojou and everyone else picked?
Nope.
These mushrooms were already in the kitchen.
It's delicious, so who cares?
The last udon tasted great too.
Now this feels like a real hot pot.
It's not over yet, Kojou-kun.
We used the leftover ingredient to make omelets!
Kojou-kun, here, say ahhh.
I'm full already!
Why are you getting embarassed?
We took a bath together before.
Bath?
Kojou, you...
That was when we were in elementary school.
Jeez, Senpai really is a lewd person.
Senpai, go sit over there.
I'm already sitting down.
Senpai, I have to do my job as an observer.
but you always interact with other girls.
You did so many indecent things to me.
If you want to do it, then do it to only me.
Yo Kirasaka, Himeragi is acting weird.
Hurry up and help me.
Kirasaka, you!
It's because this room is so hot.
Recently my bra became really tight.
I didn't hear that!
Hey, Kojou.
I knew it. You really don't like girls who are big.
Stop crying! Don't lean over! Damn it!
Hey, La Folia, help me with Kirasaka.
Choose, Kojou.
In this situation, I heard that in Japan you should play the King's game.
Where did you learn this crap?
Anyways, aren't you royalty?
I know. I'm the king right?
In that case, Kojou.
Please sign here on this marriage certificate.
The burden of this game is too heavy!
Kojou, so you really hate the heavy girls!?
Senpai, you jerk!
Sign it! For the future of Itogami Island and the Kingdom of Aldegyr.
Kojou, say ahhh.
Give me a break!
Such misfortune.
Are you okay?
You're not affected?
I have a high resistance to abnormal statuses.
My body is such that even If I eat I wont get fat.
Is that for real?
But once in a while something like this is good.
Is that right?
What do you mean? Are you not satisfied after seeing my swimsuit?
It's just the school-issued swimsuit.
Hmph.
Now that I think about it, today's wind is intense eh?
Our school will be wrecked.
Asagi, your panties?
Did you forget to wear some?
Nooo!
That's dangerous!
Where did you get that? That metal baseball bat?
A computer's harddrive will lose data after being stuck by a powerful force.
So, Kojou should as well.
Wait, Asagi, I didn't do anything.
The Hippocampus is a part of the brain that's on the side.
It's the part of the brain responsible for memory and learning.
You get it now, Kojou!?
Oh, I remember now.
I remember as well.
So that's what happened.
The thing we ate was the Amanita Phalloides.
Let me die!
Situation report.
Astarte!
Report?
Master's collection has Amanita Phalloides.
Because she is wealthy, she is willing to share with you.
Seriously?
Is that true?
No problem.
That's great. Sayaka. Looks like you wont have to commit ritual suicide.
Yea, yea, it's finally settled.
Sorry, Himeragi, we haven't...
Who is it? At a time like this...
Kojou, great, I got through.
Come quickly. There's a big problem!
Yaze, what happened?
It's a Kraken. There's also a Merman army.
We're still holding on, but if this continues we're going to die.
Please send reinforcements.
I got it.
Do your best until we arrive.
In their investigation of the Oceanus Grave II Yaze ran into trouble.
We have to hurry over.
But I...
Oh, that's my uniform?
Did Astarte-san help me wash it?
Affirmative. Retrieved it after it finished drying.
Also, the laundry pole is no longer necessary. Recommend that it be retrieved from the roof.
Laundry pole?
Since there were not enough laundry poles, after getting your consent, I used it.
So you're saying...
Is this really what Himeragi gave you to use?
Affirmative.
Now that you mention it, when we were eating the hot pot
we did discuss something like that.
Himeragi...
Yukina...
No... no! It's not my fault, it's the mushroom's fault.
It's not...
We solved the mystery at last.
Now, after all this brain activity...
The name on the cage, Pochi, can't be referring to this thing?
Lord Ardeal has some weird fetishes.
No!
Yuiri!
So the Merman and the Kraken are not on the same side?
Yes.
Damn it, there's no end to this.
Come, Regulus Aurum!
Kojou!
Behind you!
Yuki!
Thanks, Natsuki-chan.
Don't call your teacher chan, you moron.
Really, treating me like a courier delivery service.
This isn't a small favour.
Sorry, we're late.
No kidding, did you run into some trouble?
Uhh, what was it that happened, Himeragi?
Senpai!
Well, in any case, at least we got here in time.
Leave the rest to me.
This is my fight!
No, Senpai, this is our fight!
I, Sword Shaman of the High God and priestess of the Lion, beseech thee.
Dawn light of exorcism, spirit wolf of snowy mist, grant me the divine might of thy steel,
that I may smite a hundred evil spirits!
Come, Sadalmelik-Albus!
This thing...
Wait, Kujou-kun, stop!
That's...
A brand new magical artefact.
It's a magical artefact left behind by Vatler.
I'm afraid this Kraken is as well.
So that's it, you are protecting this magical artefact.
Kojou, everyone,
this child is so tiny now.
Can we please spare its life?
Stop, Sadalmelik-Albus, that's enough.
Kojou-kun.
Senpai.
Thank goodness.
Yea, I don't want to keep that magical artefact.
Giving it to the Lion King Organization or the Taishikyoku is also bothersome.
But what's up with those Merman?
My apologies, Lei-sama.
The Merman squad was defeated. We failed to recover the magical artefact.
Too bad.
That was Dimitrie Vatler's Legacy of the Old Gods.
If we acquired it, it would be useful at some point
for our plans that are about to commence.