Quratar
Are you looking for something?
Identify
Onesta
<Female 37 Years Old>
Merchant: Lv 44
Or are you perhaps looking
for a place to live?
Actually, I thought you'd be selling weapons.
I'm sorry, but this is a hardware store.
We don't carry weapons.
If you're looking for a weapon shop, there's
one on the street with the knights' station.
Thanks. I'll be back to
do some shopping later.
I'll be waiting for you.
She asked if we were looking
for a place to live.
Is that place also a real estate agency?
Possibly. I don't know what
the market is like in Quratar,
but a room can be rented for a
year for 10,000 to 30,000 nars.
For 50,000 nars, you can rent a large house.
That's cheaper than staying
long term at the inn.
Can anyone rent a place?
Probably, if the town is large enough.
I've heard a lot of Explorers live
either here or in the Imperial City.
Huh.
But in your case, since you have access to
spells, you could probably live anywhere.
Is she talking about Teleport?
I don't want people to know I can cast magic.
I should live someplace it wouldn't
be strange for an Explorer to live.
We'll be fine. Leave it to me.
I'm counting on your help
when the time comes.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
Quratar Weapon Shop
Identify.
Rod
Empty
Cane
Wand
Empty
So the maximum number of empty skill
slots is different depending on the type.
They probably get more expensive
the farther back you go.
I'll start with something for a beginner.
This one looks good.
You can judge the quality of implements?
Impressive, Master.
Yeah, don't worry.
I don't understand it, either.
Steel Staff
Iron Staff
Wooden Staff
Wooden staves, iron staves.
They've even got steel staves.
There are so many types. I don't
know how to tell them apart.
It's probably strange for an Explorer
or Adventurer to purchase a staff,
so I'm hesitant to ask an employee.
I'll take the one-third odds and buy a
wooden staff so I can get out of here quickly.
Quratar Outskirts
There are quiet residential neighborhoods
just outside the town center.
It's not too big, but there's
a shopping district, too.
It's a nice place.
Yes. I think it's a nice town.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
I asked you for directions earlier.
Welcome.
Were you able to find the weapon shop?
Yes, thanks to you.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'd like to ask you something.
Can anyone live in this town?
Yes. We'll check your Intelligence Card,
but there aren't any restrictions.
My card displays my first job.
That shouldn't be a problem.
All kinds of people become Explorers.
In this town it's considered taboo
to look into someone's past.
Here we oversee district six.
It's a nice place upstream.
If you'd like to acquire
a residence, let me know.
District six?
This town is divided along the six roads
that extend from the center of the town.
Labyrinth
Explorers
Guild
Hardware Store
Knights'
Station
They're numbered counterclockwise
starting at district one.
This is district six.
I see.
Are you an Explorer?
Yes.
What kind of home are you looking for?
I'm not sure how to answer that.
Actually, could you tell me what
kind of places are available?
As long as I can rent it for
just over 40,000 nars a year,
I don't have any particular requirements.
Will it be the two of you living there?
For now, but in the future...
I see. You are an Explorer, after all.
Why'd she smirk like that?
Did she realize Roxanne is a slave?
Um...
Maybe it's because she manages a district,
but that was the face of someone who knows.
I see. You've got a nice girl here.
Would you prefer someplace
near the labyrinth?
I don't have a preference.
For an Explorer looking to
rent for just over 40,000,
I've got some apartments
available near the labyrinth
or detached homes if you're okay
with someplace farther away.
I don't mind living a little farther away.
Since you're not an Adventurer,
I presume you'd prefer a home
made with shielding cement.
Shielding cement, huh?
Field Walk can't be used on walls
made from shielding cement.
They're probably inconvenient
for Adventurers.
I was planning to use
Teleport to get around,
but I've encountered something
I'm not familiar with.
It's not impossible to get around
if you install a sturdy partition,
so you'll be fine, even if you become
an Adventurer in the future.
Could you show us the place first?
Very well. Let me get ready.
Nice assist, Roxanne.
You can count on me.
Huh. It's pretty big.
Quratar Outskirts
Is this area the yard?
Yes.
You're welcome to use it as you like.
It's pretty neglected, though.
That's rosemary.
It doesn't look too healthy.
I see. A neglected yard reduces
the value of the property.
Roxanne deliberately said
it doesn't look healthy.
In that case...
It'll be tough to fix considering
how withered it is.
You're right.
Without anyone to take care
of it, it's bound to happen.
It should be fine.
It's even possible for you to
immediately begin growing other herbs.
In that case, would you be
willing to share seeds with us?
If you'll tend the yard,
I'd be willing to give you some.
We have hoes at the shop.
She's making us buy a hoe?
She takes every opportunity to make a profit.
One more push.
It'll probably have to be dug up once.
It'll be a lot of work.
The windows were repaired and the
house was cleaned just recently.
You could start living in it right away,
once you moved some furniture in.
She's not willing to make
any more concessions.
Just getting free seeds is a decent haul.
The previous resident made
a variety of adjustments.
Feel free to remodel the
inside however you want.
They performed a lot of revisions
to the flush in particular.
The waste water flows into the gutter outside
when you pour water into the container on top.
Since it takes in water
from the nearby river,
the gutter itself isn't particularly dirty,
but it's rather inconvenient
to get water at this location.
The previous resident was attempting to
build something else, too, but I stopped them.
What? There's another bathroom?
It's in the room back there.
It's only connected to the sewage outlet.
Nobody needs a toilet right
next to another toilet.
Were they trying to build a laundry room?
I have some questions about the kitchen.
Go ahead. Ask me anything.
This area must be for cooking with fire.
Roxanne said she could cook. She's probably
curious to know how easy it is to use.
Yes. This wall is made using
fire resistant materials.
In which case, I should test it while I can.
If you'd look this way...
Roxanne, I'm going to check
out the second floor.
Understood.
I can make water using magic.
But if this shielding cement stuff
prevents me from using Teleport,
that'll affect the home's convenience.
[Party]
• Kaga Michio
• Roxanne
So this is what happens
when I use it in a party.
Since Teleport affects my whole party,
I should disband mine temporarily.
I'll start with the room in front.
And then check the one in the back.
This room on the second
floor is the biggest one.
This would make a good bedroom.
Okay. Teleport to the adjacent room.
Come on, let me through.
Adjacent Room
It worked.
This Bonus Incantation is even
more impressive than I thought.
It can go anywhere without limitations.
I can go anywhere I've seen in person before.
But it comes with some drawbacks.
If I go someplace I'm not
supposed to be able to enter,
people will wonder how I got there.
I should confirm my destination
either isn't being watched
or is someplace I can reach using other
transport magic before I use Teleport.
How was it?
It's not a bad house.
What do you think?
The yard is a bit neglected,
and the house costs 45,000 nars annually.
It's not a bad price, either.
Fine. We'll rent this house.
Thank you. Your Intelligence Card
will be checked by the knights.
Let's return to town.
I'll write up a contract for you.
This will be my and Roxanne's home.
I passed the Intelligence Card check.
We signed the contract without issue, too.
What else do we need to live in that house?
I haven't seen this shape in a while.
That's for cooking with high heat.
Huh?
We're the only shop around
here that sells them,
so you may not have seen them often.
Oh, uh, but...
Excuse me.
If we pay for that pot along with our
rent, you'll give us a discount, right?
Right?
Uh, yes.
Thanks for your help.
Thank you.
No, thank you. I look forward
to seeing you around.
I'm glad we got a discount, Master.
Yeah, thanks to you.
It was actually my 30% off skill,
but let's go with that.
We can buy the things we need tomorrow.
Miscellaneous items, yes,
but I think we should
look at furniture today.
Even if we buy it tomorrow, there's no
guarantee it'll be delivered tomorrow, too.
You're right. Let's go.
Yes, Master.
The furniture store employee said they'd
deliver our furniture by tomorrow,
so we'd better be here by the afternoon.
It's all used stuff, but apparently
they'll make a new mattress for us.
Roxanne?
What? Um...
Weren't we told this house was
made with shielding cement?
I waited to decide if we'd buy this house
until after checking to see if I could use that.
That's incredible, isn't it?
Don't tell anyone.
Come on, let's go back to Vale.
Yes, Master.
Is what I should be saying, but...
Vale Labyrinth, Third Floor
Since I got a new weapon,
I want to test it out.
More like I've been itching to
use it and can't wait any longer.
There's one.
Green Caterpillar: Lv 3
The perfect enemy.
One the second floor it took four
casts of fire magic to take these out.
In other words, they should be able
to withstand more on the third floor.
Fireball!
Second shot. Fireball!
Is he trying to jump on me?
Before it reaches me, I'll fire off one more.
Three shots.
Impressive, Master.
One night in a two-person room.
I'd like some hot water and a lantern, too.
Sure thing.
This is our last night at this inn.
I stayed here while desperately
earning enough money to buy Roxanne.
It's the room we first entered
together after I bought her.
It's also where we spent
our first night together.
This place fills me with powerful emotions.
Excuse me.
Roxanne was nervous at first, but now...
Is that the right amount of pressure?
Yes, I think so.
I see. In that case, I'll clean
every last bit of you like this.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Master...
So there isn't a micron of grime left.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Not a picogram of dirt.
Thoroughly, carefully, and delicately.
Master.
Again and again and again.
Not there, Master.
Roxanne? Are you all right?
Yes, I think...
...so.
I'm sorry. I've never felt
anything like this before. I...
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Roxanne, you're warm.
I feel warm, too.
Well, I hate to say goodbye,
but shall we go?
Yes.
This is the first place
where you took care of me,
but you'll take care of me plenty
more times in the future.
Roxanne, you're killing me.
We don't need to pick up where
we left off last night right now.
Roxanne always accepts my advances.
I'm not the person I was
before I made her mine.
I'm ending my extended stay today.
I've removed all my stuff.
I see. Thank you.
Thanks for having me.
If you'd told me yesterday,
I would've provided a lantern free of charge.
Just a lantern?
Okay.
Waterwall.
Is that enough?
Yes, thank you.
I'll start scrubbing now.
In that case...
I'm going to check out the Quratar labyrinth.
See you later.
Quratar Knights' Station
Entry fee for six.
That will be six silver coins.
Entry fee for five.
Can I interest you in a map
of the Quratar Labyrinth?
Twenty nars per floor.
A thousand nars for a book of all floors.
These knights sure are business-minded.
Explorer
Knight
There's an Explorer here,
in addition to the knights.
They have guides here, too?
Next person, please.
Entry fee for one.
That'll be one silver coin.
Quratar Labyrinth, First Floor
Its basic construction is the same as Vale's.
If there's anything different about this one,
it's that it's crowded.
Can people really farm monsters like this?
This area is away from the other parties.
Now's my only chance.
Teleport.
I'm back, Roxanne.
Going forward, we should be
able to enter without paying.
Welcome back, Master.
If she were wearing a maid
outfit, this would be perfect.
Did you learn that greeting
at the trading house in Vale?
Yes. Was it strange?
No, it's fantastic.
Thank you.
Um, I'm dirty since I was in
the middle of cleaning, so...
You'll wipe up anything
that gets dirty, right?
Of course.
I've come to deliver the
furniture you purchased.
How inconvenient.
I'll deliver your items to their rooms.
Is this what you wanted?
I don't want him coming all
the way into the house.
It's all right.
Very well. Excuse me.
Thank you.
We'd be in trouble if anyone
other than me could use Teleport.
The two of us can manage to move
the furniture into each room.
That should do it.
Nice work, Master.
The mattress feels nice since it's new.
No one else is coming today, right?
I don't think so.
Then the first thing we need to do...
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Is take the bed for a test drive.
What do you think, Roxanne?
Um, certainly.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
That's not the right spot.
Sorry, Roxanne. I can't tell without a light.
Here it is.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
There should be a candle
around here somewhere.
Where did it go?
We don't have a candlestick.
We should've bought one today.
I'm sorry.
Candles aren't cheap, so I
thought we wouldn't need any.
If we don't have any, then we don't have any.
But the darkness will allow
me to focus on my movements.
Starting today, these sounds
of hers are all mine.
Master, right there!
Naturally, the bed felt excellent to use.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem