Good morning, Master.
Good morning, Roxanne.
I could spend all day in bed with
Roxanne, from morning until night now.
It's not that I'm not attracted
to a degenerate lifestyle,
but if I want to keep living like this...
I wish we could continue,
but we should head to the Quratar labyrinth.
Yes, Master.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
Quratar Labyrinth Entrance
It's pretty crowded.
That tends to happen, especially
here on the first floor.
Since everyone has to pay to enter,
a lot of people push themselves
to stay here as long as possible.
It certainly seems that way.
And since this labyrinth has
been around for a long time,
it's apparently quite famous and large.
I see.
Quratar Labyrinth, First Floor
Boss Waiting Room
If this labyrinth has
attracted this many people,
it wouldn't surprise me if
someone's beaten it already.
Actually, nobody knows how high it goes,
or what the boss of the top floor is, because
nobody's beaten it.
I believe the highest floor ever reached was
the 91st, by the first emperor's party.
91? We've got a long road ahead of us.
They just keep coming.
Is this the line for an amusement
park ride or something?
Can I help you?
Oh, no.
Master.
It's our turn.
Quratar Labyrinth, First Floor
Boss Room
The line moves pretty quickly
despite how many people there are.
I doubt the boss is very strong.
After all, it's a kobold.
Kobold Kämpfer: Lv 1
Kämpfer?
So he's a warrior, huh?
He looks pretty strong.
Here I go.
It's so slow.
Well, it is a kobold.
And weak.
Quratar Labyrinth, Second Floor
There doesn't seem to be anyone here.
It would probably be safe to use magic.
Are there really that few people here?
About half the second floor
seems to be kobolds, as well.
Lame.
That's enough for today.
I'm feeling kind of disappointed.
Understood.
Teleport.
What is it, Roxanne?
Nothing. Go ahead and rest, Master.
What about you?
I'm going to get some seeds.
Seeds?
Oh, you mean the herb seeds the
district manager's giving us?
Then, I'll go with you.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Let's do some gardening this afternoon.
But first...
Let's eat.
Town of Quratar
Welcome.
Ah, I've been waiting for you.
You're here for the herb seeds, right?
I'll bring them to you now.
We'll need these, right?
It's just a yard.
We can find some wooden planks
and use those to dig it up.
There's no reason to do that.
I feel like hoes would be a waste of money.
Thank you for waiting.
I'll explain what they are,
if one of you is free.
In that case, I'll listen.
This is mint, and this is rosemary.
Do you know how to plant them?
I can't let her dig with her hands.
Yes.
Quratar Outskirts
Thank you for buying me tools, too.
Don't worry about it.
We should till this entire area.
We can dig up the weeds while we're at it.
Shall I do it?
No, could you sharpen those
wood scraps over there?
I want to build a fence.
Understood.
All right. Then, let's get gardening.
All done.
I feel so exhausted and
satisfied in a good way.
We should be able to make
a nice vegetable garden.
Yeah.
I'll wash our dirty clothes.
Thanks, Roxanne.
It'd be great if I could take a bath now.
Um, Master.
It would be nice if we had a tub
for washing clothes in the future.
And a change of clothes for you, too.
Quratar Cooper
Is there anyone here?
Hey, welcome.
I'm looking for a laundry tub.
Sure thing. In that case...
How about this?
I see. It looks good.
Is that the biggest washtub you sell?
No, sometimes I make bigger
ones on special order.
You can do that?
Yeah. I've got the experience.
I can make you a functional tub.
I'd like something broader than my arm span.
Is that deep enough?
Yeah, that's plenty deep.
What I want is a bathtub.
Since we're renting a house,
I'd like to do something
about our bathroom next.
And besides...
Now when I bathe,
Roxanne will be joining me.
Imagine sitting in a bath with
Roxanne and having her wash my body.
I need a bath.
A bath is essential.
Nothing beats baths.
I must make one.
How much will it cost?
Well, around two thousand nars.
Vale Labyrinth, Third Floor Boss Room
Kobold Flour
Kobold flour?
It's a milled grain.
Apparently, it tastes better than
the flour they sell in town.
I see.
The fourth floor is next.
Yeah. I'm counting on you, Roxanne.
Leave it to me.
That's enough exploring. Let's have dinner.
We can make something tasty with this stuff.
Okay.
Master, what is this?
White cream stew.
White cream stew?
You've never had it?
No. This is my first time
hearing about it, too.
Well, you won't want to miss this.
How is it?
Master, its so thick and tasty.
Don't say that with white
stuff in your mouth!
There's more, if you want.
Thank you.
Because of you, I feel ready to put some
extra effort into exploring tomorrow.
Please just swallow it!
My bathtub should be done soon.
Maybe I'll put in some extra effort, too.
Tripe: Lv 4
Vale, Vale Restaurant
Quratar Labyrinth Entrance
I thought I wasn't afraid
of monsters anymore
because I'd gotten accustomed
to this world, but I was wrong.
It's because of Roxanne.
She fights without a single complaint.
If anything, she seems happy to do it.
Master, this enemy's movements are
not particularly impressive either.
Will we ever encounter a monster
whose movements impress Roxanne?
What just happened?
Why was I attacked?
Roxanne?
Was she attacked?
I can recover using Durandal.
I should focus on healing Roxanne first.
Treat Wounds.
Master.
Rush.
Rush, Rush.
Treat Wounds.
Rush.
Let's make this quick!
It finally went down.
Roxanne, are you all right?
I'm fine since you healed me several times.
What did that thing do to us?
You were immobile for a while,
like you were asleep.
Like I was asleep?
I see.
The Beep Sheep's skill either
puts people to sleep
or knocks them out when it sounds that alarm.
That's an annoying skill.
We'll suffer, at least,
one attack when it uses it.
It certainly seems that way.
This time I allowed it to go off
because I let my guard down.
Sorry about that, Roxanne.
What?
Let me know if you're still damaged at all.
We should prioritize recovering
our stamina above all else.
After all, I don't want to lose you.
Master...
Understood. That's what I'll do.
That's enough exploring for today.
It should be arriving soon.
Master, what's arriving?
Ah, it's here.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's the item you ordered.
It's huge.
The planks look thick and sturdy.
They need to be at least this
thick or it'll break right away.
Well, if you'll excuse me.
Um, Master.
L-Let's get this thing inside.
What is this tub for?
This is a bathtub.
What's a bathtub?
It's for bathing in.
Let's start getting it ready.
Roxanne, get the jugs.
Understood.
First...
Waterwall.
Next...
Fireball.
One more.
My head hurts.
But for now I just have to
keep doing this over and over.
I must be a huge pervert if I'm willing to
do all this to take a bath with Roxanne.
But even perverts have pride.
Okay, that's enough.
You must be tired after all that work.
I'm not the only one getting in.
What? You mean I can join you?
Of course. I heated up
enough water so you could.
You'll join me, won't you?
I'd be delighted to. Thank you.
I've been waiting for this.
Excuse me.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
What is this?
As you can see, it's soap.
I'm not sure I made it right, though.
When did you make this?
Because I did, I acquired the Alchemist job.
If the soap I made works, then we'll
be killing two birds with one stone.
It's not as good as body wash,
but at least it foams up.
Let's try washing off.
Roxanne, take off your towel.
You first.
Now, now. Don't be like that.
I made this so I could wash Roxanne.
Ah, we're performing an
experiment. Very well.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Go ahead.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
An experiment, huh?
She's not wrong.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Now that I think about it,
I'm not sure this soap is
good enough to use on people.
I'll test it on my own hand first.
All right. It doesn't hurt. It seems fine.
Roxanne, give me your hand.
Soap is slippery, isn't it?
You've never used it before?
No.
It's expensive.
Master, that tickles.
Sorry. I was trying to be careful.
Now it's finally time for...
This is incredible.
The bubbles make fond—
washing them smoother than ever.
Like snow-capped mountains,
they're turning white from
the base to the peaks.
When I shake them gently while washing them,
the bubbles tremble,
making the peaks a sight to behold.
Roxanne, how does it feel on your skin?
It's completely painless.
It feels good.
What a marvelous, snowy experience.
Eventually the snow begins to melt
and spring blooms on the mountains.
I'm getting to experience all kinds of
firsts just by being with you, Master.
I-Is that right?
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Because I washed her entire body,
she looks like she's wearing
clothes made of white bubbles.
How oddly alluring.
The way it resembles torn clothes is sexy.
Maybe it's because they're just
bubbles or not really clothes,
but I can touch her bare skin.
Roxanne's warmth is beneath these bubbles.
Um, Master?
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
This will allow us to efficiently wash
ourselves using a small amount of soap.
In my homeland,
it's a traditional bathing method
close men and women engage in.
Really?
Yeah.
Close?
In that case...
Huh?
Allow me to wash your body, Master.
She's going to start by undressing me, too?
Roxanne's slippery body is clinging to mine.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
My body is sinking into her soft damp skin.
Like this?
Y-Yeah.
My body is being stroked
by her impressive chest.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
This is amazing.
Being washed by you feels so good.
I might get addicted to this.
I'd be happy to do this anytime.
I'll wash you down here, too.
I can't believe the normally
passive Roxanne is being so...
Let me know if I'm using too much pressure.
This is amazing.
I agree. I feel great.
I had no idea bathing with
Roxanne could be so incredible.
This silky feeling...
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
It must be Roxanne's tail.
Roxanne.
How are your injuries?
Thanks to your treatment, as you can see,
they've healed completely.
They don't even hurt.
I see.
Roxanne?
I haven't washed your lips yet.
I may have access to healing spells,
but I can't keep putting
all the burden on Roxanne.
And the solution to my problem is
to add more front-line fighters to my party.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem