Quratar, Michio's House
Skill Crystal
Rabbit
A Skill Crystal...
It probably allows you to
create an item with a skill
Identify
Scimitar
Skill Slot
Empty
when you combine it with an empty skill slot.
The problem is finding a dwarf with
the dwarf-specific Blacksmith job.
Now how am I going to find one?
I'm ready.
Sorry for making you do it yourself.
It's fine.
Cooking is supposed to be my job.
You shouldn't have to help me.
We can have that conversation another time.
Our food will get cold.
You're right.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
Huh? What?
But it was green until recently.
It's probably because I merged
two crystals recently.
But...
Don't tell anyone.
You said yellow Magic Crystals can
be sold for 100 thousand nars, right?
Yes, that's correct.
Then we'll have the money we need.
Roxanne, change of plans.
Let's go to Vale after this.
Do you have business there?
I'm going to pay a visit to Alan.
I want to write a will.
A will?
Don't make that face.
I realized something after
that incident the other day.
I should be prepared to die
if I'm entering labyrinths.
Normally when a master dies,
their slaves join them in death, right?
I want you to be freed when I die.
I appreciate that, but...
If you trust me,
then please don't write a will.
What?
I'll protect you.
I'm a warrior.
If my master died,
I wouldn't be able to
continue living in disgrace.
She's not joking.
Of course I depend on you, and I
understand what you're trying to say.
But labyrinths aren't the
only places I might die.
I could even drop dead from an illness.
I'd find a way to cure you.
Um, are you serious?
Yes.
She's actually for real.
If you insist, then I won't.
Thank you.
But why?
Because you're a wonderful man.
You're young, strong, and skilled.
I'm sure you'll achieve great things.
And on top of that,
you've been nothing but kind to me.
I must return the favor.
I see.
Roxanne called herself a warrior.
She's like a loyal samurai willing
to sacrifice herself for me.
I probably can't change her mind, but...
Let me say this, though.
Yes, Master.
I probably won't achieve
anything significant.
That's not...
No, it's true.
If anything, I'm here specifically
to achieve nothing.
I don't understand.
You don't have to understand.
Just know that's how it is.
Very well.
But we're still going to Vale.
I've got other business with Alan.
I realized during battle the other day that
it's time to think about expanding our party.
You're right.
Monsters start appearing in groups
of four, starting on the eighth floor.
If I'm going to be focusing on magic,
then I'd like another front-line fighter.
Ideally, a woman.
No, they don't have to be a woman.
They don't have to be, but...
So good. Who could deny the appeal of this?
Master?
Wh-What is it, Roxanne?
I think recruiting more party
members is a good idea.
Would it be all right if I accompanied
you to Mr. Alan's mansion?
Yeah, of course.
If Roxanne is opposed to the idea,
then I don't have to choose a woman.
Vale
Alan's Mansion
Please wait here.
Roxanne, have a seat.
Are you sure?
If you don't sit,
he'll think I'm back to sell you.
In that case, excuse me.
Well, well.
Thank you for coming, Mr. Michio.
Sorry for always dropping in out of the blue.
Not at all.
You're welcome to come anytime.
So, what can I do for you today?
I'm thinking about adding
another party member.
A good idea.
I'd like to ask you something.
Would it be possible to
purchase a Blacksmith slave?
A Blacksmith? You mean a dwarf.
It's not impossible, but it is difficult.
Are you aware merging
Skill Crystals often fails?
Yes.
Because those are so valuable,
repeated failures can affect the
relationship between a slave and their master.
It's not uncommon for it to end
unfortunately for both parties.
Because dwarves know that,
they don't often become
slaves as Blacksmiths.
I'm sure they don't.
As a result, there are
few Blacksmith slaves,
making them quite expensive.
What about a dwarf who isn't a Blacksmith?
Dwarves are a powerful people.
They make excellent front-line fighters.
If you're looking for new party members,
a dwarf would be perfect.
However...
Currently I have a single dwarf,
but unfortunately,
her personality isn't suited to fighting.
"Her?" So she's a woman.
If you're determined to acquire a dwarf,
I could write you a letter of
introduction to another shop.
Well, what do you think, Roxanne?
Huh? Uh, um...
As long as we're here,
why don't we meet the dwarf he has?
If you don't like her, then you
simply don't need to acquire her.
I see. It's free to take a look.
You heard her.
Could you show us the dwarf?
Very well.
I'll have her get ready.
Wait here, please.
So anyway, I bought a house in Quratar.
I see.
Enter.
She's ready.
That's the woman Roxanne
mentioned who treated her well.
Bring her here.
Come in.
This is the only dwarf I
currently have, Sherry.
Sixteen years old?
She's the same age as Roxanne.
These ears...
They look like elf ears, but I guess
dwarves have ears like these, too.
He said dwarves are suited to front-line fighting,
but she doesn't look particularly muscular.
She seems like a short girl who's
fairly mature, slender, and cute.
U-Um, it's nice to meet you.
Uh...
I'm already a level ten Explorer.
Yeah, my Identify skill already told me that.
If you're an Explorer, then you won't
have any problems entering labyrinths.
Actually, that's not what I meant.
I...
I failed to become a Blacksmith.
I don't understand.
Do you mind if we have a seat
so I can ask her some questions?
Go ahead.
What do you mean, you failed?
Once dwarves become level ten Explorers,
they have the option to change
their job to Blacksmith.
And you couldn't?
No.
How is whether or not a dwarf can
become a Blacksmith determined?
Generally those who have an
aptitude for exploring labyrinths
can also become Blacksmiths.
In other words, since she
couldn't become a Blacksmith,
she wouldn't be useful in labyrinths either.
But is it really possible for a dwarf
to fail to become a Blacksmith
because they lack aptitude?
In this world, jobs are learned.
Status
Kaga Michio
<Male 17 Years Old>
Villager: Lv 1
Thief: Lv 1
Equipment: Sandals
I was able to acquire
the Hero and Thief jobs.
Villager: Lv 1
Thief: Lv 1
Equipment: Sandals
Meteor Crash
Gamma Ray Burst
Extreme Drop Dead
Self-Destruct
Equivalent Exchange
Though the conditions were complex,
I was even able to acquire the Mage job.
It's hard to believe the
Blacksmith job alone is innate.
How is a dwarf's aptitude measured, anyway?
Mage: Lv 1
Effect: Minor Intelligence Increase
Effect: Tiny MP Increase
Skill: Novice Level Fire Magic
Skill: Novice Level Water Magic
Skill: Novice Level Air Magic
Skill: Novice Level Earth Magic
Can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
Once you fail to become a Blacksmith,
is it impossible to become
one in the future?
The Blacksmiths Guild only allows
level ten Explorers to change jobs.
It's not as though there
are no prior examples,
but I don't know exactly.
I see.
It sounds like becoming
a Blacksmith has conditions
other than just being a level ten Explorer.
Are they abstract and difficult
conditions to meet like aptitude?
As long as she can fulfill those,
even this girl should be able
to acquire the Blacksmith job.
And it'd be a waste to turn her away
just because she's not a Blacksmith.
She's exactly the type of person I'd
want for my second party member.
I was one of the strongest
people in my village.
I'm tall for a dwarf,
and I won't cause you any
trouble in labyrinths.
I hope you'll take that into consideration.
Anyway, Roxanne was the same, but why?
Are you finished?
Oh, yeah.
In that case...
Why is she so assertive?
If I were a slave, I doubt I'd
try so hard to sell myself.
I think it's because it's a good deal.
Is it?
She'd be going into dangerous labyrinths.
She's either been to them before
or is planning on entering them.
I certainly did.
Do you think that dwarf seems promising?
Well...
I don't know much about dwarves,
but even if she lacks aptitude,
as long as she has the resolve,
then she'll manage with
hard work and training.
I see.
So she's not opposed to the idea
just because she's a woman.
But I doubt she'll be able
to do much for very long.
That's probably why she's not expensive.
I think she'd be a good purchase.
Wait a minute.
Why wouldn't she be able
to do much for very long?
She must be of a certain age.
Perhaps we should get confirmation.
What does that mean?
Sherry was definitely 16 years old.
It's her ears.
Her ears?
Dwarves' ears get thinner with age.
Hers are rather thin, so...
Is that how it works?
Thank you for waiting.
Would it be all right if I excused
myself for a moment? She...
She took care of you, right?
Go talk to her.
Thank you.
Now then, what did you think of Sherry?
Well, depending on the price,
she might not be a bad pickup.
Is that so?
Sherry may not be a Blacksmith,
but she's a 16-year-old dwarf.
She understands that she'll be a sex slave.
Since she's a virgin,
you needn't worry about diseases.
I see.
I get it now.
He had Roxanne excuse herself
so he could tell me this.
Her ears seemed a bit thin.
Indeed. But she was born that way.
I can guarantee Sherry is 16 years old.
That doesn't change the
fact that they're thin.
Naturally, her price can
be reduced accordingly.
How does 300 thousand nars sound?
Rather, I wish I could charge that much,
but she hasn't been here long.
Her training is lacking in some areas,
so how about 270 thousand nars?
That's way cheaper than the 600
thousand he charged for Roxanne.
But I can't jump at this price.
Then 260 thousand.
He dropped the price.
No, 250 thousand.
That's the lowest I can go.
He must be hoping to sell her now.
Then, I'll push a little harder.
That much?
I see...
Huh? He can't go any lower, huh?
But I've still got a card up my sleeve.
Character Settings
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
30% Sale Price Increase
Bonus Weapon
Incantation Reduction
Critical Strike Rate
Roxanne came with an outfit.
If you'll include one with her,
then I'll consider it.
That outfit?
It costs 4,000 nars.
That's fine.
In that case, since I owe you
for assisting me the other day,
how about 177,800 nars for both?
Sounds good.
Thank you for your purchase.
I'm glad I have this 30% discount.
Were you able to have a nice chat?
Yes, thank you.
About the girl...
I've decided to have her come with us.
I see. I'm glad to hear that.
Did I imagine that?
It looked like her face
clouded over for a moment.
Did it seem that way because I feel guilty,
or because I want her to be jealous?
Thank you for waiting.
Sherry, approach the customer.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for having me.
Thanks for joining the party.
Anyway, that's a ton of hair.
What's going on here?
I'm Roxanne, the number one slave.
Nice to meet you.
When was the "number one slave"
position established?
So you are a slave.
I thought you were his wife.
His wife? Don't be silly.
I heard you once stayed here.
Roxanne, I wish you hadn't
denied that so flatly.
You have such nice clothes,
and your hair is such a pretty color.
It's because my master is a
kind and wonderful person.
We have nothing to worry about when it
comes to clothes, food, and housing.
The contract is sealed.
Please check your Intelligence Cards.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Sherry <Female 16 Years Old> Explorer – Slave
Owner: Kaga Michio
Okay. Here's mine.
Kaga Michio <Male 17 Years Old> Explorer – Free Man
Owned Slaves: Roxanne, Sherry
Looks good.
Very good, sir.
The clothes will take some time to prepare.
Please return in ten days' time.
Got it.
I look forward to seeing you again.
Now, then.
Party Formation.
[Party]
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Huh? What?
Oh, I'll join.
Sherry
Okay, good.
Now you're a member of our party.
Yes, Master.
And now I can finally check.
Party Job Settings.
[Party]
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Sherry
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Sherry
Equipped Jobs
1st Explorer Lv 10
Jobs
Explorer: Lv 10
Villager Lv 3
Herbalist: Lv 1
Blacksmith really isn't there.
Since I don't know the conditions for
unlocking it, there's not much I can say,
but it's not impossible.
I'll just have to have Sherry
try a bunch of different things.
Shall we head back to our house in Quratar?
Understood.
What?
Um, Ms. Roxanne.
What is it?
Um, are there Adventurers in this party?
No, why?
He just said we'd be going back to the house.
Oh, she thinks we're going to use Field Walk.
Since I showed her my Intelligence Card,
Kaga Michio <Male 17 Years Old> Explorer – Free Man
Owned Slaves: Roxanne, Sherry
she knows I'm an Explorer,
and Field Walk is an Adventurer skill.
It does seem odd that I can use that.
But I'm not sure how to explain it to her.
It's all right. Come with us, and you'll see.
She didn't even try to explain it.
It would've been convenient if she'd
offered some kind of explanation.
What?
U-Um...?
Come with us.
Huh? What?
What?
Um...
Oh, boy. She's confused.
Have a seat.
You can sit.
But I'm a slave.
It's fine. We'll even be eating together.
What? We'll be eating together?
He's our master.
This is our home in Quratar.
Starting today, you'll be living here.
Yes, Master.
Um, are you...
Are you capable of using multiple jobs?
Wow, she figured that out without any hints.
Close. I don't have the Adventurer job.
What we used earlier was a
transportation spell called Teleport.
Teleport...
Sherry, do you know people
with multiple jobs?
Myths mention gods like that.
Then think of me as that kind of person.
But myths are made up stories.
Of course she'd say that.
I know, Sherry.
What kind of weapon would you
like to use in the labyrinths?
I'm good with a spear.
But if I'll be fighting alongside
allies on the front lines,
then a maul would be good.
A maul?
Is that like a hammer?
Come to think of it, defeating monsters
with a sword and defeating monsters
with bare hands were the conditions
for becoming a swordsman and a monk.
A hammer would suit a Blacksmith, so maybe...
Sherry, have you ever beaten
a monster with a maul?
No.
Then try using a maul for a while.
Are you okay with that, Roxanne?
Yes.
We'll keep monsters in check
by serving as the front line
so you can prepare to cast
spells from the back.
What? Spells?
You mean like offensive spells?
Yes.
What do you mean by that?
I can use them.
He can use them.
What?!
Don't tell anyone.
It's a secret.
Um...
U-Understood.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem