in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
Vale
Alan's Mansion
The door is open.
Could you handle things here, please?
What?
I've had those who look after the slaves
or can't fight gather on the second floor.
I'd like you to protect them.
That was my plan from the start.
I can't expose my customers
to anything too dangerous.
The fighting has started.
Someone's coming.
Bandit: Lv 3
It's him.
Given his level, he probably waited for
an opportunity to escape and fled here.
Come on, now. Fleeing into
that room won't help you.
But this is an opportunity.
Roxanne, stay here.
Yes, Master.
In order to acquire the Mage job,
I tried casting my bonus
incantations at random.
Gamma Ray Burst
Meteor Crash
But perhaps due to lack of MP,
none of them worked.
There are still some I
haven't tested yet, though.
Meteor Crash
Gamma Ray Burst
Extreme Drop Dead
Self-Destruct
Equivalent Exchange
There's no way I'm casting Self-Destruct,
so the question is what this incantation does.
Self-Destruct
Equivalent Exchange
Judging by the name, it sounds like a
spell that trades one thing for another.
And if it is, then it's likely to be HP.
Live
Equivalent Exchange!
In that case, if my target
has more HP than me,
Die
I'd probably die.
It was too dangerous to test on monsters
whose HP total I didn't know, but...
Identify
Givan
<Male 21 Years Old>
Bandit: Lv 3
Equipment: Copper Sword
I'm a level 3 Bandit, too,
and I've got other jobs.
It's hard to imagine I have less HP than him.
Wh-Who's there? Is that you, brother?
This would've been difficult if
we could see each other clearly.
In any case, I've gotta do it.
Meteor Crash
Gamma Ray Burst
Extreme Drop Dead
Self-Destruct
Equivalent Exchange
Equivalent Exchange!
This powerfully unpleasant feeling...
I must've lost MP. A ton of it, too.
It worked. It actually worked.
I wish it had failed instead.
What have I done?
Master. Are you all right, Master?
Roxanne, when did you get here?
Mr. Michio, are you all right?
Yeah.
One of the bandits escaped.
I believe he came this way.
What is this?
Crap. He'll definitely find this weird.
Was it a Self-Destruct Orb?
Self-Destruct Orb?
I've heard it's an item
that does this to people.
I didn't expect these bandits
to have any, though.
I'm not sure what's going on,
but it seems like he didn't
figure out I cast a spell.
I've recovered some of my MP.
Master.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah, barely.
If I'd run out of HP first,
I would've ended up like that.
Thank you for today.
Here's your reward.
Thanks.
Well, excuse us.
I feel terrible.
I need to restore my MP soon.
Um...
I'm sorry this happened because
of my selfish demands.
You have nothing to apologize for.
This happened because I insisted
on testing Equivalent Exchange.
I need to get to the labyrinth
as soon as possible.
I screwed up.
Casting Warp would obviously consume my MP.
How did I fail to realize
something so obvious?
I'm an idiot.
Master.
All right. I've recovered completely.
Master, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
Now then.
Mage: Lv 1
Effect: Minor Intelligence Increase
Tiny MP Increase
Skill: Novice Level Fire Magic
Novice Level Water Magic
Novice Level Air Magic
Novice Level Earth Magic
There it is. Casting Equivalent
Exchange was the right choice.
What spells can I cast?
Novice level spells for
fire, water, air, and earth.
Roxanne, what kinds of spells do Mages cast?
I've heard there are three types of spells.
Those that damage all targets,
those that create walls,
and those that fire orbs.
Huh.
Producing fire is probably an attack spell.
An orb of fire? Or a flaming sphere?
Fiery Orb, Flaming Sphere, Fireball?
So Fireball was right. Let's see.
All right, it worked.
I can finally cast spells.
Huh? What?
Master, aren't you an Explorer?
How did you cast that spell?
Don't tell anyone.
Impressive as always, Master.
Fireball!
It didn't go down in one hit.
Well, I'm sure its power will
increase as I gain levels.
I'll try making a wall next.
Since it's a wall of fire...
Firewall!
I see. That's certainly a wall.
Yes, Master.
This is probably for defense.
That just leaves the multi-target attack.
Since the other two were "ball" and "wall"...
Fire Strike? Fire Attack? Firestorm?
Whoa, I lost MP.
Nothing happened even though I expended MP.
Is it because there were no enemies nearby?
In that case...
Roxanne, let's head to the second floor.
Yes, Master.
Vale Labyrinth, Second Floor
Perfect. There's two of them.
Firestorm!
Dude, magic is awesome.
After that, I learned from various tests that
spells are a combination of elements and form.
In other words,
"Ball" produces a single-target attack.
Ball
Wall
Storm
"Wall" creates a defensive barrier.
"Storm" is a multi-target attack.
"Fire," "water," "breeze" and "sand"
can be combined with each one.
For example, a wall of water can
be produced with the incantation...
Waterwall!
Like that.
Hey, Roxanne. Do you think
we can drink this water?
Probably.
I see.
We no longer need to carry
around heavy flasks.
Thinking ahead, I'd like to switch from
relying on Durandal to primarily
using magic in combat.
Because
I want to protect Roxanne.
She has such a gentle personality
and she serves me well.
I can't imagine losing her.
To that end, we should farm experience
so we can raise our level.
In the long run, that should reduce our risk.
Master?
I'm thinking about using primarily
magic in combat from now on.
It might be an inconvenience, since it'll
take us longer to defeat monsters.
It's no problem at all.
Roxanne truly is wonderful.
That said...
This would be easier if my spells
were a little more powerful.
You're right. I've heard
Mages often carry staves.
A staff, huh?
That's exactly the kind of thing you'd
expect a Mage to carry around, but...
The next market day is in four days.
It'll be a while before we can acquire one.
You're right.
Around here, you'd need to go to
Quratar to visit a permanent shop.
Quratar?
Yes.
There's a large labyrinth there,
so there are many shops serving Explorers.
It might be worth checking out.
Vale Labyrinth, Second Floor
Boss Waiting Room
We're already at the boss room?
There doesn't seem to be anyone waiting.
Shall we attempt the boss?
Let's do it.
Vale Labyrinth, Second Floor
Boss Room
I-I've got a bad feeling about this.
A bug. I knew it.
But I don't have time to be intimidated.
Firewall!
Here I go.
Then I'll attack from behind.
Good work.
Not at all. Thanks to you,
we were able to defeat it quickly.
Okay, onto the third floor.
Yes, Master.
Vale Labyrinth, Third Floor
There's probably a single kobold up ahead.
A kobold, huh?
I haven't seen one of those before,
but if it's just one, that's perfect
for seeing what they're like.
There it is.
It's got a knife.
Kobold: Lv 3
He who strikes first, wins.
Fireball!
It's so weak.
Kobolds are beginner level monsters.
Salt, huh? How much is this worth?
I believe it's the cheapest
item you can sell at the guild.
One is worth four nars.
So cheap.
They may be monsters,
but kobolds look like people.
If I'd encountered these before
I'd gotten used to this world,
I may not have been able
to handle them calmly.
When I think of it that way,
maybe it's for the best that kobolds didn't
start appearing until the third floor.
Firestorm!
It's not salt this time.
Some monsters drop a variety of items.
It's full already.
Let's leave for the day.
Yes, Master.
Those must be heavy. I'll carry a few.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I've got space in my Item Box.
Um, forgive me,
but may I ask what your level is, Master?
Huh? I'm a level 20 Explorer.
Level 20? Impressive, Master.
Don't tell anyone.
Yes, Master.
My level is a little high for my age,
but I don't think it's that unbelievable.
Thank you for waiting.
Sure.
One-way trip to the Imperial City.
Anyone for a one-way trip
to the Imperial City?
One-way trip to the Imperial City.
She's using Field Walk like a stagecoach.
Even a trip that's a several days' walk
can be completed in an instant
if you're willing to pay.
It's convenient.
I see. That's one way to make money.
I might've gone to Quratar, but I've
got no business in the Imperial City,
so it's none of my business.
Quratar and the Imperial City
are near each other.
They are?
When I previously visited Quratar,
I passed through the Imperial City.
I'm not sure if you can travel
directly to Quratar from here,
but you can definitely
get to the Imperial City.
I see. Then maybe we should go.
Yes, Master. I'll see you later.
I'll be waiting here for you to return.
What?
The cost is per person.
If I go to Quratar alone,
then we'll be able to travel there
for free using Warp going forward.
That's certainly true, but I guess
Roxanne is stronger than I thought.
One-way trip to the Imperial City.
How much?
One silver coin.
For my trusted companions.
Whoops!
I need to remove Roxanne from my party.
[Party]
•Kaga Michio
•Roxanne
Pure-hearted and sincere.
Party formation.
Confirm Party Formation
Yes
No
Let's go.
This must be the
Imperial City Adventurers' Guild.
It's much larger than Vale's.
Wait, I don't have time to stand
around staring. Let's see.
Excuse me, but could you
take me to Quratar next?
Yes, certainly.
Huh. I thought this place would be bigger,
but it's actually pretty small.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
I should return to Roxanne now.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
Whoa.
Master, are you all right?
I made it back okay,
but I expended more MP than I expected.
Now we can go to Quratar anytime.
Let's head back to the inn for today.
Yes, Master.
Is this the right amount of pressure?
I-I can wash the front myself.
No, we'd better make sure we
don't leave anything behind.
Kiss me.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Master, you can thrust a little harder.
This is a room at an inn.
There are other people just beyond the wall.
If we lived in a house,
I could enjoy my time with Roxanne
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
without worrying about anyone else.
Town of Quratar
I see. Like you said, we should be
able to get most of what we need here.
Master, the labyrinth is this way.
Oh, whoops.
Quratar's labyrinth is at
the center of the town.
All major roads radiate out from it.
Look, you can see it now.
Quratar Labyrinth Entrance
What's everyone doing?
They're paying the entry fee.
What?
So you have to pay every time?
Couldn't we enter without paying the
fee by using your teleportation magic?
Roxanne, you're a smart girl.
Thank you.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem