Everything was shrouded in complete darkness.
I have to take her hand.
But to take her hand, I...
Just for her hand...
I...
Come to your senses, Kasuga Arata.
If you do not, you will die by my hand.
Make your choice, Kasuga Arata.
For it was your wish that created this world,
and your wish alone.
A Black Sun
A black sun...
Its black light swallowed everyone up.
Breakdown
Phenomenon
Please.
Save Arata-san.
Grant his wish.
Please...
don't forget about me.
Hijiri?
Hijiri!
Royal Biblia Academy.
I came here to bring Hijiri back
from wherever in the world she went off to.
This school has seven students who are like a game's boss characters.
Boss characters?
The Trinity Seven.
That's what they're called.
Seven mages who excel in their respective fields.
My figure has nothing to do with this.
Asami Lilith.
89, 55, 89.
I'm a ninja. The name's Kazama Levi.
Kazama Levi.
78, 54, 77.
This is pretty difficult.
Kannazuki Arin.
83, 56, 84.
I will allow no impurity before me.
Yamana Mira.
79, 55, 78.
It's my job to exterminate evil!
Fudou Akio.
82, 56, 83.
You're all invited to my world!
Kurata Yui.
84, 55, 83.
I would stop time for you,
so we could do whatever we wanted to.
Lieselotte Sherlock.
85, 56, 84.
These girls, known as the Trinity Seven,
research their respective Archives
These are the Themas
bestowed upon these 7 girls
to master their own Themas.
I'm also studying every day so
I can become a mage, but...
Arata!
I did not expect a demon lord candidate's magic to be this powerful.
I have no choice.
Now that it's come to this, I have to at least...
Demon Lord
Element
So I have this thing called
a "demon lord element"
that makes its presence known at times.
Demon
Lord
Candidate
Demon
Lord
Candidate
Apparently, I was born as a
"demon lord candidate."
And they say that I was the one
who destroyed this world.
Surrender yourself to me.
Then I guess I'll have to show you what I'm made of.
Astil Codex
So now our cast includes me, the Trinity Seven,
Iliad Fragment
Okay, Arata-san!
my grimoires, Sora and Ilia,
Liese's sister, Selina,
I'll go.
a mage from Iscariot, Lugh,
Gospel  Seekers
Iscariot
I shall respond with equal resolve.
a paladin named Master Liber,
Whatever shall we do?
and my childhood friend, Hijiri.
I have earned the right
to be declared a Trinity.
Our journey to study and
master our magic continues!
I believe everyone loves you a lot.
U-Uh...
Arata...
Husband...
Onii-san...
Arata-kun.
Arata-san.
Arata!
Want to touch my boobs?
Impure boy.
It's my husband's fault.
My wonderful demon lord candidate.
You've worked really hard.
But I won't die, either.
I'm going to pick the third option.
Everyone, I'm about to make a selfish request,
but please help me out.
Let's go, everyone!
Run, Lilith!
I can't run away and leave you behind!
In that case, I'll end both of you.
Get away, Lilith!
No, I won't!
Just get away from me!
Damn it...
Isn't there anything I can do?
Oops, my bad. I didn't mean to do that.
I just couldn't resist grabbing it.
But what I really wanted to grab is this!
Please use me, Papa-sama!
And that was my dream last night, Liese.
You know, if you like butts so much, you can touch mine all you want.
Hey, Onee-chan! That's my body, you know!
Hey, I won't allow any of that, Arata!
No perverted behavior.
I'll make that my goal for the month.
He doesn't plan to give up at all!
I guess there's no other choice.
I'll let you do all the lewd stuff you
want to my actual body instead, darling.
Oh? I am completely okay with that.
We're absolutely not!
My master never changes!
So what was Arata-kun's dream about, Ilia-chan?
Well, Arata-san is a demon lord candidate,
so I'd think there would be some sort
of significance to his dreams...
Do you know anything, Sora?
Hmm, not really.
Though I'd imagine that lady over there appears in his dreams quite often.
Arata dreams about me?
Yeah, that's true.
I always have these dreams where I fondle
her breasts then get slapped right after.
I-I think that's just your memories and
your desires merging together, Arata-san.
So what you're saying is now he wants to
grope Lilith-sensei's butt, too?
That's probably not it.
Like, this is Arata-kun we're talking about.
Considering I lost to him,
it has to be something really amazing.
I'm curious as to why my
grimoire was shining as well.
So that's your grimoire, huh?
Yes, the Hermes Apocrypha.
That feeling just now...
Arata!
What's happening!?
Master's magic is being
absorbed by the grimoire!
We have to stop it!
M-My grimoire is absorbing Arata's magic...
ETERNAL LIBRARY & ALCHEMIC GIRL
Uh...
This is...
My grimoire...
took on a human form?
Papa-sama! Mama-sama!
Papa-sama!?
Mama-sama!?
Uh, so who are you?
Please give me any name you like, Papa-sama.
Can I?
Well, you look a bit like Lilith, so... Lilim.
Arata, you can't just...
Lilim!
I received word that my husband had a child.
You can call me mother as well.
What?
My Mama-sama is Mama-sama alone!
This is pretty difficult.
So this child belongs to you and Sensei, correct?
Yeah, that's not far off the mark.
I'd say it very much is!
I sense both Lilith-sensei's
and my husband's magic from her,
so I was sure that she was your child...
But she's a grimoire, isn't she?
So you have both of our magic, then?
Onii-san!
I felt some really strong magic just now...
I wanna make a kid with you, too!
I wanna!
Hold up, hold up.
I didn't actually have a kid, you know.
You didn't?
Then she's not your and Lilith-sensei's child?
No, of course not!
She's...
Mama-sama!
Lilith?
I... I don't think I mind considering her as my child anymore.
Yay! Mama-sama!
So what happened here, anyway?
Yo, ninja. You know anything about this?
Oh? So you noticed I was here?
Nah, I figured you'd be hanging around.
I'm glad I could live up to your expectations.
Lilith-sensei's grimoire sucked up your
magic and took on a human form.
That about sums it up.
But I'm way more interested in learning exactly how far you and Lilith-sensei have gone together.
W-We haven't gone anywhere!
Hey, 'sup everyone?
I sensed an impure presence here.
Did you do something again?
Whoa, Nii-chan, Lilith-sensei...
So you had this kid who looks exactly like the two of you, huh?
What!?
Then it really is true!?
I-I think that's about enough.
Lilith, I know Lilim is really cute and all, but people are getting the wrong idea.
I can't believe myself.
I forgot about my responsibilities as a teacher.
Hey, darling...
Oh, too bad.
I wanted to have a kid with you, too.
Hey, just what do you think you're doing, Liese-san!?
How's it going, Lilim-san?
Would you like some candy?
Here you go.
Thank you!
Here I go.
I'm so happy.
I'm so glad I could experience a grimoire licking a lollipop.
Please stop toying with Lilim!
Mama-sama's chest feels nice.
Oh, Lilim...
Mama-sama...
Oh, ho! Allow me!
You may not, Arata!
Well, it's great that we're all having a blast here, but you know...
You don't look too good.
Oh right, Lilim took my magic.
There he goes.
Arata!
It seems, Liber-chan, that
your prophecy has come true.
The forbidden world,
the Eternal Library, has awakened.
Yes, our world could meet its end,
Headmaster of Biblia Academy.
Well, that'd be a problem.
Would you mind helping me out?
Are you sure?
We're Iscariot. We vanquish demon lords, you know.
That's why I'd like you two to back me up
as well, Hijiri-chan and Lugh-chan.
Are you sure? I'm...
Well, it seems that Arata-kun
will die at this rate.
I will be the one to defeat Arata-san.
I'm probably the second
strongest in the world,
so no problem here.
Who could be so dangerous, anyway?
The alchemist sealed away
in the Eternal Library,
the ultimate product of Outer Alchemic:
the man-made creation: the White Demon Lord.
Awaken, White Demon Lord.
Who are you?
I am a Magus who expects
great things from you.
A Magus... I see...
So the magic cast on the Hermes Apocrypha,
my creator, has been activated, then?
Indeed.
When the demon lord candidate
touched the grimoire,
the Eternal Library awakened
from its long slumber.
And now the time has arrived for the master of this place
to become the true demon lord.
The time for me to become
the true demon lord...
You were born as the White
Demon Lord for the sole purpose
of fighting the demon lord candidate.
That's right.
The Trinity Seven's demon
lord will come here soon.
If I defeat that demon lord,
then I will become one!
That's right.
I am expecting great things from you,
White Demon Lord, Last Trinity.
Now, what will you do, Arata-kun?
What will I do...
What, another dream?
Her voice sure sounded nice, though...
Hey.
You awake now, Master?
It seems your magic has recovered as well.
I guess you two helped me out.
Thanks.
Well, now that things have settled down,
I guess I'll go take a bath.
Sounds great. I'll join you.
Sure, thanks.
No, you can't!
Women's Bath
Wh-What are you doing, Arata?
Oh, it's Papa-sama!
Lilim!
Oh, Lilim, you were taking a bath, too?
You were resting, so we were
all taking care of her.
I made friends with her, too!
I see.
Well, that's good.
You two need to cover yourselves!
What an unfortunate accident.
Well, with the way things were going,
what else could've happened?
It's nice taking a bath with everyone.
Honestly, Arata...
Papa-sama and Mama-sama
get along so well.
We sure do.
But why would a grimoire
take a human form?
It's strange for them to
suddenly gain consciousness.
Then does that mean you two are some kind of exceptions to the idea?
Yes, the grimoires Sora and
I originally came from
had consciousness to begin with, so...
Did you know that my original form had quite the bounce to it?
Seriously!?
I'd love to see it!
Papa-sama, Mama-sama is...
Mama-sama is pretty bouncy herself!
See!?
S-Stop...
Don't count me out, either!
Mira and I come out on top in terms of shape.
I-I'm not participating in this contest!
It's okay, Selina-san.
You have the same blood in
your veins as Liese-san.
I'm sure yours will grow in time.
Y-You think so?
Hey, Boss, if you cover up that tightly,
he's gonna see your nips.
Just kidding.
Smirk, smirk.
Come on, you guys!
Don't make fun of me!
Mira-chan's so silly.
Thanks, Lilim.
For what, Papa-sama?
Everyone's having so much
fun because you're around.
So thank you, Lilim.
Not at all.
You're all taking such good care of me.
I couldn't be more grateful.
Yeah?
If it's okay with you,
we can take a bath anytime you want.
Thank you, Mama-sama!
They really do look like a married couple.
Yeah, it makes you feel all warm inside.
I want to act married with my husband, too.
I want to pretend to be a wife, too!
How impure...
But it really is great that we're all able to relax like this.
Yeah.
Oh, by the way, I had another dream earlier.
Really?
I heard a girl's voice and she sounded really nice.
Let me see...
I sense an alchemist and
a magic close to Yui-san's.
It's possible that a magic for controlling dreams, like mine, is being used.
Like a fairy or a spirit.
Dreams, huh?
Well, I did have that other dream earlier.
What type of dream was it, Master?
Well, I was sleeping, and this
really sweet voice woke me up...
Oh, but she might not
have been talking to me.
She wanted this "White Demon Lord" to awaken.
I think his name was...
"Last Trinity."
What is this?
A Luxuria breakdown phenomenon!
Let's go, everyone!
Right!
Yes.
Got it, husband.
Roger.
I'm going, too.
Let's go!
Of course.
Right.
Connecting to Superbia Archive.
Execute Thema!
Connecting to Luxuria Archive.
Execute Thema.
Connecting to Ira Archive.
Connecting to Invidia Archive.
Execute Thema.
Connecting to Avaritia Archive.
Connecting to Gula Archive.
Execute Thema.
Connecting to Superbia Archive.
Connecting to Acedia Archive.
Execute Thema.
Sora! Ilia!
Right!
Got it!
Mama-sama, I'll help you.
Right. Realize!
Oh? They wasted no time showing up.
What an impure aura!
Well, let's get this started.
Yep.
Oh, good evening, Levi-san.
Good evening, Lugh-san.
Oh, you're...
the girl with the perfectly soft, palm-sized boobs.
I'm aghast that the demon lord candidate
has such a weird way of remembering me.
You shouldn't remember girls like that!
Good evening, Arata-san.
Hijiri...
Did you all do this?
Not at all.
This school's headmaster asked us to help.
The headmaster?
You expect us to believe that!?
Looks like we don't have time to chat, Boss.
I believe you, Hijiri!
Arata-san...
So what's going on?
It seems we have been sucked into the world of the Eternal Library.
The Eternal Library...
Also known as the workshop
of the progenitor of alchemy, Hohenheim?
That's correct.
Lilith-san's progenitor mage was
doing research on how to create
an artificial demon lord here.
He is also referred to as "the White Demon Lord."
The White Demon Lord...
I heard that name in my dream.
Yes. Supposedly that artificial
demon lord will awaken
and come to defeat you, Arata-san.
I see.
Then the words in that dream weren't for me,
but for that White Demon Lord.
The master of the Eternal Library,
the White Demon Lord.
When you spoke his name,
It's likely that this world became linked with ours.
It might have been the progenitor mage's plan
to have the alchemist's grimoire go berserk
and absorb Arata-san's magic, too.
So when I ate tons of Papa-sama's magic...
And now that the
White Demon Lord has returned,
he's caused a breakdown phenomenon
in his attempt to destroy this world.
As another demon lord, do you feel anything?
Well...
I feel a strong power from within the school.
That might be the White Demon Lord.
Oh, here comes a big one.
Be careful, husband.
That's a...
Code D!?
It's huge!
It seems to be a Sealed Magic Beast that was sealed within the Eternal Library.
I smell treasure.
I see.
So it's best to have us handle this,
while Arata-san and the others
go after the White Demon Lord.
Yes.
Let's take it out at once.
Yeah.
Best of luck, Nii-chan and everyone.
If all of you are staying behind,
I might as well join in, too.
All right!
I got nothing to worry about with you five around.
You're the strongest five around!
Okay, we'll meet up with you later.
Arata-san and company, go on ahead.
You set up a death flag with that line, you know.
What? I-Is that so?
In any case, we'll leave the Code D to you.
Go get 'em!
Arata, where are we going?
This way.
He's over here.
Papa-sama!
Eihwaz!
Thanks, Hijiri, Arin.
No, I'm just glad you're okay, Arata-san.
Yeah, I'm glad you're okay, husband.
That was an Outer Alchemic...
Oh?
So you blocked that, huh?
Are you the White Demon Lord?
Indeed.
I am the White Demon Lord, Last Trinity,
demon lord candidate.
He looks just like you, Arata.
Yeah.
This is bad, Arata-san!
Husband!
Too late.
Arata!
The demon lord candidate's magic is now mine!
Onii-san!
He can take Arata-san's magic
just by looking at him...
Not just his magic.
That's Arata's—
I have no need for you any longer,
Demon Lord Candidate!
Arata-san!
Husband!
Hijiri! Arin!
Arin-san, I'm going in to attack.
I'll back you up, Hijiri.
Themas: Ruina, Partum, Analysis!
Oh?
Reconnecting to Ira Archive.
Execute Thema.
The demon spear, Gáe Bulg.
How interesting.
An Ira Magus with a legendary weapon.
A perfect sacrifice for me,
Last, the White Demon Lord.
It won't be that simple.
I am a mage who exists to kill demon lords.
Black Azazel!
And I am the wife of a demon lord.
We did it!
No, look closely.
It seems he has regenerative abilities.
N-No way...
Reconnecting to Avaritia Archive.
Execute Thema.
Meteo Symphony!
Yui-san's offensive magic...
No way...
Now I know all of your powers.
Even if you do, you cannot stop this spell.
Vegtamskviða!
Hijiri! Arin! Yui!
Arata-san, please run.
I won't let you, Ira Magus!
This is...
He put up a barrier.
Now we can't get help
from the outside, either.
Now, demon lord candidate...
I shall take the last of your magic.
Arata!
My magic affects this Eternal Library
as well as sealed magic.
In other words, all of your friends will
fall before my demon lord power!
Everyone...
Akio!
Are you okay, Akio!?
Ow...
Akio?
Yeah, I put all I had into defense.
I'm completely spent now.
What type of weird magic are you using
that makes you smaller
when you use it too much?
My defensive powers get worse,
but I can then focus on attacking,
which makes me stronger.
That was close.
Wow, if we take a direct hit
from that, we'll be in real trouble.
It's gotten stronger than before.
It won't stop flying.
Players would get really frustrated if this were a game.
Anyway, we need to take him down a peg.
Can I have you carry me over there?
Sounds good.
I've been wanting to show off a bit.
Reconnecting to Invidia Archive.
Solvo Arm:
Bladed Wings of Light, Claíomh Solais!
You won't be able to catch the
Light Goddess, Lugh, like that.
I think I'll be going now.
Okay, have a good trip.
Reconnecting to Invidia Archive!
Levi-san!
Ninja Art: Body Replacement!
Secret Technique: Crescent Moon Strike!
Did we get it!?
Not yet!
Execute joint magic.
Okay.
Got it!
Reconnecting to Superbia Archive.
Reconnecting to Gula Archive.
Reconnecting to Acedia Archive.
I'll start things off!
Chrono Calculation!
I'm going to borrow your magic, Selina.
Okay, Onee-chan.
Numbering Seal!
Demon Destroyer Advent!
Take this!
Senpai!
Boss!
Luxuria Archive. Acquiring Thema: Sileo.
You'll regret that your impure existence
ever crossed us at Grimoire Security!
White Universe!
Yes!
We did it!
Good work, Mira-san.
Yes.
I hope Arata-san and the others are okay.
What will you do now,
alchemists of the Trinity Seven?
We use the same magic.
I don't mind if you're the
only one to escape from here.
I couldn't do that...
Yes, Lilith.
You run.
Arata!
Run, Lilith!
I can't run away and leave you behind!
In that case, I'll end both of you.
Get away, Lilith!
No, I won't!
Just get away from me!
Huh? I've been in this situation before...
I sense both Lilith-sensei's
and my husband's magic from her,
so I was sure that she was your child...
But she's a grimoire, isn't she?
Sensed both my and Lilith's magic...
If we weren't in this situation,
I would have spent more time enjoying this.
Give me your power, Lilim!
Please use me, Papa-sama!
What are you...
Take it all, Meteo Dragonar!
Lilith, I'm going to borrow your magic.
R-Right.
Connecting to Luxuria Archive.
Execute Abies!
My Archive and Thema!?
Wh-What!?
Where are we?
We're inside me.
Papa-sama connected to me,
so I was able to invite you in.
Lilith's and my magic is inside Lilim.
So I figured I could
connect to it like a Thema.
Y-Yeah, but that doesn't mean it was a good idea to execute someone else's Archive and Thema.
What would have happened if I'd messed up?
Hmm, best case scenario: your magic
would have run completely wild.
And worst case scenario: you'd have been completely destroyed, Arata-san!
Seriously!?
I'm glad I succeeded!
Well, I imagine you were able to connect
because Lilim was born from
your own magic, Master.
Because you ate Arata-san's
magic, right, Lilim-san?
Yes, I'm Papa-sama's daughter.
Okay, it's a father's job to show
off to his daughter, isn't it?
Are you sure, Master?
Huh?
If you use your magic that's within Lilim,
then that magic will be removed from her.
And if that happens, Lilim will...
Yes, I'll lose my consciousness
and return to being a tool that cannot speak.
But if I'm able to help
Papa-sama and the others,
I...
Please...
don't forget about me.
Don't smile like that.
How was it being a human
and spending time with everyone?
It was very fun.
Mama-sama was soft.
The lollipop was good.
The bath felt nice.
Everyone was so nice to me.
I'm just a grimoire, and
everyone treated me so well...
That's why I...
Then...
What do you want to do, Lilim?
I love you, Lilim.
I love you too, Lilim. I love you so much.
Yes...
I love Papa-sama, Mama-sama,
and everyone else, too!
I don't want to disappear!
In that case...
Let's try our best together, Lilim.
But...
To walk the path of magic means
diverging from common sense.
We're mages, and you're a grimoire.
Add me, a demon lord candidate,
we can do any crazy thing we want!
Hey, most of this stuff just works itself out.
We're the ones saying it,
so it must be true.
Papa-sama.
Please use my magic.
Got it.
Let's do this, Lilith, Lilim.
Right.
Right!
Leave controlling your power to me, Master.
I'll protect your body, Arata-san.
All right...
Let's go, everyone!
Right!
What's up with that arm!?
Arata...
Arata-san, that magic just now...
It wasn't a demon lord's power.
Onii-san, is that...
Yeah, I feel like I can
do anything right now!
Lilith.
Reconnecting to Luxuria Archive.
Execute Thema.
Impossible!
That's...
One of the ultimate magics...
The paladin form.
Arata is connected to the power of Hohenheim,
the author of the Hermes Apocrypha
and the progenitor of alchemy.
You were born from alchemy,
and thus can be defeated by alchemy.
You think a stop-gap magic like that
can defeat the new demon lord!?
Take it all, Meteo Dragonar!
Realize: Buster Mode!
Disintegrate into light! Meteo Buster!
That kid... He finally used
paladin abilities such as ours.
To think he used the paladin powers
sealed away in the Eternal Library,
retrieved from Lilith-chan's Hermes Apocrypha...
What amazing talent.
I guess that's what it means to be a
demon lord that rules everything.
Yep.
My demon lord candidate and the
Trinity Seven just keep on growing.
Exactly how much
has he accounted for in his research?
Looks like we beat him.
I agree.
Oh, are you alright, Hijiri?
Yes, Arata-san.
The strong magic that enveloped this place has disappeared.
I see.
Onii-san!
Husband.
You two doing okay, Yui, Arin?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You're amazing, husband.
What's going on, Nii-chan?
That's a pretty gallant outfit you've got on.
Luxuria magic...
It doesn't seem to be an impure power.
By the way, I've been here for a while now.
So have I.
I think I worked a bit too hard.
Yep, you really did your best out there.
All right!
All that's left is taking out that white sun, right?
An impure power is growing stronger.
He's still alive.
He's taking in the breakdown phenomenon.
Not yet...
I will swallow all...
Take in all...
and become the true demon lord...
You look like you're in pain,
White Demon Lord.
You were born just to become the demon lord,
but then you were defeated,
and now you're forced to stay alive,
even in that condition.
It must be painful.
Papa-sama...
Arata...
Lilith, Lilim, everyone.
I want to put him out of his misery as fast as possible.
Will you help me?
It goes without saying that we'd
help you do whatever you want.
All right, everyone!
Throw everything you've got at him!
Right!
Here I go!
Meteo Symphony!
Technique: Mistilteinn!
White Universe!
Demon Destroyer Advent!
Secret Technique: Avidya Slash!
Lance of Piercing Light, Brionac!
Chrono Calculation!
Black Azazel!
Disintegrate into light!
Meteo Buster!
I am... to be destroyed?
But I was born to become the demon lord...
Leave being a demon lord to me,
and you may rest in peace.
The Luxuria breakdown
phenomenon has vanished.
Arata-san and the Trinity Seven have won.
We did it!
It's all over...
Papa-sama!
Ow...
Are you okay, Lilim?
Papa-sama.
Yeah?
It's about time.
Lilim, you...
Lilim...
Papa-sama, Mama-sama.
I will always be with you!
Yes.
I'll make sure we see each other again!
So until then...
Wait for us, Lilim!
Okay!
Well, then...
I can release this paladin form now, right?
Yeah, why not?
Okay, in that case...
Paladin form, release!
H-Huh?
A-Arata!
kagami ni touta "ano taiyou wa dare no mono dai?"
I asked the mirror, "Whom does that Sun belong to?"
kussetsu shita hikari boku wo yubisasu
The refracted light points at me
tada waratteiru dake no orokamono ni wa yuzuranai
I won't hand it over to a fool who can do nothing but laugh
nisemono no sora ni saigo no kane wo narashite iku
The last bell rings to a false sky
nanatsu no tori ga naite boku wo habamu
The singing of seven birds stop me from advancing
Don't give up & stay on your way
boku ga dekiru shoumei
I'll prove that I've got what it takes
tatoe koe ga karete mo utai tsuzuketa
I kept singing even as my voice grew hoarse
Enter a new era & I will end it
hajiru wake ga nai darou
There's no reason to feel ashamed
boku wa omae? omae wa boku?
I am you? You are me?
ikinokotte kotae wo akase
Survive and reveal the answer
eiyuu ga ita jibun no michi dake wo aruite ita
I kept walking my own path which a hero had passed
(This one's for the last fight)
sou jikojitsugen suru imi wo sagashite
Yes, searching for the reason for my self-actualization
(This one's for the black lust)
What am I gonna do?
I can't believe anyone anymore!
Keep moving, keep moving!
All there is to it
(This one's for the freedom)
Let's go to heaven, come on "Trinity Seven"
We got to fight to the powers that be
The end is near, I prove it to you
(This one's for the last fight)
tatakau shika nakattanda
There was no choice but to fight
Don't let me down & I need you right now
agaki moeru tamashii
My soul burns fiercely in an effort to fight back
boku ga tsumi to iu nara kowashite miro
If you say I'm at fault, then try and break me
Long for your arrival & Good bye boy
naze michi wo tagaeta ka
Why did I differ from the path?
sukuu ka sukuwareru ka wa taiyou ga erabu no darou
Can I save or be saved is for the Sun to decide
ai mo kizuna mo kireina tori mo inai
In a place where there is no love, bonds or beautiful birds
boku wa tada sakenda
I just kept shouting
fukiareru kaze ni naru
I'll become a violent wind
(fukiareru kaze ni naru)
(I'll become a violent wind)
tobikau yume ni madou
Confused by the jumbled dream
(tobikau yume ni madou)
(Confused by the jumbled dream)
aratana ashita ga hajimarou to shiteru
A new tomorrow is about to begin
saigo no honoo wo saigo ni hikari wo
Extinguishing the last flame and lastly bringing light
Don't give up & stay on your way
boku ga dekiru shoumei
I'll prove that I've got what it takes
tatoe koe ga karete mo utai tsuzuketa
I kept singing even as my voice grew hoarse
Enter a new era & I will end it
hajiru wake ga nai darou
There's no reason to feel ashamed
boku wa omae? omae wa boku?
I am you? You are me?
ikinokotte kotae wo akase
Survive and reveal the answer
Last Proof
So he was able to rule even
Luxuria's paladin power...
Jeez...
This demon lord candidate is insane.
Yeah.
I'm even more interested now.
What's with you? You look really happy.
That's because I've always
loved the demon lord candidate.
So we should go see him next, Arsha.
Oh, all right. I guess I'll have to
stick with you until the end, Ana.
Hey, stop.
Oh, come on.
Jeez...