Stamp or sign, please!
What did we get?
Remittance from Valhalla.
Wow! It's full of gadget materials!
Oh, we got some mead!
I just don't understand what you find
delicious about mead.
You'll get it when you're an adult.
Can you please stop treating me like a child?
Sorry!
Oracle
From Your Dad
Is this...?!
Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Sagashita amai negai, kyou mo
Kizuite to, watashi no naka kara
Dare ka ga kimi e to sakebu yo
Mitsumeau, modokashii kyori ni
Abaredashita samishisa
Kamishimeru hitori
Suki toiu omoi o
Iitai demo ienai
Itsumo soba ni kimi ga iru no ni
Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Tomoshita tsuyoi omoi
Mayowanai mayoitaku wa nai kara
Shinjite ima, ippo fumidasou
For the sake of myself
Father's oracle is here!
There's an akuma attack tomorrow.
Therefore, after this we will hold a strategy meeting.
So they haven't given up yet.
I'm sleepy.
Originally, I wanted to have
Natsuki-chan fight like always,
but Natsuki-chan, can you please transform for us?
Huh? O-okay!
We haven't kissed since the campus festival, huh?
H-here goes!
R-right.
What? I can't transform!
Why not?
L-let's try again!
O-okay!
Damn it, why's this happening?
Maybe it's like that time...
N..Natsuki-san?
You can stop kissing him now.
Why is it always Natsuki-chan! No fair!
Natsuki! I cannot believe you!
No, this was just...
I thought so.
Kururi-chan, is the thing I asked you for ready?
'Course it is!
Valkyrie 9 Sisters
Break Down Manual!
Okay, everyone, get a load of this!
Brunhilde
Spear
Points until next level
Attack:
Special:
Defense:
Range:  Short
Gerhilde
Castle
Points until next level
Attack:
Special:
Defense:
Range:  Long
Ortlinde
String
Points until next level
Attack:
Special:
Defense:
Range:  Mid
Waultraute
Armor
Points until next level
Attack:
Special:
Defense:
Range:  Short
Shwertleite
Chain
Points until next level
Attack:
Special:
Defense:
Range:  Mid
Helmwige
Wing
Points until next level
Attack:
Special:
Defense:
Range:  Short
Siegrune
Blade
Points until next level
Attack:
Special:
Defense:
Range:  Mid
Grimgerde
Sound
Points until next level
Attack:
Special:
Defense:
Range:  Short
Rossweisse
Cannon
Points until next level
Attack:
Special:
Defense:
Range:  Long
And Sue-chan's
here too!
It's a chart of everyone's parameters, huh?
I'm sleepy.
This tablet is a present for you!
Th-thanks.
N-Natsuki is a given, but I'm at
an even lower level than you, Mutsumi?
Attack:
What does the 'AP' here mean?
Siegrune
Blade
Points until next level
Attack:
Defense:
It's the energy that we, the gods, need in order to act.
Our AP is used up the entire time we're in action.
When we attack or receive damage
and exhaust our AP,
our transformation is broken and it vanishes.
The reason why Natuki-chan's AP is zero may be
because the campus festival date was so intense.
Intense? N..Natsuki-chan, explain!
N-N-N-Natsuki, I cannot believe you!
Th-that was beyond my control!
Natsuki!
Natsuki-chan!
It was beyond my control!
Well? Who's going to end up fighting the akuma?
We don't have a decent attacker.
You're right.
Big Sister Ichika is still level one...
and Shino-chan is in no shape to fight.
And Kururi-chan... has her own issues.
Sorry!
Kururi-san... has her own issues?!
Takuma-chan can currently
make up to two people transform.
So that means...
Mutsumi-chan, Yakumo-chan.
Please look at the camera.
O-okay.
Mutsumi-chan! Nice! You look great!
Th-thank you so much.
Val Love, "Hold Hands with Lover for One Hour."
We're leaving it to Mutsumi-chan and
Yakumo-chan this time around.
R-right!
Ugh...
Takuma-chan, please raise their levels
before the battle begins.
G-got it.
But that being said...
I-I can't do this, I'm suffocating!
Er, I would really appreciate it
if I could have a sip of tea...
What?
Why do I have to give you some of my tea?
You know I don't want to do that, right?
Is that how much you want to
give me an indirect kiss?
That's dumb.
What a pervert.
I hope you die.
Stab!
Are those two okay?
You shouldn't keep looking over at them.
They'll find out who you are even with a disguise on.
This parfait is yummy!
Want mine too?
I'm worried.
You want me to tell you about Yakumo?
Um... I always feel an extraordinarily
intimidating air from her,
so I want to start mentally preparing myself
for tomorrow right now.
Rumble
Ba-dump
Oh.
He comes to speak to me
more often than he used to...
I suspect that Yakumo may be bothered by
the sound of your heart beating.
Huh?
Yakumo has had very sensitive hearing
since she was born.
Seidr. It's an idiosyncrasy
that a demigod is rarely born with.
In Yakumo's case, that means she catches
everything, no matter how small the sound.
It's at the level where if she doesn't wear her
headphones to block out the sounds around her,
it would interfere with her daily life.
Give them back...
Now that you mention it, she really hated it
when I got her headphones during Tag.
I-is the sound of my heart that noisy to her?
Well, even with my ears I can hear it faintly.
Anyways, don't get too frightened
if you want to avoid upsetting Yakumo.
Though, he is mustering up the courage to go for
that date, and that's a good mindset to have!
You can do this, Takuma!
At any rate, I have to make sure
my heart doesn't beat too hard!
Alright, I think it's beating just fine right now.
Upset
It's hammering away!
I have to suppress this hammering more!
Stop it! Stop hammering in my chest!
Hammer... when was that made again?
The Jomon Era? The Yayoi Era?
Mutsumi-chan's such a cutie!
Totally worth it to skip club and come see her today.
Yamada-san?! Wh-wh-why is he here?!
Val Love: "Hold Hands with Lover for One Hour " Failed.
Val Love
Hold Hands with Lover for One Hour
Failed
I-I-I'm sorry!
First of all, Big Brother...
Stop your heart. It's loud.
Death!
I-I'll try.
I can't comprehend just why Dad chose you for this.
You're a wussy loser
who's always making gross noises.
There's a limit to how pathetic one can be.
I'b shorry.
Honestly, shouldn't you do something
about Natsuki's AP?
I heard that you can use a recovery ability now.
Uh, well... I did my best to somehow produce a book,
but ever since the campus festival,
I haven't been able to do it again.
Lame.
Stab!
Mutsumi-san, it's break time.
We'll resume in 30 minutes.
Okay, next time you'll prove it to me, then.
Prove to me that even you can do this.
I'm still don't like being in front of others...
But, since Natsuki-chan can't fight right now,
we have to do our best!
Our last date got weird, though...
but on this next one, I'll make sure of it!
Takuma-kun and I... will have a proper k-k-k-kiss!
Mutsumi, we're coming in.
P-pardon the intrusion.
Wh-wh-what's going on, you two?!
We're here because Big Brother screwed up our date.
C'mon, hurry up and get ready. You gotta start.
Val Love, "Private 30 Minute Photo Shoot
with an Idol," commence.
Val Love
Private 30 Minute Photo Shoot with an Idol
Commence
This swimsuit is tiny!
You ready too, Big Brother?
I wonder if it's okay to use this...
I get to see it, right?
Show me what makes you our lover.
Um... Can I wear something other than a swimsuit?
I understand.
I'll take nothing but exquisite pictures of you
in our private photo shoot!
Takuma-kun's face is so full determination!
I have to show him that same determination!
I'm Takuma-kun's g-girlfriend, after all!
There are staff members right outside of here...
Y..Yakumo-chan?! What're you doing?
I thought we could spice things up a bit more.
Mutsumi, your boobs are really huge.
You should flaunt them.
Huh?
Big Brother, are you getting these shots?
Uh, yeah!
Wow, Mutsumi, you're letting Big Brother
take your picture in that outfit.
You. Are. So. Bold.
D-don't say that.
Okay, here, hold this.
Huh?
It's an ice cream treat for you. Take it.
C'mon, you too, Mutsumi.
O-okay.
How did this happen?!
But I have to keep going!
MOLE
Fine Confections
Sweet Buns
This is a gift for Mutsumi-chan.
I hope she likes it!
Huh?
What is that?
Another akuma?!
Let's go! Get out of here!
Get away from here now!
O-okay!
Seems the interference with the Oracle
is still happening.
I would like to survive until
the other three get here, though.
Big Sister Ichika, do you think we can defeat it?
Quit babbling, Futaba.
Don't lower your guard.
It won't even take me 100 seconds
to chop you into pieces!
No way, we're still in the middle of our date!
Mutsumi, let's hurry and transform.
O-okay.
What? She chose his lips?!
Er, then where will I...
Big Brother, next time for sure...
I want you to show me what makes you our lover.
I won't let you down!
Hey, you two.
Leave the rest to us!
Akuma Exhaustion Tag Strategy...
Commence!
Here we go, you two!
'Kay.
O-okay!
"Akuma Exhaustion Tag Strategy..." what's that?
Just like we said earlier,
the gods need AP in order to act.
But it's the same thing for the akuma.
They get summoned,
and their AP decreases just by being here.
And when the AP reaches zero, the akuma vanishes.
"Damage Taken... 1 AP Consumed"
So Mutsumi's "Evade the akuma on wings
and make it consume it's AP" is named...
"Summoned... 10 AP Consumed"
"Attack... 10 AP Consumed"
the "Akuma Exhaustion Tag Strategy"!
Did the akuma disappear?
Darn...
A song?
Speed reduction!
Thanks, Yakumo-chan!
We should get out of here while we still can.
Right!
What was that?
That was scary!
We've gotta call the cops.
I told you there was nothing to worry about.
Eikthyrnir is a normal attack type akuma,
focused on slash attacks.
Helmwige's wings and
Grimgerde sound will defeat that.
Yeah.
You can do it, Mutsumi, Yakumo... Takuma!
Yakumo-chan, do you have any energy left?
I'll be okay for now, but a long battle
may be cutting it close.
Takuma-kun, do you have the tablet
you got from Kururi-chan?
We can measure the akuma's parameters with it.
Right. Let me see...
It hasn't gotten much weaker at all.
Eikthyrnir
Helmwige
Grimgerde
Can't do anything about that.
Th-the fight has just started!
We're getting serious now!
Those two are extremely worn out...
Are their levels still too low after all?
It has to be because I've failed so many dates!
It just has to!
So noisy.
I can hear the sound directly
since I don't have my headphones.
Shut up.
I seriously want to threaten him as soon as...
Watch out! It's below us!
Attack weakened. Defense strengthened.
Alright. This'll be okay.
As long as we keep evading it,
and as long the akuma keeps attacking,
our victory draws closer!
I will protect those two!
Huh?
An arrow?
I can't believe that akuma self-destructed!
Mutsumi-san, Yakumo-san!
Takuma-kun! Get out of here!
A few days earlier
Takuma-chan, do you know what this is?
It's a sprig of mistletoe... Misteltein, was it?
Yes.
The tears of the tree of life, divided into three...
Of the branches of Yggdrasil Ea, it controls progress
and is the most valuable asset of Asgard.
Right now, it's power is completely exhausted
and it's lying dormant.
Do you remember, Takuma-chan?
Do you remember when you almost died
at the campus festival?
Yeah.
It was your ability as Einheijer
that revived you at that time.
However, you're like a bud
that has still only just blossomed.
Without the help of Miteltein, we don't know when
your restorative ability will be invoked.
It's true that I haven't been able to
call forth that book at all since then...
You may not be able to handle everything
next time, Takuma-chan.
So don't force yourself, alright?
Okay.
Moreover, I'm extremely sorry about this, but...
Huh?
...please take good care of my younger sisters.
The only one who can heal the maidens is Einheijer;
and that's you as their lover, Takuma-chan.
No!
Get away!
Takuma-kun!
Compared to people...
akuma are a joke!
Einheijer...
Invoke... the book!
Holy Sword, Maximum Strength!
This is quite the mess.
I prefer not to use any more war assets in Midgard,
where there are restrictions to demon summoning.
That being said, even if I attack,
I'll just be killed by the first or second one
at level one while seeking my revenge.
Besides, Einheijer is in the process
of awakening his abilities.
Though I'm loathe to admit it, I suppose I have
no choice but to summon her after all.
I'll call the demigoddess, 'Our Lady.'
Tea
Goodness, swinging at that akuma
was way too reckless of you.
Here's some tea.
Th-thank you.
We got a report from around this area...
You're clearly imagining things!
We're just taking Sue-chan for a walk!
M-Mutsumi-chan! I-if you don't mind,
please accept this gift!
Wow, thanks! Um...
I-I'm Yamada! I'm in the class next door!
But, well... um, I suppose...
That was kind of cool, I guess.
I said "kind of" cool! Only kind of!
O-okay.
What's wrong, Yakumo?
Nothing.
Er, u-um, Yakumo-sa...
I hope you die.
Stab!
I-I'm sorry.
I hope you die.
Stab! STAB!
Y-Yakumo! Th-that's enough! Stop it! Stop it!
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Koi o shiranakucha you and I, hajimaranai no yo?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
We wanna share your heart!
(How do you tell me?)
Amai kotoba o input
Shippai - Cancel - Zenzen hibikanai wa ne
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch shite todokete yo
Seikou - Complete - Saisentan ga ii yo ne?
(Hold me tight)
Naze koi to itte kurenai no?
Ai ni yukou!
Motto keiken shite level up otome gokoro
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Oshiete ageru wa, koi wa otome no power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Jucchuuhakku kitto mou lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Tokimeku mune dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Akuma de shy na mind, kiss for you!
Kaete shimau yo na, kiss for me!
Koi o hajimemasho!
It was a task to deceive that officer
that came here due to the report.
Sorry, Itsuyo-chan. But you know,
I'm glad we defeated that akuma.
Even though I'm not suited to battle,
if I have the help of Yakumo-chan and Takuma-kun,
it seems like things will work out.
Big Sister Misa's strategy was also quite good.
Since Natsuki has the highest level of all of us
and she can't fight, we did what we could.
Next time, "The Touching Maiden
and the Touched Maiden."
Next time: The Touching Maiden and the Touched Maiden
I'll use this opportunity to do
all the Val Love that I can with Takuma-san!
No fair, Itsuyo-chan!