Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
The sweet desire I found is here today as well
From inside of me
Someone screams at you to notice
We stare at one another, at an irritating distance
Alone, I endure
The onslaught of sadness
Though I want to tell you this feeling of love
I can't say a word
Though you're always at my side
Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
A strong emotion set aflame
I won't hesitate, I don't want to hesitate
I'll believe in now, and take a step forward
For the sake of myself
What is it you wanted to tell me, Father?
Listen closely, Gelhilde.
What I am about to say,
you must always bear in mind.
You are weak.
Summon the castle wall.
Alright. We're going to
sneak around the back, Lover.
R-right!
To get straight to the point,
we cannot beat the Norn.
As we are, we don't stand a chance against
those akuma and their method of annihilation.
If there were only one or two of them
it'd be no problem, though.
Then that means...
Yes.
We will kill her lover Snorri,
and leave the Norn powerless.
When the Norn attacks, we'll launch a surprise attack
from the back and bring her down.
Since Natsuki can't fight, I'll do it.
At that time, Futaba, distract all of the akuma
so they won't catch wind of my movements.
Leave it to me!
Huh? Are you sure, Futaba?
Come on, who do you think I am?
But doing all that at your level, Futaba...
You worry too much, Misa-chan.
That weakling is the problem here.
I can transform for about a second.
In that case, it's essential that you
go together with Takuma-chan, right?
I'm actually unsure as to whether that weakling
is prepared to take a step towards death or not.
Huh?
E-excuse me!
Perfect timing.
We need to ask you a favor concerning the Norn.
About that...
I think I have no choice but to attack them.
Huh?
That Norn seems very strong, but, uh... well...
if we can disable her lover,
I think it might work out somehow...and...
So, uh...
What?!
I guess I wouldn't be able to...
What's with this sudden change?
So you're ready to to save the world
in your own spineless way now?
Uh...
Well...
Well, it's fine.
In that case, go get ready for this immediately.
Before I stab your ass to death.
Calm down, Big Sis Ichika.
Get ready?
Well then, shall we get started, Takuma-chan?
Val Love, "Embrace Without a Stitch of Clothing On
and Kiss Passionately for 5 Minutes"!
There you go.
This time, if we aren't in EX mode from the start,
this will be hard to accomplish.
I-I see!
Do you hate older women?
N-no! I just thought you were
strong enough to not need to do this.
You are Her Majesty, after all.
That isn't true at all.
Because I'm weak.
Shall we get started now?
Val Love, commence.
Takuma-chan, relax.
I have to do my best!
Takuma-chan, you may be a little too ravenous!
I-I-I'm sorry! I just...
But you know, I like people that will do this
to try to become stronger.
Please, don't ever lose that desire.
Summon double castle wall!
She's been engaging in only
hand to hand combat this whole time!
What happened to that castle she's so proud of?!
I wondered what type of person you were,
since you're exalted as a main god or "Her Majesty."
Is Einheijer incompetent?
Or have you always been this weak?
Or perhaps both?
Well, at any rate, We are simply
too strong for you, aren't We!
Of course, Our Lady.
Yes, that's right!
You've been chattering on for quite some time now.
Hurry up and come at me, you little brat.
Such impolite language...
Massacre them!
Stop, Lover.
A surveillance akuma.
I thought they'd set one up.
This way.
Uh, okay.
If we don't hurry, Futaba's castle will fall.
Why doesn't Futaba-san attack with her castle?
It isn't that she won't use it, but she can't.
Huh?
Have you heard about the aether?
U-uh, yeah.
The aether is like their souls,
and the more aether they have,
the stronger the ability they can use, right?
In simple terms, that's correct.
The amount of aether Futaba has
is considerably small.
She is easily the weakest of the sisters.
Huh?
The castle is the ability to summon Valhalla,
the fortress of the aether.
With the perfect amount of aether, she can call forth
all sorts of aether weapons including a war cry,
but Futaba can't do that
with the amount of aether she has.
A higher level would be better, but at her current level
the most she can do is summon the outer walls.
Therefore, Futaba has no choice
but to fight barehanded.
I-I don't believe it.
That's precisely why Futaba got stronger.
In order for her to hold her own
even with her weak abilities in a fight with enemies,
she became a disciple of Thor and trained hard.
Since her vision is blocked,
she also honed her senses.
Futaba is not worthy of being called "Her Majesty"
due to her physical strength.
It's due to the strength of her heart that will
never allow anyone to set foot inside our castle!
Big Sister Futaba!
I am...
weak.
The aggression of the spear and the blade;
the specialty of the chain and the wing;
the versatility of the thread and of sound...
I have none of that.
Even so, I swear I will protect my family!
Mere drivel.
Just die and let me through!
I'm going to take a look.
Do not fail, Lover!
Got it!
Okay, off to round two!
Yamada-san, you're drinking too much!
Ugh, you sound like my dumbass son!
The streets have been dangerous lately,
so let's head home now.
Oh? What was it again?
It was something about akuma or...
Are you alright, Big Sister Shino?
Our father once prophesized:
Those who lie idle
tend to be unable to claim victory.
A barrier has been granted, born from my body.
The Helmet That Transcends Time
(Bergelmir)
If I cannot fight...
If this is how it must be... then I will withstand it.
Until my body gives out... and only then.
There are four eggs left.
Including the akuma at our feet,
taking them all on would be a challenge.
We'll wait until the Norn has
more of her attention on Futaba.
G-got it.
I guess this much fortification around us
is challenging for Ichika since her transformation
is effective for one second.
There are four eggs left?
Um, are there really only four left?
What?
I can't sense anything!
Don't spout useless things at me, you weakling!
I-I'm sorry!
What could this be? Something doesn't feel right.
Futaba-san!
This is my fault.
A higher level would be better,
but at her current level...
If I had been more thorough,
I'm sure I would have been able to
raise Futaba's abilities!
If I were more reliable,
then both Futaba-san and Ichika-san
would be at a high enough level from the start!
I'd also be able to restore Natsuki-san's AP.
More than two of them would be able
to transform right now!
This is all because of me!
Is it time yet?
At this rate, Futaba-san will...
Not yet.
But-
Not yet!
If there's no smashing through the castle
or breaching the barrier, what do we do?
Dumplings are so tasty.
Despite what you say, it's only a matter of time
before the Valkyrie of the castle collapses.
At this rate, I think it is a good idea
to take our time attacking her.
I know that!
Though you're at such a high level,
you can't take me down on your own.
She must be a failure after all...
Aren't you, lover?
Our Lady?
Take a note, Roskva.
A noble will not give in to cheap provocation.
However...
ridiculing Roskva will not be tolerated!
The gods dread that spear.
While it is the counterpart of her body,
and while it's power is a mere flicker.
All of creation is in that one spear.
That body will undoubtedly become bright red!
She really is a strong Norn.
However...
now I have Snorri to myself!
I knew something was off!
This uneasiness that I've been feeling...
when we first encountered the Norn,
there were twenty-one eggs in all.
But now, after her summons,
there are only twenty!
There's one egg missing!
I have confidence in my memory.
I'm positive I have the number of eggs right!
Then that means...
The last egg is...
What are y-
That wasn't very wise, Valkyrie.
It was clear that you, Valkyrie of inferior strength,
would aim for me.
Therefore, I let it hatch inside of me.
It seems you've been able to avoid the akuma,
but unfortunately for you...
I am also an akuma.
Roskva.
Yes, ma'am.
There are two aether responses to the northwest.
So they've managed to escape, huh?
But Einheijer's abilities are yet to be awakened.
It should still take some time
for the misteltein to sprout,
so these idiotic beasts are inferior to even ants.
Now then, time to hunt Einheijer!
I can't believe she's trying to unite with an akuma...
What a mistake I've made.
And what's more...
I'm being carried on this weakling's back!
Kitadai Park
L-let's hide here for now.
Ichika-san can't move.
Now that it's come to this, I have to...
invoke my abilities!
Dammit!
Why can't I even do it at a time like this?!
How long will I stay like this?!
Lover...
Leave me behind.
Huh?
Go back to the house and regroup.
Einheijer is the heart of the Valkyrie.
We can't lose you here.
Misa is in command.
Do as I say.
B-but...
Don't get arrogant, Lover.
This does not mean that I have
accepted you in the slightest.
It is all for the sake of my dear sisters
that you have survived so long here.
If you understand, then go.
I leave my sisters to you.
No... I won't!
No...
I won't!
What the hell are you doing?!
I am extremely sorry to say this,
but to be honest,
I don't like you, Ichika-san.
I shake under the ferocity of your formidable nature,
and your eyes are somehow scary.
You're one to talk!
But... without you, I'm sure everyone
would be heartbroken.
So I absolutely will not leave you behind!
You mean you're trying to make it so I can fight?
You're telling me to level up as quickly as possible?
What a coincidence. I really hate you too,
but I don't want to see my sisters grieving.
Alright, then!
Come and seduce me right now, Lover!
Val Love, commence!
Val Love
H-how is it? I mean, does it feel good?
I'm not so easy of a woman
to be seduced to this degree of-
This is so shameful!
Can I really get stronger from this?
I've never undertaken any love training,
so I have no idea!
Run, Lover!
They have evaded all of the bullets.
Keep firing!
On the right!
Okay!
My ideal man, Father?
Yes. Brunhilde, what type of man do you prefer?
As a Valkyrie, you've dreamt of
your future mate, haven't you?
Einheijer...
By the way, I personally like long,
dark hair like your mother's!
She's the perfect example of the
"ideal woman of virtue" I've heard about!
Let me see... At the very least...
weak, rude, and shallow guys
are the ones I definitely can't stand!
Just thinking about 'em makes me wanna puke!
Please don't break the game pieces.
I don't need a lover.
I'm beyond competent in fighting
with this one spear.
You know for sure how strong I am, right, Father?
But I want my sisters to meet a good man.
He doesn't need to be strong,
but if he disregards himself in favor of my sisters,
and never backs down from a steadfast spear,
then he's surely good enough for my sisters.
So even you have one!
You do have a preferred type of man!
Val Love...
Val Love
"Accept the Lover," successful.
Accept the Lover
Successful
Impact confirmed.
That was a lot of trouble.
There's no way they're still alive,
but what do you think, Roskva?
Yes ma'am.
Our Lady!
What... The Valkyrie of the spear?!
She should be completely powerless!
I am not prepared for something like
saving the world.
But...
Even so...
I swear I will guard all of your lives!
Because I...
I love you all.
Someone once said:
Someone once said
"Love is the source of a maiden's power.
Love is the source of a maiden's power.
However, it is impossible for a maiden
to sustain that love alone!"
to sustain that love alone
Einheijer
Book Lv. 10
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
If we don't understand love,
you & I won't get anywhere, you know?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
We wanna share your heart!
(How do you tell me?)
Input sweet nothings
Failed - Cancelled - They don't resonate at all
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch me and bring me one
Successful - Complete - Isn't cutting-edge tech great?
(Hold me tight)
Why won't you say romance?
Let's bring it to love!
Get more experience and level up my maiden heart
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
I'll teach you that love is a maiden's power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Nine times out of ten, they're surely already lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Fluttering in my chest, dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Your shy akuma mind, kiss for you!
Will completely change, kiss for me!
Let's begin our romance!
Takuma, the clothes you're wearing...
is that the power of Einheijer's book?
I don't know.
I was thinking about all of you, and then...
Stay on guard, Lover!
The enemy is that Norn and Snorri,
who's become an akuma!
Please, Takuma-chan.
The Lover is the only one who can heal the maidens.
You can do it, Takuma-kun!
Takuma-san, you were the one chosen by our father.
We're counting on you, Takuma!
Big Brother Takuma!
Big Brother.
Master.
Takuma?
I-I'll do my best!
Next time: "The Loving Maiden!"
Next time: The Loving Maiden