Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Sagashita amai negai, kyou mo
Kizuite to, watashi no naka kara
Dare ka ga kimi e to sakebu yo
Mitsumeau, modokashii kyori ni
Abaredashita samishisa
Kamishimeru hitori
Suki toiu omoi o
Iitai demo ienai
Itsumo soba ni kimi ga iru no ni
Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Tomoshita tsuyoi omoi
Mayowanai mayoitaku wa nai kara
Shinjite ima, ippo fumidasou
For the sake of myself
Huh? Where's Takuma?
Takuma is off taking the national mock exam.
That thing he was up til late
last night studying for, right?
Oh, then we should have sukiyaki
in celebration of today.
Big Sister Misa, you just want to
eat sukiyaki, don't you?
I'm home.
Welcome back, Big Brother Takuma!
Takuma?!
Oh my, what's wrong?
The testing site was more crowded than I anticipated...
I was so terrified by the situation
the entire test was a complete disaster.
You were so terrified you shrunk?!
Okay, let's play a game of Tag!
Huh? You want to play Tag?
Sounds like fun!
Let's play, Big Brother Takuma!
I can't, I have to study...
Big Brother Takuma, you pervert!
What?!
All you do is study and you never play with me!
I-I'm sorry!
I've just been so out of shape lately, it's ridiculous.
Please, just this once.
If I tell them no right now,
they'd probably disrupt my studies...
Okay, just once.
Okay then, let's all draw and
whoever gets the red one is It.
Guess I'm It!
Futaba is It...
I'm awake now.
You're joking.
Then the competition has to be...
You lose when your panties are stolen, okay?
You lose if you get your panties stolen?!
Alright then, ready...
Start!
I'm going to give chase after 3 minutes!
I don't have the time to do things like this...
Maybe I can hide somewhere and study...
I-I-I-I-I'm sorry!
Takuma-san...
I can't stop staring!
We sisters are indeed freeloaders.
However, we should at least receive
the bare minimum of manners.
I would appreciate it if you would knock next time.
O-okay.
Sorry about that, Takumacchi.
That was a strange thing to see.
I just wanted some of this thread...
Thread?
I was going to use my sacred sword
to sense Futaba's movement.
I was unraveling a string from this shirt
and stretching it all through the house.
Wh-why are you doing all of that?
Because she's reached full proficiency
in the Gourai Isshin-style
as the top disciple of Thor, the god of thunder.
Even at level 1, Futaba is strong enough
to snatch a pair of panties in an instant!
Again with the panties?!
Also, the nickname she got from that strength is...
"Her Majesty the Queen!"
A panty-snatching queen?!
Well, I'm going to focus on the string,
so you two get prepared to attack.
What is this air of intimidation?
I guess choosing to pat her on the head
in the gym storage room
was the wrong thing to do after all...
I-I'm sorr-
I've been doing my best recently!
What?
Not only have I been doing
various student council duties,
but I'm also checking over the events for
campus festival attendees and everything...
I've done my very best, lately!
So... um...
It's alright to pat me as a reward.
Is it okay to pat you on the head?
If that's what you want to do,
Takuma-san, then by all means!
It seems like she'll be mad if I don't.
Itsuyo-san?!
D-don't worry...about it.
Please continue... to do that pat-pat.
"Do that pat-pat?"
N-no, I mean...
Get away from the wall!
Y-you don't need to pat me there yet...
I-I-I-I'm sorry!
Relax, Takuma-chan.
I'll fix your damaged house later
with my sacred sword.
Big Sister Misa, it's...
Futaba has her glasses on!
G-glasses?!
Futaba's eyesight is so bad,
she can't see anything with her naked eye.
So when she's serious about fighting,
she puts on her glasses!
And then she steals her defeated opponents' panties!
But why panties?!
Panties are the last line of defense.
Gulp!
Hence, having one's panties stolen,
is, in other words, equivalent to death.
Death?!
DEATH
Huh?
Takumacchi, take flight!
Oh dear, Takuma-chan got away
and now you're the bait.
Bait? Underestimating us would be a mistake, Futaba.
It's two on one, now!
Don't assume you can take us down so easily!
Oh my...
I'm not assuming I can take you down easily at all.
Let's see, to borrow the words of Big Sister Ichika,
if it's for my beloved sisters,
I will take all the time I need.
Now then, please hand over your panties.
Ouch. That was very violent.
Squishy?!
Big Brother, I'd like you to
give me back my headphones.
Huh? Oh, sure...
Suddenly flying in without warning
and forcing a younger girl down,
and furthermore, thoroughly groping her chest...
I hope you die.
Ooh, there they are!
Hey, why is he so pale?
Dunno.
Anyway, we have to work out a strategy.
The discrepancy between Futaba's combat ability
and ours is glaringly obvious.
The most dangerous part of it is
her holy sword "Castle" ability.
The holy sword "Castle" is the ability to summon
the entirety of Asgard's Valhalla.
At level 1 she can only summon one castle wall,
but until she employs that strategy,
Her Majesty the Queen won't stop.
However, as long as we can
manage to outrun her, then we win.
Only think about protecting yourself.
I spy panties...
H-Her Majesty the Queen!
We're doing exactly what we discussed!
Level 1, sacred sword summon!!
Sacred sword, strengthened.
So you're using a co-op technique, huh?
However...
I wonder if you can break through
my "castle" with that?
I absolutely cannot go along with them.
I'll hide in the storehouse for now.
Are you sure about that?
There's a voice coming from the storehouse!
My father once told me a proverb.
"If a coward escapes from battle,
he thinks he can live forever.
However, even if he can avoid the lance,
he cannot avoid the advancement of age."
You can understand that too, right, Master?
What should you fight for, to reach your own goals?
W-well...
You can't do that, Natsuki-chan.
No panty-less persons on the battlefield.
Panty-less?!
Ow!
Well now, next is Takuma-chan.
Only three more meters to Takuma-chan's undies...
Death!
Academic
Achievement
Here's a good luck charm
for your academic achievement.
A rune that stands for knowledge, is the best thing
to keep your needs etched into your mind.
Huh?
That one is handmade by us.
Jeez, Futaba, you got a bit too serious with this one.
I do apologize. I got so excited!
Actually, this game of Tag was a plan
to help refresh you, Takuma-chan.
Takuma-chan, you're always staying up
studying until late, right?
I was hoping it'd be a good outlet for you.
Natsuki-chan, I'm sorry.
I was the one who gave him the present...
I-I-I don't care who gave it to him!
Anyway, that's a present from us to thank you
for always taking care of us.
I-I mean, it's nothing big,
but you've accepted us into your home, and...
Is Takuma dead?!
I told you that if this game of Tag was too stressful,
something like that could happen.
Big Brother Takuma, you're super pale!
I hope he does die.
Whoa, Yakumo, he might actually be dead, you know!
Oh dear.
I see. You got the good luck charm
to Takuma-kun safely.
You really call that safe?
Everything after it was a mess.
And also, I played with Big Brother Takuma,
and it was fun!
That's great, Kururi-chan!
Big Bro forced me down, though...
T..Takuma-kun forced you down?!
Yup.
What?!
We worked hard together to make it.
I hope he's happy with... with that good luck charm.
Mom...
It turns out I really can't live with other people.
Why do I have to go through this?
But I wonder how long it's been...
Academic
Achievement
since I've gotten a present from someone?
It's almost time for the campus festival.
Along with the Val Love for
"Campus Festival Date" is "live together,"
so this is a chance to everyone to raise their levels!
We must make this a success, by all means!
The problem is all of the instances of
Father's oracles being wrong.
Did you all see anything suspicious out there?
It's not necessarily the case that their souls
are accidentally drawn into these things.
Their souls are accidentally...
What about you, Itsuyo?
Let me see. Suspicious people...
Lovely to see you!
Lovely
Council
Stu
dent
to see you!
Council
Stu
dent
Council
Stu
dent
All of them are good people.
I see.
Sorry, no one suspicious comes to mind.
I mean, the most suspicious person around is me, so...
No one stands out to me either.
Big Sister Misa...
Huh?
What's up with you two?
I thought you were sleeping.
Kururi was crying.
Oof.
Did you have a bad dream?
I'm right here with you, so calm down, okay?
I'll verify the oracle being wrong with Valhalla.
In any case, our combat power is still unstable here.
Everyone be careful, and let's support this date!
For the campus festival...
it looks like our class will be doing a maid café.
I-I gotta potty.
Do you know what that is?
Pa... Father told me that a maid outfit may be
the same as a woman's combat uniform in this world!
I wonder what they look like.
You're enjoying this, aren't you, Natsuki-san?
Campus festivals aren't part of the culture of Asgard.
Even though it's my duty,
I'm looking forward to going around all the shops!
Well, I guess you aren't interested in going
on a date at the campus festival, though.
No, I'm looking forward to the festival, too.
Huh?
Because...
I have free time during the festival,
so I can study all I want!
Oh, right...
Natsuki, what do you think you're doing
during break time?
I'm cleaning, of course.
I have to make sure the school building is nice and tidy!
After all, today I am...
on day duty!
For just one day
Class
Commander
At least this much can be done before breakfast!
Is Takuma studying?
He's always like that, no matter what time it is.
Yesterday, he wouldn't even look in my direction.
N..Natsuki-chan!
Cleaning on your own sure is rough, huh?
I'll help you out.
Natsuki-chan, are you listening?
Goodness, what do I do about this?
Natsuki-chan, can you hear me?
Could it be...
that he's not attracted to me?!
Compared to Itsuyo and the others,
my body is definitely lacking...
But I'm still developing, and thinking back on it,
I think I've been the harshest on Takuma so far...
Natsuki-chan?
Maybe I should play up my cute side some more...
Natsuki Saotome-san?
I-I don't, though!
This is just... to level up more efficiently!
Y..Yamada-kun?!
I'm sorry! I was just... well...
I-It's okay, Natsuki-chan.
No it isn't, really...
Sorry, okay?
She's an angel!
Yamada-kun?!
Yamada fell again!
Natsuki.
We need a favor from you, is that okay?
You know there's an inspection for
what we're doing at the festival, right?
We have to do a demonstration
in front of a student council member.
W-well...
The girl that's supposed to do it is absent today,
so we'd like you to do it in her place...
Oh man, she's an angel!
So cute!
THIS is the rumored maid outfit?
It's much cuter than I imagined it would be!
I hate that it calls attention to my worst feature
but I have to do my best.
After all, I'm on day duty!
Excuse me.
I'm Inukai from the student council.
I'm here to inspect your festival presentation.
O-okay!
Frozen
stiff
Thank you for your guidance todyay... today!
Oh no, thank you for your cooperation.
Is something wrong?
Ah, no. I was just recalling something that
the president was concerned about.
Itsuyo?
Something like your interests being
far too childish for your age, Natsuki-senpai.
What?!
Th-they aren't...
I have work to do for my day duty...
but I don't have particularly childish interests...
It's alright.
It looks great on you, Natsuki-senpai.
Th-thank you.
Ugh.
You seriously believe what I said about that dress?
But why did I have to be so nice to those
who are part of the main gods in the first place?
I'm going to devour you!
Don't you blush at me!
And you can't just talk to me freely!
You meatless skin bag.
Thicken up and then do your squealing!
Oh, it's nothing.
Well then, shall we go ahead
and begin the inspection?
It's like watching an angel and an akuma.
Is Natsuki-chan okay?
How did this happen?
You may begin.
He's still uninterested in me, just like always!
Watch me now! I'll show you that I have a cute side!
Maid outfits... are a woman's...
combat uniform!
Combat uniform!!
Welcome home, Master!
Throb!
Oh no, death by cuteness!
I think I might fall out of the window again...
An excellent response!
Now witness this technique
transmitted directly from Papa!
He's not looking!
Dammit!
I'll make you a parfait.
What kind would you like?
Uh... I'm not very hungry right now.
Choose from vanilla, chocolate, or green tea, please!
I-I'll have vanilla.
Dammit!
Day Duty
Natsuki
Saotome
Apologies for the wait!
Is this the, uh... vanilla?
Yeah!
It's my own special interpretation!
Interpretation?
Now then, to top it off,
we'll cast some magic on it to make it yummy!
While I add the cream...
Huh? The cream won't come out...
S-sorry, I'll clean you up right away.
Screw that Akuma!!
That jerk! How dare he get so close
to Natsuki-chan's maid outfit?!
I wanna eat her parfait too!
Come on, stay still!
But I can do it myself!
Feed us...
Huh?
PARFAITS!
These are... akuma!
What's going on?
There were no signs of any until a little while ago!
I can't believe there's a demon appearing
on campus again after the other day.
And at a time like this...
Could it be that whoever is interfering with the oracle
is an accomplice of the malevolent gods?!
Save me!
He's so weak!
What a pain!
Natsuki-san!
No, let me go!
What are you doing?!
Help me...
Takuma...
A-are you okay?
Thanks.
I get it now.
So this is the limit of the Valkyries in their human forms.
Today was rough, wasn't it?
It sure was.
And today's commotion ruined the afternoon classes.
Seriously, studying is the only thing
you think about, huh?
S-sorry.
It doesn't matter. I'm used to it already.
Well, it's fine, I guess.
You probably don't want to be with
a girl who's as homely as I am anyway.
I think you're pretty cute, though.
Huh?
Wh-what's wrong?
Natsuki-san?
Wh...
Huh?
It's nothing!
Huh? But your face is red.
When I say it's nothing, then I mean it's nothing!
Uh... N..Natsuki-san?
Shut your mouth! And don't follow me!
What?! Was it something I did?!
Natsuki-san!
Please, wait up!
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Koi o shiranakucha you and I, hajimaranai no yo?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
We wanna share your heart!
(How do you tell me?)
Amai kotoba o input
Shippai - Cancel - Zenzen hibikanai kedo
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch shite todokete yo
Seikou- Complete - Saisentan ga ii darou?
(Hold me tight)
Naze koi to itte kurenai no?
Ai ni yukou
Motto keiken shite level up otome gokoro
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Oshiete ageru wa, koi wa otome no power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Jucchuuhakku kitto mou lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Tokimeku mune dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Akuma de shy na mind, kiss for you!
Kaete shimau yo na, kiss for me!
Koi o hajimemasho!
The akuma are appearing in rapid succession,
so perhaps there's something
going on at the school after all?
I hope it'll be okay.
The campus festival has finally just begun.
If we succeed at the Val Love, "Festival Date"
then everyone can level up all at once.
We have to give it our best!
You've become somewhat
reliable lately, Mutsumi-chan.
Next time: "The Believing Maiden."
Next time: The Believing Maiden
Now that I think about it, your panties are
the only ones I have yet to snatch, Mutsumi-chan.
Big Sister Futaba, why are you wearing glasses?!
Wait!