So this is Midgard, huh?
We're already at our destination, my lady.
Please be cautious.
Good. Make a note of this, Roskva.
It is also one's duty as a noble
to expose oneself to their subjects.
Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
The sweet desire I found is here today as well
From inside of me
Someone screams at you to notice
We stare at one another, at an irritating distance
Alone, I endure
The onslaught of sadness
Though I want to tell you this feeling of love
I can't say a word
Though you're always at my side
Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
A strong emotion set aflame
I won't hesitate, I don't want to hesitate
I'll believe in now, and take a step forward
For the sake of myself
Will you go to the city after school
and get some sewing tools for me?
Good grief! Big Sister Misa and the others would be
completely hopeless without me! Seriously!
At any rate... this is a train, huh?
It's just as packed as I heard it would be.
I want to hurry home and treat myself
to a mikan under the kotatsu.
C-could this be...
what they call a "groper"?!
The fiendish enemy of maidens, akin to an akuma!
Trying his hand against a Valkyrie has sealed his fate!
I will capture him!
W-wait, Itsuyo! It's me!
Natsuki? Wh-what in the world are you doing?
What do you mean?
Didn't Misa-san ask you to do Val Love,
"Protect a Maiden from a Groper"?
You're gonna do a Val Love with Itsuyo, okay?
You'll be the groper.
I guess I have to.
I agree to go shopping!
I was so happy that I to be given a task by
Big Sister Misa I completely forgot! How dumb!
Exactly what I wanted!
Now then, come on and grope me!
Shh! You're too loud!
When the train gets to the station,
I push Natsuki-san aside and rescue Itsuyo-san!
Push Natsuki-san aside and save Itsuyo-san!
Okay!
Excuse me, can I have a word with you?
Huh?! I-I'm...
The suspicious person is in custody, over.
Will you come with me to the station staff office?
C-crap!
Okay, we're going to start again.
G-got it!
Val Love, commence.
Val Love
Commence
In any case, this pressure is intense.
They were about the same size when we were younger,
so why is there such a big difference now?
We grew up under the
same circumstances and everything!
N-Natsuki! You're focusing too much on my chest!
S-sorry.
This is to become the strongest of the Valkyries!
The train will sway up ahead, so please be careful.
N-Natsuki? That place is very...
I told you, you're concentrating
too much on my boobs!
Natsuki! Are you listening to me?
What a gorgeous body...
This must be the ideal maiden "boi-oi-oing"!
Here too!
And here!
We're almost at our destination!
I just have to tolerate this a bit longer...
Due to discovery of a suspicious person in the station,
train operation has been interrupted.
We apologize for the trouble,
but please stay put for the time being.
A suspicious person?!
Who in the world would do something
at a time like this?
I can't believe this is still happening.
Hurry, hurry and get to the station!
I-I'm glad I could somehow clear up
this misunderstanding.
Looks like the train isn't here yet,
so I'll just catch my breath for now.
The train on track two will arrive momentarily.
Please stand inside the yellow line.
It's here! Push Natsuki-san aside
and save Itsuyo-san!
Push Natsuki-san aside and save Itsuyo-san!
Now!
C-crap! The exit's on the other side!
T
This side
will open
I
N
I-it's so horrifically packed in here.
My internal human sensor
can't move past this and it's going off...
But, I'm going in!
E-excuse me!
Found 'em!
G-groper, eradicated!
Val Love, "Protect a Maiden from
a Groper," accomplished.
Val Love
Protect a Maiden from a Groper
Accomplished
We did it, Itsuyo! The Val Love was successful!
Y-you did a great job!
Dash
Everyone's too handsy with my boobs!
Flounder's cheap today! Super cheap!
Good evening, sir!
Oh, Taka-chan. What'll it be today?
Let's see... Can I have three herring, please?
Here, this one's on me, too.
Huh? Are you sure?
The two of you brothers living huddled together
is enough to make me wanna cry!
Don't worry about it!
Thanks, sir!
Oh my, Taka-chan, on your way home from school?
Yes.
Taka-chan, good evening!
Good evening, flower shop lady!
Taka-chan, would you like to
come over for dinner tonight?
I've made too much...
I'm sorry, I'll have to pass this time.
Today, a friend of mine is coming over to play!
Big Brother, I'm home.
Good grief.
Tore your collar off, eh?
You'll be punished again later, Big Brother.
I haven't eaten anything in three days.
I'm starving.
Let me eat something.
No.
More importantly, I bought some ingredients
so I need you to cook.
We must prepare our welcome for Our Lady.
You're outta your damn mind!
Why the hell do I have to...
Yes, sir! I'll get right on it!
By the way, would it be alright if I had
a few nibbles of something?
I'm feeling a bit hungry...
No.
You got it!
Herring simmered in soy sauce...
Put it all backwards and what do you get?
Something different!
Now then, Our Lady loves sweets.
It's simple, but dessert will be...
Great.
This is pretty good, these dumplings or whatever.
We are satisfied.
It is Our Lady!
Oh, Our Lady, what a sight for sore eyes you arf!
Did you like to eat spicy foods?
Garm-sama, take it easy with the joking.
I will slaughter you.
Stop that.
Yes, ma'am.
We were given two imperial commands
from the duke:
Destroy the Valkyries, and acquire the Misteltein.
Everything else is trivial.
Take a note, Roskva.
Yes, ma'am.
The sweets of Midgard are quite tasty.
"Proverbs of Our Lady"
They are quite tasty... okay.
What a nice place Midgard is.
I, Skuld, will unquestionably fulfill
the imperial commands,
guide us toward the victory at Ragnarok,
The Third Norn
"Skuld"
Egg Lv. 52
so just try save this world!
Things are getting perilous aren't they, Valkyries?!
Is something wrong?
No, I just got a chill.
Anyways, have you been able to
summon that book at will yet?
N-no. I'm sorry.
Well, you are a normal human,
so there's likely a large degree of
inconsistency for your abilities.
By the way, Takuma, what is that you have there?
It's a study book.
There's a mock exam coming up.
I forgot about that!
Not to be rude, but Natsuki-san,
I think you should study harder.
I-I know that.
Look! I even got new glasses the other day!
Oh...
When I put these on,
my grades should improve in no time!
See? Look! How's this?!
Um.
I'm freezing... Did I catch a cold?
Wh-wh-wha...
Er, well... You looked cold, so I thought
if I held your hand it might warm you up.
E-even so, it's shocking to have someone
suddenly grab your hand, right?!
You could have given me a jacket or something!
I-I'm sorry!
But...
I feel very warm. Thanks.
Natsuki-san?
There's something here!
It was just a moment... but I'm sure I felt it.
A feeling of bloodlust like a spear
that pierces even the darkness!
Is this a new type of akuma?
A vanguard of the malevolent gods?!
Could they have made it this far
without being sensed by the aether stream?!
Um...
Stay back!
Natsuki-san!
My arms are so numb I can't move them.
I've still got a ways to go until I'm home...
What do I do?
This is happening when I can't transform, of all days!
At this rate, I'll die...
Ten seconds.
I can't believe you handled my lunges
in ten seconds flat.
You've improved, Natsuki.
That voice...
Exactly what I'd expect from my little sister!
Ichika Saotome
"Brunhilde"
"Spear" Lv. 1
Good grief, I can't stand guys like you...
It's pathetic that you're always
being protected by Natsuki!
Shame on you, Lover!
wobble
shake
Er, well...
I'm sorry.
Defeat
C-Captain, it's not that bad...
Natsuki, you have to fall back!
Er, um... It's nice to meet you, elder sister.
This is NOT the first time I've met you!
I've been guarding your ass this entire time.
At that time, and at that time, and that time too!
My beloved sisters are with a weakling like this,
and going on d-d-d-dates?!
It's too late to change Einheijer at this point.
But here's something to keep in mind, Lover:
Next time, just try to make one foul move.
When that happens,
you'll be gored to death within a second!
What?
You're back, Big Sis Ichika?
Wow! It's Big Sister Ichika!
It's been so long, my beloved sisters!
I missed you all!
Big Sister, you're just as little as you always are!
And you get bigger every time we meet, Kururi!
Big Sister Ichika, I baked cookies.
Would you like some?
Of course I'd like some!
I should go to the bathroom while I can...
Wobble
Where are you off to, Lover?
I'm not done speaking with you.
I'm behind her, how could she tell?!
Calm down, Ichika...
Here you go, Sis.
Delicious! As expected from my little sister!
The time has finally come.
Big Sister Futaba!
Big Sister Futaba cleaned the bath for us!
Big Sister Ichika is here to take
the offensive role in place of Natsuki-chan.
I'm sorry, Captain.
Don't worry about it, dear sister!
Big Sister Ichika is still level one,
so you have to work hard, Takuma-chan.
Now then, let's get started with... Val Love:
"Scrub Each Other Down in the Bath!"
Throb
This is even more pressure than with Natsuki-san.
Why are you so hesitant all of a sudden?
Were you seriously thinking that you're a man
who is worthy of being recognized as one?
You need to re-evaluate yourself, weakling.
I'm sorry.
I heard something from Futaba, Lover.
She says you can't efficiently handle your abilities.
Come on, try to call forth that book.
Huh? O-okay.
Ability... invoke!
I... I'm sorry. I really can't seem to do it.
You, Lover...
What do you think about my sisters?
Wh-why this all of a sudden?
Just answer the question you've been asked!
You surely don't mean to say
that you hate them or something...
I-I-I would never!
I'm grateful to them.
Though this is to save the world,
they still keep me company.
Having me as their partner must be tough,
so I'm sorry about that.
That was a pathetic answer.
This must be why you can't efficiently use your ability.
Huh?
You're Einheijer, aren't you?
It's highly unlikely that a lover
can become stronger without falling in love.
What you feel toward my sisters
isn't love; it's obligation!
Though there are nine sacred swords
in your possession,
you can only handle two at once,
and that's why.
When the maidens and their lover
feel the same, they become stronger.
Therefore, while you remain weak it's difficult for
the maidens to get stronger than they are now.
It's impossible to change the lover at this point!
At the very least, try to become a man
that can make me fall for you, Lover!
Respond.
O-okay!
Excuse us...
Oh, what is it, my sisters?
Futaba asked us to do something...
It may get heavy in there with just the two of them,
so try to keep the mood nice.
I just wanted to get in the bath early.
Huh?
What?!
D-don't stare at me, dummy!
I-I-I'm sorry!
Were you staring at her, bastard?!
I'b shorry!
W-well, I'm going to start now.
Hey, hey, Big Sis Misa.
Hmm?
Is Big Sis Ichika really that strong?
Oh right, you've never seen Ichika fight, have you?
Big Sister Ichika has a Seidr,
just like Yakumo-chan and Shino-chan.
A Seidr where in exchange for their mighty power,
they have abnormal conditions.
Though Big Sister Ichika's a demigoddess,
she may be capable of competing on
the same level as the high-ranking gods.
Abnormal conditions?
Yeah. Yakumo has hypersensitive hearing,
but in Ichika's case,
it's extremely sensitive skin.
Big Sister Ichika's skin feels things very easily.
She can sense the position of the enemy
through the sensations on her skin.
Even at level one she can
completely defeat the enemies.
She was very reliable on the Valhalla defense mission.
She was so amazing then!
Then with her sensitive skin...
is it okay if she and Big Brother
are washing each other?
Well, Natsuki is with them so it'll be fine, right?
Kururi-chan, do you want some snacks?
Gimme!
It's so warm under here...
Endure...
I must endure!
Don't wither under the sensations of the Lover...
I have to... keep feeling it!
U-um, are you okay?
I will not be taken down by the likes of you!
What?!
It's my turn next.
I think I'm experiencing déjà vu or something.
I hope we can finish this with no incident.
An incident!
Err...
Wh-what is it, Lover?!
What are you doing right now?
What do you mean? I heard this is
the traditional way to bathe in Midgard!
Yakumo told me!
Yakumo-san?!
I can't believe I'm doing something so disgraceful!
And for such a weakling...
Every time I rub on him, I feel like I'll pass out.
But...
I haven't lost yet!
...ki... tsuki...
Natsuki...
Wha?!
You've been so fidgety, what's wrong?
N-nothing's wrong!
I thought you might want to do
a scrub down with Big Brother too.
Th-that isn't...
Wh-what are you doing all of a sudden?!
I just kinda wanted... to tease you a bit.
You're so blunt!
You like Big Brother, right?
Wh-wh-who would would like someone so shameless?
It's okay to admit it, you know.
If a maiden is emotionally involved with her lover,
it's easier to accumulate experience points,
and everything is smooth sailing from there.
You should go ahead and confess to him.
If he feels the same about you,
he might touch you more.
Perhaps your cute boobies.
Wh-whoa, Yakumo! Cut it out!
It's true, I love your voice most of all...
H-hey! That's not a good...
S-stop doing this!
Ow...
Whoa.
Kiss with Lover, confirmed.
Kiss with Lover
Confirmed
Invoking Valkyrie...
Valkyrie Invoked
The First Valkyrie
"Brunhilde"
"Spear" Lv. 1
Make one foul move,
and you'll be dead in a second.
I-I'm sorry!
What just happened was an accident-
Even at level one the Captain is ridiculously strong,
but her AP is extremely low.
In other words, I guess you could say
she has bad energy efficiency, or...well...
Since she's level one, even when she transforms
she's unable to move for even a second.
Uh...
Don't you think you've won this, Lover.
This is nothing more than the prologue
to a long-lasting battle!
Know that it is the one standing in the end
who is the true victor!
C-Captain, I'll turn you face up for now, okay?
Thank you, Natsuki.
As expected of my little sister!
I can't breathe like this.
I seriously went too far.
Sorry.
It's totally okay so don't worry, Yakumo!
I wonder what love is...
Val Love, "Scrub Each Other Down
in the Bath," accomplished.
Our Lady. Will you please say that once more?
Very well. Take a note, Roskva.
Yes, ma'am.
Listening to the needs of the subjects
is also the duty of a ruler, after all.
"After all"... okay.
We once more declare:
From here, we will infiltrate the enemy fortress,
and kill Einheijer in a single blow!
What is it, you bastard?
You surely don't think you've won
on such a trivial matter, do you?!
N-no.
Uh... having super sensitive skin
seems like it'd be rough in daily life.
That's a worthless opinion typical of a weakling.
My super sensitive skin is instrumental
precisely because I'm on the battlefield.
I sense even the slightest move of the enemy!
I-I see.
That means you can throw your spear
precisely without even looking, right?
If you make one foul move,
this spear will pass through you in a second!
Eek!
Next time, "The Drunken Maiden."
Next time: The Drunken Maiden