Joint Campus Festival
99th
Hokuou
Academy
Come get your delicious okonomiyaki!
Oops, excuse m-
A-Akuma is walking with a girl?!
She's wearing our junior high section's uniform!
Is this a kidnapping?!
Everyone's staring daggers at me!
Forgive me...
At times like this... I should smile...
Didn't mean to scare you to DEATH...
Death?! H-h-help!
Shake
Worry
DEATH? N-no! I said I scared you to death!
D-d-d-don't kill me!
Big Brother.
What are you even doing?
I wish you'd escort me properly.
O-okay.
It's more crowded than I imagined!
Val love "Campus Festival Date"...
Seems like it's a bonus stage
where the more we go around together
the more experience points we acquire,
but I have to make sure I do my best
not to die from fear!
Big Brother.
I wish you'd hurry up.
Maid Café
C'mon in
You two sure took your time!
But what's wrong?
You look like you're about to die.
N-nothing. It's very crowded.
I'm hungry...
I'll take you to a table, so hold on a second.
Please take your time and enjoy!
Th-thanks.
What is it?
I-It's nyaathing!
Something weird's going on with Natsuki-san.
Did I do something wrong again?
But right now...
What?
Er, nothing!
Uh, Yakumo-san, what would you like to eat?
Anything is fine,
so I wish you'd hurry up and choose.
I-I-I'm sorry!
I'm getting agitated for some reason.
Okay, this is where I...
Let's see... well then, we'll have this
squid ink pasta with squid ink on the side...
Rumble
Sorry for the wait!
Here's the Lovey-Dovey Couple drink!
Um... err...
It's alright, this is my treat. After all, I'm...
Yakumo's big sister, you know!
Take that!
O-okay, I appreciate your kindness.
Ew.
Huh?
I don't wanna drink from the same cup as you.
That's gross.
But...
If you insist, though...
Then suck on this.
May as well since we'll be
drinking it together, right?
Uh, but...
I wish you'd get on with it.
R-right! Sorry.
You're so bad at this... easy with the teeth.
S-s-sorry.
Sue is so much better at this.
That feels nice.
Do you want to drink more?
U-uh, yes, please.
My neck is getting stiff.
I'll adjust my posture...
Woah, I'm soaked. Gross.
S-s-s-sorry!
Were you hoping to suck on something like this too?
Pervert.
Stab!
Pervert
Yakumo! You can't take your clothes off here!
Natsuki, get off my back.
Shock! A-anyways, put your clothes on!
Ooh, there's a huge crowd here.
But what are you guys doing?
Misa, sisters, hey there!
Getting here was pretty rough.
Pretty rough!
Everyone seems to be fully
enjoying themselves despite that.
Chatter
Hey, what the hell is going on there?
Akuma is surrounded by girls?!
This absolutely has to be...
Blackmail!
My stomach hurts!
By the way, Takuma-chan.
Are you okay with being Natsuki-chan's
partner for the dance party?
Y-you mean that thing?
What are you talking about?
I heard there's a late-night festival where
a man and a woman pair up and dance.
Is there a huge event like that?!
D-dance party, huh?
But I have no interest whatsoever
in cute things like that!
And I've never thought anything like
I'd like to try dancing with Takuma at least once...
You're so obvious!
I think Natsuki would make a good partner.
I sincerely do not care.
R-really?
But I want to dance too!
Which do you like more, dancing or snacks?
Snacks!
W-well, I don't care either way,
but if that's what everyone wants...
Er, well, you see....
It's just that I don't want to go with Natsuki,
but lately people have been getting scarier to me
day by day or something like that,
and it feels even more like I'm gonna get killed
if I'm with such a popular girl like Natsuki-san.
So maybe it'd be better
if I paired up with someone else...
Er, um...
I forgot that I'm working right now.
Big Sisters, see you later!
Takumacchi, pretend that
fairly awful exchange didn't happen.
Huh?!
Yes, that was fairly awful.
Nanna.
A sprite that lives in the realm of the gods.
Munch
A fairy?
Nanna the Fairy always
gives me snacks so I love Nanna!
Dance Party Info
I just don't want to go with Natsuki-san.
I get that he has no interest in me, but...
Natsuki-chan, are you okay?
I thought you might be feeling down.
N-No, I'm not.
Still so young...
M-more importantly, Big Sister Futaba,
are you all doing okay?
I'm shocked everyone came today, too.
Goodness, what a day this has turned into...
Hokuou Academy's No. 1 will be decided!
Miss Hokuou Academy Beauty Pageant
Beauty Pageant
What is this?!
I'm looking forward to seeing who wins.
I didn't enter this!
Someone else chose to do that!
Itsuyo-chan applied to this!
She said it was a competition.
That idiot!
But there's something else I really want to hear about!
I already know.
Big Sister Ichika is on alert for us.
The captain is?!
The campus festival is a chance for
all of us to raise our levels at once.
But the buildings are now densely packed.
Therefore, the crowd is overflowing.
Under these circumstances,
the enemy is definitely setting something up.
Three guests, coming through.
Haunted House
A-Akuma?! Someone come work the front for me!
This is pretty professional.
Uh, Takuma?!
tremble
shiver
I don't mind ghosts, but when I think about
people dressing up I-I-I-I...
Your phobia of people!
And what's wrong with you, Kururi?!
I thought it was a snack house!
That's not even close!
Misa-san...
Big Sis Misa...
You two are hopeless. Jeez.
Watch your step, okay?
Sorry, Big Sister Misa.
I-I-I'm truly sorry about this...
You know, Takuma, a guy
really shouldn't cower that much.
It lowers your self-worth.
Huh? Oh well... Er...
I-I'm sorry.
You said it again.
I-I-I'm sorry!
Listen to me.
When you're feeling helpless,
don't say "sorry," say "Thanks."
That sounds way cooler.
Misa-san...
Maybe it's because her hair is nice and neat,
Messy
What's up?
Maybe it's because her hair is nice and neat,
but she seems less aggressive than usual.
Thank you, Big Sister Misa.
You're welcome.
Th-that stupid Akuma!
While I'm covered in sweat from working
he's freakin' flirting with girls!
Maybe it's time to settle old scores, huh?!
Also, apologize to Natsuki later, okay?
All of that made her pretty angry.
Er, why was Natsuki-san angry?
You should at least figure that part out on your own...
R-right, er... Sorry.
Or maybe I should say "thanks"?
You're very rigid, aren't you?
That's another reason Natsuki is angry with you!
I-I'm sorry.
Kururi?! What's wrong with her?
Who knows.
Of course you'd be afraid of a live eel.
Now for the other two.
Wh-what happened?!
There's something in my clothes!
T-Takuma...
Yes?
I can't stand... the wriggling...
Get it out...
O-okay. Here goes...
N-no, go lower!
I-I'm sorry, I mean, thank you very much!
You idiot!
No... don't touch me there!
I'll let it go outside!
Hey, someone might be falling out of the window!
I-idiot... Now he's alone...
Is he falling or not?
He fell!
I-I'm exhausted.
What am I doing?
I was planning to focus on my studies
during the campus festival...
Seriously, why in the world is this happening?
Academic
Achievement
Akutsu-senpai?
Uh, y-you're from the student council...
I'm Inukai. What are you doing here?
Huh?! W-Well to be honest,
I thought this eel here was a ghost,
and uh, I went out to look for some water I guess, um...
You're very entertaining.
He's the first person I've talked to
besides Natsuki-san and her sisters,
Thumptwitch
but I'm doing fairly well... kind of...
But I'm shocked to see that you're
actually enjoying the festival, Senpai.
Actually... I, uh... was invited by someone I know.
O-oh, is that so?
Then I suppose I have to show some appreciation
to that person you know, right?
Where did Takuma-san go?
He might be over here.
What, are you feeling discouraged, Natsuki?!
Huh? I-I'm really not...
I do think that it'll be fine since
Big Sister Ichika is here, but...
Excuse us, we're in a hurry. Let us pass through here.
I've been worried about you this whole time.
I had no idea what I'd do if you hadn't shown up.
I thought I would starve to death...
An akuma!
Those akuma are the kind that possess humans!
Did they really possess the entire academy?!
Someone once said that love is
the source of a maiden's power.
That's why I must stop that source.
Battling maidens without their Einheijer
are the same as pigs that only exist to be eaten.
Now then...
Here's the main dish I've been waiting for.
The enemy did set something up for us...
Big Sister Misa!
Take a look at this. It's the entrance to the barrier.
Did Big Brother put the akuma inside a barrier?
The barrier manifestation point is
the little finger of Einheijer's left hand.
Th-then where in the world is Takuma?
Could it be that after the barrier was stretched,
he fell victim to the enemy?
It's because we left him on his own!
There's no point talking about
what what's already done.
For now, we need to do something about that akuma.
At this rate the barrier will be broken
and Midgard will perish!
There are two ways to destroy the barrier.
We can either destroy it from the inside,
or destroy it from the entrance on the outside.
Natsuki, stand by in front of the entrance.
I need you to guard the outside.
G-got it.
But what about you and everyone else?
Until Takuma gets here,
we'll go inside and keep that akuma in check!
It sure is huge now that I'm seeing it up close.
I-I wonder if we'll get out of this alive...
We're not necessarily trying to defeat it.
Remember what our teacher told us?
When up against a stronger enemy,
the three guidelines are:
"Don't worry about your weaknesses."
"Don't rush in without a plan."
"Don't die."
Surviving means you can
have a meal with everyone again.
That's not something you need to point out to us!
I see. Sorry about that.
Well then, are you two ready?
Sacred Sword "Cannon," strengthened.
Sacred Sword
"Cannon"
strengthened!
Kururi!
Take that!
Keep them apart and don't let their awareness
turn towards the barrier.
Got it!
There are so many of them!
Disgraceful!
Oh no...
C-Captain!
Sorry I'm late.
I-it's okay, you saved us!
I received a message from Misa.
She said there's a possibility that weakling
got captured by the enemy.
Well...
So this is what happens when you're
away from him for even a few moments... Pitiful.
I'm pissed we have to deal with
the consequences of his failures,
but we'll protect the barrier until the end!
R-right!
Takuma...
please be safe!
Cooking Room
Y-yummy! Tasty, tasty, this meal is so tasty!
Those piggies are going to meet their end
without me even laying a finger on them.
The meal I'm having while watching all of this go down...
It's all so scrumptious!
Don't you agree, Akutsu-senpai?
What do you think?
How do you like this banquet I'm hosting?
Have yourself a bite too, Senpai!
Here, come on!
Get to eating, already!
How dare you act so ungrateful
towards me for sparing your life? Eh?!
Well, that's fine. The banquet has just started.
Let's take our time and enjoy ourselves...
Let's watch those piggies get sloppily devoured...
I have five string puppets left...
Can I really hold out?
Oh no, Itsuyo! That's...
Oh no!
My body... No!
Help me, Father...
Takuma-san!
Itsuyo!
Kururi-chan, wait!
Love is the source of power?
You make me laugh.
Having to rely on such a thing for power,
it is of no importance.
Big Sister Mutsumi!
Power is the rampaging appetite itself!
You two, stay back!
Svadilfari will consume them all.
He'll turn the bait into puppets,
and their pain, their pleasure,
their souls will all be eaten up.
He's already sunk his fangs in...
All that's left is to savor the flavor.
What's keeping the barrier up
is the fact that the weakling is still alive.
I presume that means the enemy has not killed him.
What does that mean?
I'm not sure why, but one thing that's clear is
unless the weakling escapes from
the hand of the enemy, it's over for us.
I believe in him.
Because Takuma-kun is our lover!
I can't move my body.
Maybe that's because there's a hole in my stomach
I wonder what happened to everyone else.
No... My mind is so foggy...
Sorry, Mom. I couldn't keep my promise.
I'm sorry, everyone...
Academic
Achievement
Natsuki's Room
E-excuse me.
What do you want? Today's the festival, you know?
You know we have to practice for the dance.
Dance?
I-it's nyaathing!
Uh, a-actually, I was thinking I wasn't
a suitable lover after all...
So... I'm very sorry...
And there's no way I can accept this.
Academic
Achievement
What? Why?
I heard from Misa-san that it was highly likely
an enemy would attack during the festival.
In other words, you want to run away
because you don't want to put yourself in danger.
Is that what you're saying?!
Yes, that's right.
I mean, if I die no one will be able to
transform anymore, right?
My legs won't stop shaking, even now.
The way that I am now,
I can't do anything when I need to.
Leave me behind with everyone who can't fight
and I'll die in an instant!
That's why, well...
So you really are...
an idiot.
Huh?!
You being incompetent isn't anything new,
and absolutely no one here expects you
to suddenly spring into action now!
If you're always assuming that you're going to die
then there's nothing to be done about that.
That was a waste of time.
Come on, let's get to school.
I-I was being serious about that.
You can't do anything when the time calls for it?
Don't be stupid.
Haven't you saved me numerous times
when I needed you?
Both when an akuma was summoned to the park
and when I was attacked in the classroom,
It was just like the first time I met you.
That's why I'm not worried about anything.
I believe in you, Takuma.
I believe that in your soul resides a sword
that's greater than anyone's...
Oh?
Oh no, what's wrong?
You've suddenly got much more motivation!
Would you mind not interrupting my meal?
Were you always so callous towards others, Senpai?!
It's true that I'm afraid of people.
Just being near them makes me scream,
and they're always making rumors about me,
and not even Natsuki and her sisters
understand this fear. But...
Even though I'm scared...
I didn't mind it!
Shut up.
Shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up!
I told you not to freakin' interrupt my meal
with your bullshit.
Your stomach is already sliced open, so die.
His stomach is sliced open?
You sure are the type to say some rather brutal things.
You look like you're wondering
how I knew you were here.
My older sister went around putting an
identifying tag on everyone she passed by.
The people we monitored, including the participants
of the campus festival and the guests,
totals 862.
She also tagged your hair, you know?
With thread.
Now let's see.
Something about this situation
feels somewhat ominous,
so would you mind giving me an explanation
as to what's going on?
I'm so glad!
Everyone started getting unruly
and so I was hiding with Senpai!
Oh my!
I was so scared it was like my stomach
was going to split open!
Oh my, are you okay?
So I'm not able to fool you, huh?
You should all just obediently get devoured!
This means that atypical behavior is indeed
involved with the malevolent gods.
I'm going to devour you right here.
I don't want your undies.
Instead...
I'll have your life.
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
If we don't understand love,
you & I won't get anywhere, you know?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
We wanna share your heart!
(How do you tell me?)
Input sweet nothings
Failed - Cancelled - They don't resonate at all
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch me and bring me one
Successful - Complete - Isn't cutting-edge tech great?
(Hold me tight)
Why won't you say romance?
Let's bring it to love!
Get more experience and level up my maiden heart
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
I'll teach you that love is a maiden's power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Nine times out of ten, they're surely already lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Fluttering in my chest, dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Your shy akuma mind, kiss for you!
Will completely change, kiss for me!
Let's begin our romance!
What attacked Natsuki-chan and the others were akuma
that were possessing and manipulating people.
And that guy's the leader?
This is looking a bit troublesome...
Futaba, how's it going in there?
I just came across Takuma-chan.
I also happened across the enemy mastermind.
Futaba, are you okay on your own?
What? Do you understand who you're worrying about?
Y-you're right, my apologies, Your Majesty!
Next time: The Naked Maiden
Next time: "The Naked Maiden"
Your younger sisters will take care of everything here!
We'll leave Takuma to you!