Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Sagashita amai negai, kyou mo
Kizuite to, watashi no naka kara
Dare ka ga kimi e to sakebu yo
Mitsumeau, modokashii kyori ni
Abaredashita samishisa
Kamishimeru hitori
Suki toiu omoi o
Iitai demo ienai
Itsumo soba ni kimi ga iru no ni
Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Tomoshita tsuyoi omoi
Mayowanai mayoitaku wa nai kara
Shinjite ima, ippo fumidasou
For the sake of myself
You're going to take my life?
Do you understand what's going on here?
Try to take even one step.
I'll cut your lover's head off!
You should go ahead and do it, if you can.
A wall?!
Takuma-chan, now's your chance!
Right!
Don't underestimate me, you sow!
You can't cut through anything you want
with your bare hands!
If I use my hand as a sword,
it's basically the same, you know?
I've separated Takuma-chan from the enemy.
When Takuma-chan finds his way
to Natsuki, we've won!
Did you think you had won or something?
What a shame.
My ability is of the parasitic type,
and it's already been implanted.
I thought I told you...
My fangs have split his stomach open!
I...
I... can... not... die!
I'm sick of this. I don't want... anyone else to die.
Academic
Achievement
Absurd...
That's "Misteltein"!
Why are you looking over there?
I'm the one you're fighting against, aren't I?
What the hell are you all thinking?!
You bestow something like an "Yggdrasil Ea"
upon a meager human?!
Meager human? What are you talking about?
"Misteltein"... The mistletoe's branch
dwells in the body of the owner,
and that hidden treasure of Asgard
super fortifies the ability therein.
Hence, Takuma-chan's own ability
brought him back from death's grip.
Do you think Takuma-chan, who is recognized
by my father, is a meager human?
Spit it out! Does that loser have that sort of ability?!
Come together and get that sow!
This bitch... I can't stop her!
Hey!
Okay.
I don't know what's going on.
Though he's been revived, he's died once!
He should remember it all.
The pain he felt, and the fear that consumed him!
Is she seriously fighting for that loser?!
Japanese & Math
3rd Grade Elementary Review
General Academic Review!
Hey Mom, look at this!
Oh, wow, you got them all correct!
Hey Mom, will you praise me?
But you know, Takuma...
It's okay to go outside and play sometimes.
It's okay, I don't care to do that.
I'll just scare them.
Just watch, Mom. I'm gonna get the next set of
questions one hundred percent right, too!
Takuma...
And also, I heard something on TV the other day.
Right in the midsts!
Academic Society
Annual Salary 10,000,000
I can't believe this suffering
Dead End of Inferior Education
I should have studied more
For those of you who want to realize your dreams,
choose university right now!
This world is generally an academic society!
Statistically, according to lifetime
annual salary measurements,
academics are the key to success!
If I study a lot, get into a good university,
and get a job in a good company,
they said I can be a "respectable person."
If I become a "respectable person,"
do you think I can have friends too someday?
You'll be fine. You're such a kind boy...
You'll certainly have friends one day.
Really?
Come on, have I ever lied to you?
You know, there are tons of things
I want to do when I make friends!
Like study together, and play Tag! And also...
When I get the kind of friends
that aren't scared of being around me, I'll...
Out of my way!
Now's my chance...
He's somewhat taken on the look of a warrior.
2,558 seconds.
That would normally result in severe punishment,
but I suppose this is acceptable.
Don't think that I'll let even a second pass,
from here forward you puppets.
Eldest of the nine Valkyrie sisters,
Valkyria Ichika, Brunhilde,
entering the battle!
Natsuki-san!
Takuma...
S-sorry it took so long.
That took way too long!
I'b sho shorry!
What have you been doing this entire time?!
Er, uh, well...
I'm glad you're safe.
Th-thank you.
Jeez.
We can't afford to waste time.
We're getting out of here!
Oh dear, I suppose this is over now?
So what?!
Don't get cocky, you sow.
You lot don't even come close to
being a match for Svadilfari.
What you're saying is very wrong.
You mean to say if you're not going to win...
then just getting stronger is enough, right?
Nurse's Office
You two can do it...
Val Love, "Embrace without a stitch of clothing on
and kiss deeply for five minutes"!
Okay, let's do this!
Val Love, "Embrace without a stitch of clothing on
and kiss deeply for five minutes"!
Er, l-let's get started.
W-wait! Take a look at us, we're filthy. S-So...
let's wipe each other down until we're clean!
Wh-why?
I already told you that if there's a single fiber
on our bodies then this won't count!
You can't check every nook and cranny
on your own, can you?!
I-I-I'm sorry!
In any case, you're covered in dirt.
I-I'm sorry.
Okay, I'm done with your back.
Turn towards me now.
Huh?! I-It seems I can't...
Right now, the others are
restraining the enemy for us.
We absolutely... positively
cannot fail this Val Love.
So... please!
I-I understand.
U-um...
I-it's okay! I'll take care of it!
I-I'm going to touch you.
I can't believe I'm being tormented by
someone besides Takuma-kun!
Big Sister Mutsumi!
Kururi, stand back.
Sacred Sword, maximum strengthening.
Th-thanks, Yakumo-chan!
Thanks to that can't move anymore, though.
Where's Itsuyo? Where's Itsuyo?!
She's okay. She's with Big Sister Misa.
Pant Gasp
Um... So what's next?
It's my turn next. Hurry up and do it.
O-okay! I'm sorry...
J-just to let you know...
If you try anything funny I'll be pissed!
Right.
She's so cold.
I'm counting on you.
R-right!
Are you okay, Itsuyo?
B-Big Sister Misa!
That was scary! I was so scared!
You're acting like a kid again.
Where did all those posh expressions go?
Huh? N-No, Big Sister! What's this?
Relax, Itsuyo.
Your big sister will save you.
I'm done.
We've finished preparations. Next is...
Natsuki-san?
It's nothing.
Let's start.
O-okay!
Commence Val Love!
I-I'm... going to use my tongue now.
O-okay.
Wait for me, everyone...
I'll come help you, for sure!
Dammit, his breath is...!
Guys, I'm borrowing your clothes!
I-I can't breathe... What's going on?!
Isn't deep kissing supposed to feel good?!
It's totally different from what I read in that book!
Natsuki-san?!
I-I'm fine...
Her body is still cold.
She must be at her physical limit.
She was in the rain fighting and she didn't
stop moving the entire time I was gone.
What do I do? At this rate everyone will...
What should I do?
What do I need to do, as their lover?
A book?
What is this?
My body's warm all of a sudden...
I'm sorry I'm late. I'll defeat that akuma.
I swear, by this blade!
Seventh Valkyrie
"Siegrune"
Blade Lv. 23
Hurray!
Oh man...
The akuma "Svadilfari" will devour everything!
The Sacred Swords are no exception.
What we need to defeat that akuma
are not cheap tricks,
but the single swift blow of
one that will not be possessed.
O Rune, please grant us power.
I doubt you even care for Midgard at all.
You could forgo that useless sense of justice,
but you care so damn much,
you disgrace of a divine being!
Useless sense of justice?
What are you talking about?
I am, simply...
furious that my family has been hurt!
Moreover, as for our leaning towards Midgard,
it's untrue that this place is irrelevant
to the main deities.
"Ragnarok"...
You malevolent gods are gathering aether
for the great war that is to come, yes?
Arrows?
That doggy sure is quick to run away.
Well, results-wise, thanks to you all
Takuma-chan has gotten stronger.
And now the rest of us can also
get much, much stronger.
O Rune, please bring destruction onto our enemies.
We're getting out of here!
O-okay.
Got it!
The stronger Takuma-chan gets,
and the more he becomes a man we yearn for,
the stronger we can become.
After all, love is the source of a maiden's power.
O Rune, please grant us this victory!
Good grief.
So this is what you were bragging about?
Get out of here immediately.
When you get back you will be punished.
Piss off! I can still keep going...
Shut up, you mangey mutt.
You've failed your mission.
Do you want to be disciplined after you're punished?
But, a "book," huh?
A restorative ability that trumps death.
If he gets any stronger than he is now
it may complicate things.
We must watch Einheijer.
Oh my.
What a beautiful sky.
And now for the 99th Hokuou Academy
Joint School Festival Beauty Pageant...
The glorious winner of the beauty pageant is....
Mutsumi Saotome-san!
Thank you, everyone!
Overwhelmingly Defeated
Withdrew
I'm exhausted!
I'd love to dive into a hole right now.
C-congratulations.
Takuma-kun! Let's dance at the party, okay?
Huh? I was supposed to be
dancing with Natsuki, though.
Now that you mention it I never told you!
C-C-C-Craaaaap
With me?
Today was tough.
We were somehow able to drive the enemy back,
but we barely got to do the campus festival date
that we've been waiting for.
This means that we've gotta do
our best at the night festival!
Itsuyo-chan! Natsuki-chan!
Huh? Wh-What's wrong with you two?
Gloom
I can't believe that Inukai-san was
a part of the malevolent gods...
Great work today,
President.
Oh, thanks
And he was such a nice boy, too...
But thinking back on it, he may have been
pretty nosy with his questions...
By the way, President,
what's your ability?
It's the chain!
Be a little more cautious, Itsuyo-chan!
Why are you so down, Natsuki-chan?
Uh, well...
Can I really face Takuma after doing that sort of thing?!
"That sort of thing?!"
What did you do, Natsuki-chan?!
Just as Mutsumi says, we have a unique chance
with the Val Love "Campus Festival Date"!
Ta-daaa
Each of us can be constantly with him the whole time!
Okay, pay attention! Attention!
The main event of the campus festival is
the dance party, so how does this plan sound?
Ahem.
The winner of the beauty pageant
can dance with Takuma at the party!
Wouldn't it be fair in that case?
Y-yeah... I'm okay with that!
I don't even want to do the pa-
Shaddup, Natsuki!
You will become the strongest Valkyrie,
as acknowledged by Father!
To do that... Natsuki! You must be the winner!
The dance party, huh?
No, er...
It's not just that I don't want to go with Natsuki,
but lately people have been getting scarier to me
day by day or something like that,
and uh, it feels even more like I'm gonna get killed
if I'm with such a popular girl like Natsuki-san.
So maybe it'd be better
if I paired up with someone else...
Um, well... We all decided that whoever wins
the beauty pageant gets to dance with you.
B-but...
But I'm sure they didn't tell you, but,
you know, I think that you should...
Are you okay with giving the right you won
fair and square up to Natsuki?
Yeah... It kind of feels like it wasn't fair
and she let me win.
You're honest in a weird way, Mutsumi.
Besides, this is the first time I've been asked
something like this by Takuma, so I'm happy.
Ehaha~
You're quite simple, aren't you?
Y-you're one to talk, Itsuyo-chan!
What's the big idea turning me down once
and then wanting to dance with me?
Err, there's something I'd like to
say to you about that.
Oh?
I can't face Takuma...
Why would he do something like that
and then continue going like normal?!
This insensitive, perverted idiot!
I knew it...
Takuma really couldn't care less about me.
Just a little while ago he was
so lovestruck by Mutsumi and Itsuyo...
Could that be what he wanted
to talk to me about?!
Goodbye forever,
Natsuki-san
I want to date girls
who are stacked
with hot bodies
Like that?!
oh no oh no
Is the dance today my last offering before he leaves?
I feel like that might be possible,
but I also feel like it couldn't...
Natsuki-san!
N-no! I'm still a growing girl!
If you look at Mutsumi and Itsuyo,
my future shows great promise!
So please...
Well, thank you for the other day!
Eh?! Thank you?
I was thinking that you asking me
to dance was an attempt
to help me get over my illness
by being around people.
And it's inexcusable that I made you mad
by refusing to accept after your efforts.
Weak
Um, Natsuki-san?!
No, that was my fault.
That was never one of the many reasons
that I wanted to dance with you.
And you don't have to worry about that.
Th-then why did you want to dance with me?
W-well...
The dance party will start in ten minutes.
All who wish to attend please gather
in the school courtyard.
I guess it's time.
Choke
It's terrifying to think about
just how crowded it will be, but...
no matter what, I'll do my best.
Natsuki-san?
Huh?
I asked you to dance so I can level up, of course!
You dummy!
shock
Uh, is there another akuma around? Where is it?
We were able to safely defeat the enemy this time.
However, they're going to keep coming to attack.
So from here on out...
Will you help me...
Help us, and stay by our side?
Yes.
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Koi o shiranakucha you and I, hajimaranai no yo?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
We wanna share your heart!
(How do you tell me?)
Amai kotoba o input
Shippai - Cancel - Zenzen hibikanai kedo
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch shite todokete yo
Seikou- Complete - Saisentan ga ii darou?
(Hold me tight)
Naze koi to itte kurenai no?
Ai ni yukou
Motto keiken shite level up otome gokoro
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Oshiete ageru wa, koi wa otome no power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Jucchuuhakku kitto mou lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Tokimeku mune dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Akuma de shy na mind kiss for you!
Kaete shimau yo na kiss for me!
Koi o hajimemasho!
The akuma was super strong this time!
Yeah. It would have been bad if Natsuki didn't level up.
Me too! I should get stronger too, right?
With my leveled-up cannon I could
take that akuma down like bla-blam!
Uh... well, you're still little, so you should
leave the combat and stuff to your big sisters!
Then maybe I can help you with an invention!
Next time: "The Reeling Maiden."
Next time: The Reeling Maiden
Big Sister Misa,
is there anything you want me to make?
Maybe a new rice cooker?
Okay, I'll add a super rice boiling mode to it!