Hello, dear sister.
How are you feeling?
Getting kidnapped by the maid you took
such good care of... You poor thing.
Why would you do something like this?
To make my dear brother angry, of course.
Up until now, my brother hasn't
paid any attention to me.
It's was only when I interacted
with you that he looked at me.
When my brother is angry,
his emotions turn toward me.
That realization gave me a sense
of peace deep within my heart.
You want to be closer to your older
brother, don't you, Your Highness?
What?
This is stupid.
I'm going to go play with
my older brother now.
Make sure you behave yourself.
Lady Rishe!
Are you all right?
Please don't worry.
No matter what happens, I
promise I'll protect you.
I promise!
Lady Rishe, I swear I will help you.
Prince Theodore has ordered you
two to do something, hasn't he?
How did you know?
The letter I received from Prince
Theodore the other day...
that was you, Elsie, wasn't it?
You're the only maid here
who is from the slums.
Sir Kamil, you're from there, too.
And for many years, Prince Theodore has
been privately supporting the slums.
Lady Rishe, we've been
ordered to imprison you.
But we've been told to
make sure you aren't hurt.
I see. You can tell me the details later.
For now, we should be on our way.
On our way?
Of course.
I will go and be imprisoned, just
as Prince Theodore has ordered.
What?
This makes me so happy!
To think you'd come all the
way here just to see me!
How many years has it been since
we've spoken this way, dear brother?
Wait, this is the first time!
So, if it's for her sake,
you'll do what I say.
Get to the point.
What I want...
is to be next in line for the throne.
If you want my dear older
sister returned to you,
then renounce your claim to the throne.
If you don't comply, I can't be bothered
to make sure nothing untoward befalls her.
You don't want that to happen, do you?
Your expression seems unconcerned,
but you're worried, aren't you?
You're absolutely beside yourself with worry.
Because that's how important
she is to you, right?
You treasure her!
You show interest and concern for her!
You want to keep her by your side!
Unlike me! You don't even
want to see my face!
I can tell that much, you know?
After all...
I've been watching you all this time.
Come on, Brother. Say it.
Say, "You win."
Say, "This time, you've beaten me."
If you'd just do that...
my life would be complete.
Theodore.
You said that you'd imprisoned her,
but did you put her in a prison?
I put her in a room that's
as good as a prison.
And the door is locked, of course.
Locked, is it? What else?
There are some rough types keeping watch.
The room is on an upper floor,
so she won't be able to escape
out the window.
I see. So, there's a window, too.
What are you trying to say?
No one could possibly escape!
Not normally, no.
Let me warn you, if I
give just one indication,
it will be all too easy
to hurt my dear sister.
My foolish little brother.
There isn't a single path
for you to win here.
Not from the moment you thought
you had captured that girl.
What? Brother, you aren't
acting like yourself.
If you have something to say, then just—
Listen.
Here it comes.
What are you talking—
This can't be real.
I've come to settle things
between us, Prince Theodore.
This isn't possible.
I heard you were being held in
a room "as good as a prison."
Did you leave through the window?
Or, did you do something like
punch a hole through a wall?
I left through the door like a normal person!
Through a locked door being
watched by guards. That's normal?
How did you do it? Has someone betrayed me?
Prince Theodore.
I respectfully offer you
the following advice.
Advice?
First of all...
when you have captured a prisoner...
you must be careful never to
take your eyes off them.
Even if you lock them into
a room by themselves,
leaving them alone is
completely out of the question.
You should always leave at least
two guards in the room with them.
And second...
the search of the prisoner's body should
always be conducted by multiple people.
Don't allow them to keep their clothes on.
Searching them while they are
completely nude is most effective.
That way, they won't be able to
hide weapons or tools for escape.
And third...
after you have shackled their
hands behind their back,
the best thing to do is to tie
them to a pillar or a bed,
but that's still too lenient.
Do you know what the one thing
you absolutely must do is?
Break both their arms and both their legs.
Restrain their broken limbs,
take everything they have,
and have a group guard them.
That's what it means to
take someone prisoner.
Why are you instructing the
person who took you captive?
Your Highness! I'm perfectly all right!
It's fine. You wear it.
But, your neck will be...
What is that scar?
I don't know anything about it.
I knew it. I'm not good enough after all.
Prince Theodore.
Please answer me. What is your aim in this?
To be next in line to the throne.
There's no other reason for two people in
the line of succession to fight, is there?
I don't believe that to be true.
I think it's actually the opposite.
Your objective is to abdicate your place
in the line of succession, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
I couldn't understand
why you would target me.
I told you! It's to make my brother suffer!
If he couldn't protect his fiancée, then
his reputation would be completely destroyed!
Using someone as trivial as
me to steal the throne...
You don't seriously believe
that would work, do you?
By playing out this farce of a kidnapping,
you intended to create a commotion and
disgrace yourself as a criminal, didn't you?
You're wrong.
There was a certain moment at which
you ceased your public works
in the slums, didn't you?
I grew weary of that ludicrous charity work.
That's a lie.
Even very recently, you've been sending
support to the slums, haven't you?
There isn't any evidence
of public funds being used,
so you must be investing your own money.
You worry more for the people
of the slums than anyone else,
and you've approached them with kindness.
But you have deliberately
neglected your public duties.
I just want to beat my brother, that's all.
If that were the case, then you'd
have attacked Prince Arnold directly.
You're wrong.
But you couldn't do that.
That's because everything you do
is for your older brother's sake—
You're wrong!
You're wrong! Wrong, wrong, wrong!
Honestly, what is all this
nonsense you're spouting?
I want my brother to hate me!
To despise me! To cast me out!
If he'll never accept me, then being
killed by him would be so much better!
That's enough. This stops here.
Prince Arnold.
I've told you, Rishe.
Don't interact with him.
Please, wait. Your younger
brother's true feelings are—
I don't care.
Regardless of what his desires may be,
they have nothing to do with me.
I already knew that all too well.
Prince Theodore!
Leave him be.
Why do you intentionally try to
distance yourself from your brother?
I told you. He doesn't matter to me.
If you really felt that way,
then you wouldn't order me to
stay away from him, would you?
You said something the other day.
You said, "The resolve to be my
wife? There's no need for that."
I've been trying all this time to
understand what your words meant.
You are looking at the future
which should be yours
with the intention of throwing
it all away, aren't you?
That's what your younger brother
is afraid of, isn't he?
That's why he puts on an act of being the
second prince with no aspirations to the throne,
of being someone who should disappear
from the future of this empire.
But isn't there some other
path for you two brothers?
Please tell me what you're thinking.
Oh, I see.
And now, I've finally confirmed it.
You're quite adorable.
What are you...
You can't understand my intentions,
so you feel confused, right?
But it's better that you don't understand.
I will say it again, leave Theodore alone.
He should never have gotten
involved with someone like me.
You do adore your brother, don't you?
What?
If you didn't treasure him,
you would never have said
something like that.
Your Highness, have you ever considered a
future opposite to one where you disappear?
Opposite?
One where your brother disappears.
There may be a future like that, too.
Please live your life in a way that you
have no regrets if that does come to pass.
And if I had my wish, I'd do the same.
So that even if this life is my last...
And I intend to live my life
as your wife with no regrets.
Damn it.
This is just about all I have left in me.
But...
I can still remember what
happened on the battlefield.
Hang in there! The medicine
will be here soon!
Thank you.
We're being attacked!
There wasn't anything that someone
as useless as me could do.
I knew that, but I still...
Brother?
As a member of the imperial family,
I can't praise your actions.
Next time, don't do anything
that puts your life at risk.
But the fact that you acted
to protect your vassal...
That's something to be proud of.
Well done.
Prince Theodore.
Are you planning to follow your lecture
on imprisonment with one on escaping?
You weren't planning on
escaping, though, were you?
My brother, you see, never shows his
achievements to the outside world.
On the other hand, his infamy spreads
to other countries unnaturally quickly.
Why do you think that is?
Prince Arnold is intentionally
spreading it himself, isn't he?
I know because I've been
watching him all this time.
I see him and think, "He's acting in a way
that will let him disappear at any moment."
But for a person as wonderful
as him to disappear...
that just isn't right.
If he intends to entrust the
empire to me and disappear,
then I just need to disappear first.
If I do, then my brother won't be
able to do anything stupid anymore.
It's the one and only way that
I can be useful to my brother.
I'm certain that your older brother intends
to do something utterly unreasonable.
Which is why I plan to use
everything I have to stop him.
If there are others whose strengths
I can call on, I will do so.
And, Prince Theodore...
I need your strength, too.
Someone like me will never
be a strength for you.
No, that's not true.
After all...
you are the only little brother he
has in this whole world, aren't you?
I wanted to help my brother one day.
Thank you, Sister.
For you to tell me you need me is
unexpected, but it makes me happy.
But I will decide how I will best be used.
I should have done this a long time ago.
He couldn't possibly!
This was all such a huge failure, wasn't it?
Your Highness!
Brother?
What were you thinking?
But...
But... this is the only way
I can be useful to you.
I have never once done anything
to be a big brother to you.
What kind of idiot risks his
life for someone like that?
The choice your little brother made
may not have been the right one,
but his desire to become a strength
for you isn't wrong, is it?
It's just as she says.
I'll wish this over and over again.
I want to be a strength to you!
I want to be useful to you!
If I can be of help to you,
then I'll do anything!
Because you're my only big
brother in the whole world,
and I look up to you so much!
Never do anything this foolish ever again.
I told you.
Don't ever put your life at risk again.
You remember?
Of course I do.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Big Brother!
I'm sorry, Big Sister!
I'm sorry...
I understand, so stop crying.
But, this is just...
Rishe.
You came for him, didn't you?
Because you said something that bothered me.
I'm glad you two were able to mend things.
I'm so glad...
Rishe?
Sister! What do I do? This is all my fault!
No, it isn't.
What?
She's just sleeping.
You can't be serious. In these circumstances?
Theodore, you have a carriage
at the ready, don't you?
O-Of course I do.
I'll call for it right away.
I'll leave it to you.
"I'll leave it to you," he said.
My big brother. To me.
You're already awake?
Have you stayed with me all this time?
I'm so very sorry!
How are you?
I'm fine now.
Good.
To my sister,
I'm sorry for doing all
those awful things to you.
There are many things I want to say, but
firstly, I promise to repay the debt I owe you.
And you said you'd stop whatever it is that
my brother is trying to do, didn't you?
Given the way things are now,
I'd like to help you with that.
To that end, I'll let you
borrow my people in the slums.
That's what people refer to
as a common front, right?
Come to me for help any time.
With due gratitude to me, of course.
Lastly...
thank you, Big Sister.
You and Prince Theodore
had a talk, didn't you?
Why are you smiling like that?
Because I'm happy, of course.
Think of something else you want.
My promise not to touch you.
I broke it again, didn't I?
I-I don't need anything!
More importantly, the reason why
Your Highness would do such a—
Do you want to know why?
I do not!
Rishe.
What is it now?
Thank you for looking
after my little brother.
Not at all.
He will be my little brother, too, after all.
I see.