Lady Rishe, are you awake?
I'm Prince Arnold's aide, Oliver.
Y-Yes! Just a moment, please!
Thank you for waiting.
My apologies.
This is the only time I could manage
to get away from the prince's office.
Then, you haven't managed any rest?
I'm better off than others are.
Prince Arnold hasn't managed even a nap.
He's been hard-pressed to complete the work
that accumulated while he was away in Hermity.
I feel I should apologize.
Not at all.
The prince said he had no intention to marry,
but through these events,
he's found a lady to be his wife.
Please look as much as you'd like.
Pardon?
You were examining me, weren't you?
My apologies! That was terribly rude of me.
Your insight is just as keen
as the prince said it is.
Master Oliver, your worry for
His Highness truly is heartfelt.
Have you been with him long?
It's been ten years.
If you've served him for that long,
then would you know why he
has decided to marry me?
Well, to be honest, I'm
surprised by it as well.
However, I've never seen the prince so happy.
When he's with you, Lady Rishe,
his smile is so honest and open.
I feel I'm being treated as some sort of toy.
He isn't denying it.
I didn't mean to get
absorbed in conversation.
His Highness asked me to bring you a list of
the honored guests for the wedding ceremony.
Thank you.
Princess Harriet of Siguel.
Duke Jonal will be in attendance
to represent the Kingdom of Domana.
And Prince Kyle of Coyolles...
And this is a list of attendees
for the party tomorrow evening.
The party?
Um, Miss Diana, where do these go?
Go and line them up the way I
showed you yesterday please.
But...
I'm in the middle of something right now.
It's Rishe.
Your Highness, may I have
a moment of your time?
Yes.
Prince Arnold, I've come
to beg something of you.
You did tell me to think
of something, didn't you?
Think of something you want.
My agreement not to lay a finger on you.
This time, I truly did break it.
Would it be possible to leave the
selection of my maids to me?
You can do as you like with that, but...
It seems Oliver didn't tell you.
This party tonight...
It's meant to say, "The crown prince is
looking for someone to marry from the empire."
It's a pointless pretense
held to keep up appearances.
Your Highness,
in this country, I am the crown
princess only as a hostage.
However, I find no dishonor in that.
Please,
feel free to formally reveal
your fiancée at the party.
I suppose I have no choice.
Especially as I've received
your permission to touch you.
Well, we are both wearing gloves after all.
This seems to be a much grander
event than I'd anticipated.
This is still on the smaller side.
The standards of a large
country are different.
Prince Arnold!
I was honored to receive an
invitation to attend this evening!
Thank you for coming.
Your Highness, please tell my
daughter stories of your travels.
Unfortunately, there aren't any points
worth speaking of on their own,
but I did find good fortune on my trip.
As you can see, I've found
someone to be my wife.
Did he say wife?
His Highness is smiling!
But he's never so much as
glanced in our direction!
Then, this beautiful lady is...
Curiosity, jealousy, ulterior motives...
Compared with having my engagement
broken in front of everyone,
this feels like nothing at all.
I am pleased to meet all of you.
My name is Rishe Irmgard Weitzner.
As my future wife has only just arrived from
another country, she has no one to rely on here.
I would like for you to help her.
Of course we will!
"Future wife"? There's no need to
provoke the other ladies that way.
It's better to make it
apparent now, while we can.
Make what apparent?
The fact that I will protect
you, no matter what happens.
Protect?
Did he just say "protect"?
Arnold Hein?
The man who killed me?
Your Highness is probably the
one who is most dangerous to me.
In what sense?
Well, I don't think I could
match you in swordplay.
It might be worthwhile for me to
try sparring with you one day.
I would like that very much!
And I know it's asking a lot, but I'd
love to receive training from you!
You always reply in ways
that exceed my expectations.
I may learn the attack method behind
that fearsome sword technique.
No need to force yourself to dance.
Oh, but as I'm here anyway,
I would like to enjoy myself.
This closeness...
It takes me back to that moment.
Perhaps I'll try playing
a little trick on him.
If I take the lead, what will he do?
Then, what about this?
He looks like he'd like to say, "No
matter what you do, it's no use."
He's so close, but he hasn't
crossed over into my space at all.
Wait...
Now that I think about it, he's been...
No. Back then, too, the whole time, he was...
I'm going to fall!
That was splendid!
The two of you were perfectly
in step with each other!
It was as though I was
watching a sword dance!
Lady Rishe?
Your dance earlier was quite lovely.
Thank you.
If you'd like, please accept this wine.
Thank you, I will.
That's the aroma of crushed red peppers.
To think they'd play pranks with food.
This wine has an unusually striking aroma.
It's quite intriguing.
Are you displeased with
the wine I've brought you?
As I thought, it has a
very stimulating flavor.
It makes me very happy to have
been welcomed in such a way.
Let's go.
That's spicy.
Spicy?
Your Highness.
This wine has peppers in
it. It's a special blend.
You should just throw that away.
No. This wine has lost its chance
to be enjoyed for its flavor.
The least I can do for it is to drink it all.
What? Wait!
Spicy indeed.
I did say so, didn't I?
Has this fulfilled your duty to this wine?
Yes.
Thank you.
What were you thinking
about during our dance?
What?
You were thinking of someone
other than me, weren't you?
I can't tell him it was his future self.
I was worried for your health, Your Highness.
This spot...
You've been wounded there, haven't you?
The movement of his left shoulder is
slightly clumsier than that of his right.
It was back then, too.
It's an old wound.
It runs all the way along
the top of my shoulder.
There's a spot where it
slightly constricts my skin.
How horrible.
It's a very old scar.
He was struck with a blade over
and over... with killing intent.
Only a few people know about this scar.
And no one has ever guessed at its existence.
Why do you have a scar like this?
The night wind has grown colder.
Do you think the lady's
maids will be chosen soon?
Yes.
But with the way things are,
we probably won't be chosen.
Haven't you finished yet?
I-I'm sorry, Miss Diana!
I'm sorry.
And those sheets this morning
weren't folded the way I taught you.
With skills like that, you'll never be
chosen as the crown princess's maids.
I'll help you.
You again?
I don't know which group you belong to,
but I'm amazed that you have
the time to help others.
And all of you, finish that up quickly.
It seems that the tablecloths
for the villa will arrive today.
If we help with that, I'm certain
we'll be valued more highly.
Let's go. Maya? Laura?
Yes.
I'm sorry. We're just so
bad at remembering things.
You haven't been at the
palace very long, have you?
No one gets everything
right in the beginning.
And it isn't that Elsie and the
others are unused to doing laundry.
They're completing their work. It's
just taking longer, that's all.
In that, Diana is right.
But the cause of it is very clear.
Have you heard anything about Miss
Diana's life from before she came here?
I think I heard that she's from a
wealthy family that has several shops.
I've heard that, too.
But they lost it all because
they went into debt.
I see.
It's sparklingly clean.
When did that happen?
I wonder who did the cleaning here.
And that girl who always turns
up uninvited isn't here, is she?
An upstart newcomer like her?
Of course she wouldn't be here.
Indeed. To serve the crown princess,
manners are absolutely essential.
My heart's pounding. Is yours?
Yes.
What do you think the crown princess is like?
Lady Rishe is here.
I am Rishe Irmgard Weitzner.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to learn the truth
about your situations,
and I thought that speaking to you as a
fellow maid was the best way to do it.
Now, I will read off some names.
Miss Marguerite.
Miss Elsie.
Miss Nichole.
Miss Rosa.
Miss Hilde.
Miss Amelia.
These people will be my maids.
What?
I look forward to getting to know you better.
Now, everyone whose names
have been called, come to—
But why, Lady Rishe?
Everyone you've chosen is new!
We have more experience as maids!
Disrespectful.
It's all right.
Yes, what I am saying is disrespectful!
But please look at our
abilities as maids!
Miss Diana.
Yes?
As of today, you will no longer
hold the position of maid.
What?
But that's...
Say, Diana? When you
first came to the palace,
can you remember what you
had the most trouble with?
Were you able to complete your work the
way you do now right from the start?
No. In the beginning...
it was difficult for me to
understand how things were done.
I couldn't remember after
being told only once.
But everyone who had been
there longer was so busy.
They'd say, "I don't have time to
teach you, so watch and remember."
Even so, I've grown into a
very competent maid!
I'm not like those girls!
You're right. There is one way in which
you are very different from those girls.
What?
You can read and write.
You were born into a merchant's family
and received a good education,
but there are very few ordinary people
who have had the same sort of education.
You could write down what those with more
experience told you and read it again later.
But what if you hadn't been able do that?
Go and line them up the way I
showed you yesterday please.
But...
And those sheets this morning
weren't folded the way I taught you.
When my family went bankrupt, we lost
everything. There was no one to protect me.
Even so, I made myself into a lady's maid.
I kept wondering, why
couldn't all of you do it?
But it's because I didn't teach you properly.
I'm sorry.
I was the one in the wrong.
I'm really so very sorry.
Lady Rishe, Miss Diana is very skilled,
and she always works her hardest!
Please don't make her quit.
Thank you, but it only makes
sense that I wasn't chosen.
Miss Diana...
There's something I'd like to ask of you.
I'd like to make this villa into
a training ground for new maids.
While they're learning household skills,
I'd also like them to learn their letters.
If they learn to read and
write along with their work,
wherever they go, whatever their situation,
it will be an asset to them.
Even if they find they must begin a whole
new life, it's sure to prove useful.
Diana, I'd like for you to help me
create their teaching materials.
Me?
Even though I said all of
those disrespectful things?
Why, whatever could you be speaking of?
Will you help me?
Yes, it would be my pleasure.
I see.
Is it as you predicted?
Of course not.
Though I did think she'd
create some sort of havoc.
Showing your amusement too openly is
disrespectful toward your future wife.
Though, I may end up
enjoying myself as well...
wondering what sorts of things she
will accomplish in this country.
Oliver.
I didn't bring Rishe here to be my wife to
benefit the imperial family or the nation.
As for the first words they'll learn, what
do you think about cleaning implements?
Since they're used every day,
I thought everyone might be able to
see how useful it is to memorize them.
Yes, I think that's a very good idea.
Thank you.
Lady Rishe...
Thinking of the best ways to
teach everyone is so much fun!
I'm glad to hear that.
Excuse me.
Lady Rishe, you must get ready soon.
Yes.
Then, I'll take my leave here.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, Miss Diana? After dinner,
will you help me study some more?
Of course.
Thank you.
What a lovely dress.
It's the most valuable one I have.
Will you help me put up my
hair in a style to match?
Yes, my lady.
Um, I've heard that your guest is a merchant.
Is your most valuable dress really necessary?
Well, it's one potential ingredient, you see?
Ingredient?
After all, these are the people who drilled
what it is to be a merchant into me.
If I can gain them as allies, then my choices
moving forward increase dramatically.
The Aria Trading Company has
only just been established.
A business negotiation with the
imperial family of Galkhein...
that's something they should want
to be successful, no matter what.
Would dressing more gaudily make me seem
more like a mark who loves to spend money?
I think it's a shame.
Putting your hair in a bun with some
trailing tendrils would give you a refined air.
I feel it would match this dress better.
Thank you, Elsie.
But this outfit is for my battle today.
Battle?
Your guest has arrived.
Allow me to congratulate you
on your upcoming nuptials.
I am Kaine Tully, from
the Aria Trading Company.