I apologize for my sudden discourtesy.
I have something I wish to ask of you.
Would you please...
do me the honor of becoming my wife?
What? Your wife?
Yes.
Me, become your wife?
That's right.
I respectfully decline.
Why?
Why is he laughing like
he's really enjoying this?
Th-The Crown Prince of Galkhein
proposed marriage to Rishe?!
The man who killed me is proposing to me?
It doesn't make sense. I don't
understand what his aims are.
It's the king!
Why is the king here?
Your Majesty!
Father!
Why would you come all this way—
Your Majesty?
F-Father! The stones...
Prince Arnold, my idiot son has
shown you unthinkable rudeness!
The stones are digging into my face!
F-Father, I, um...
Lady Rishe, I truly apologize for
the matter of the broken engagement.
M-My beautiful face is going
to be full of stones...
I offer you my heartfelt apologies.
I believe you have heard
Prince Arnold's intentions,
but I ask it of you as well.
They're going to leave scars.
This trifling matter will cause no discord
in the friendship between our nations.
But if at all possible, I would ask
for some time to speak with her.
P-Please go with him, Lady Rishe.
Ow!
Should you refuse, I will simply
proceed to the next tactic.
What exactly are you plotting?
Nothing.
I've fallen completely in
love with you, that's all.
Fallen in...
With your engagement broken, you no longer
have anyone backing you, correct?
He's right. In my first life, I
would have leaped at this chance.
But as I am now... I know that
life holds infinite opportunities.
Still...
The Savage Emperor. The Invader.
In all of the lives I've lived,
he's instigated a war.
Why would he do such a thing?
If I stay by his side,
will I learn the reason?
You say that you've fallen in love with me.
That's why I proposed marriage.
Then will you agree to a few
selfish requests of mine?
If it lies within my power, I swear that
I shall make your every wish come true.
First, everything needed
for the marriage ceremony
will be procured through the
trading company that I specify.
As you like.
After we are married, please provide a space
where I may receive guests from other countries.
As the wife of the crown prince, you would
be asked to do such things in any case.
I would prefer to live
separately from the emperor.
If it's for you, I would do anything.
Lastly, I have one more very important point.
I will absolutely laze around the castle!
I will loaf about, idle my days
away, and do no work at all!
Oh. Additionally, I request that you
lay not a single finger on me, please.
What do you mean to do with that hand?
You promised, didn't you? I asked you
not to lay a single finger on me.
Don't regard me with such contempt.
I was simply trying to retrieve
that which you took from me.
I'm so terribly sorry!
Slumped over with a sword for support...
I'm amazed you could sleep like that.
To think that I used the sword that
impaled me in place of a pillow...
It's incredible that you sensed
me without my touching you.
To reach such a level, you
must have trained quite a lot.
Y-Yes, I did.
I've invited the trading company
you selected for a meeting.
Thank you.
The Aria Trading Company.
There's been talk of that company lately.
Do you patronize them regularly?
No. I've simply heard that
they procure very fine goods.
I want to interact with them as
soon as possible in this life, too.
The devastating power of
incredibly good looks...
What is it?
Oh! It's nothi—
Stop the horses!
Enemy attack!
Um, I—
You stay here and behave.
There are knights here. Why
would he go to fight himself?
He told me to behave, but...
Finished already?
And when I took the trouble
to face you by myself, too.
This didn't even serve to stave off boredom.
Arrest the brigands.
Those with nothing else
to do, see to the wounded.
Sir!
He hasn't killed them.
Not a single one of them.
What's wrong, Kamil?
Hurry!
Are you all right? Hey!
Is something wrong?
My body... feels numb.
Poison, is it?
Tie off a spot between the wound and the heart immediately, then suck the poison out.
Sir!
A scent like that of an overripe apple...
This is an anesthetic made of shea
grass and bluecap rock mushrooms.
It's likely something that
hunters in this area use.
While it won't be fatal, the effect
will last for several days.
It will take another two
days to reach Galkhein.
If we look after them as we travel, then...
We passed a hunting settlement along the way.
We'll return there and procure the antidote.
Excuse me.
I can make an antidote.
What?
It's lucky that I'm able to make
this with the plants I have on hand.
It's actually more effective if it's boiled,
but as haste is needed here, let's use this.
Could it be that they're suspicious of me?
Hey!
What are you doing?
It's all right. Please don't worry.
This antidote is made of liquori grass
and luqua flowers with some carilya nuts.
Please, make your decision. Will
you use this medicine right now,
or will you endure that numbness
for the next few days?
Right, Your Highness?
I'm glad that nothing terrible happened.
That aside, for what purpose do you
suppose that you have guards with you?
Rather than sustaining losses by having
knights fight off the battlefield,
stepping in myself better protects
our national interests.
And we did, in fact, sustain casualties.
You say that with the benefit of hindsight.
And the fact that you brought
Lady Rishe out here with you...
That was not my doing.
So, the flowers weren't simply to
look at, they were for practical use.
How did you get out of the carriage?
It's a secret.
In my life as a maid,
my lady would often lock
herself in her rooms,
and every time, I'd have to unlock the doors.
Is he a child staring at a line of ants?
Is there something on your mind?
I have no hidden purpose. I was simply
thinking that you are unfathomable.
What means will you use
to entertain me next?
I'm beside myself with anticipation.
He speaks of me as though
I'm some rare beast.
I'm not doing this for
Your Highness' amusement.
I know.
One of the knights you pressured
into your threat-like choice
is someone who once lived in the slums.
Galkhein extols itself as a meritocracy,
but there are many who are unfairly
judged due to their origins.
Even so, he has never caved
to outside pressures.
He worked hard and became a knight.
The knight with the worst case of numbness
hasn't been assigned here for very long.
He trained himself night and day
for the sake of this mission.
The older knight was trying to protect that
newer knight and was injured alongside him.
He's a man who excels
at looking after others.
You know quite a lot about the knights.
Because I've chosen all
of them as my retainers.
I thank you for saving them.
I don't understand anything anymore.
Is this a false face of his?
Or is it...
I simply made use of
knowledge I happen to have.
A noble lady who happens to have knowledge
of herbalism? There can't be many of those.
Now that I think of it, why
were the knights so wary of me?
They heard that you are a lady
whose engagement has been broken.
They've likely wondered what
sort of villainess I'm marrying
and have all sorts of notions.
I see.
Then, what did you say when you told
His Majesty the Emperor about me?
"She's from a ducal house with
connections to the royal family,"
"and was fiancée to the crown prince."
"She's taken my fancy, so I've stolen
her." That's what I told him.
Stolen?
Because the empress must be from the
royal family of another country.
You mean... a hostage.
In Galkhein, there may be those
who behave rudely toward you.
If the worst happens, I will—
But that's splendid!
What is?
If I'm treated as a hostage, then I won't
be brought out for official duties, will I?
Well, I suppose not.
Wonderful! That means I might
actually be able to laze around!
Thank you, Your Highness!
It's nothing.
Oh, and while I'm thinking of it, you were
about to take my hand earlier, weren't you?
That was unavoidable.
A promise is a promise.
Possessing fertile land
and abundant resources,
Galkhein influences every
nation in the world.
In all of my previous lives,
it is the only country I've never visited.
So this is the imperial capital!
Is something the matter?
Preparations of the imperial
villa have been delayed.
I'm sorry, but today you'll be
staying in a room for noble guests.
There's no need for such considerations.
I will be quite happy in the villa.
It hasn't been used in a long
time. It's in a terrible state.
I don't mind.
Besides, I...
am a hostage!
Why do you seem proud of that?
This place certainly hasn't been used in
quite some time. There's so much dust.
Now then...
Shall we begin?
The maid in me
finds this quite exciting!
Excuse me, Lady Rishe?
Is there anything that we might help with?
I couldn't possibly ask my guards to clean.
Then, at least allow us
to carry in the furniture.
Thank you so much!
A few years from now, Arnold Hein
will kill his father, the emperor.
Then, the war will begin.
There may not be much point to it,
but I'd like to keep him
away from his father.
Why did he wage war against the world?
In all of my lives, the cause of my death
has always been connected to
the war started by Arnold Hein.
I am firmly opposed to war!
If only it weren't for that war!
And here's to a long life spent lazing around comfortably and without care!
Are you seeing this?
The novice is working so hard.
No matter how hard you try, it won't work!
We'll be chosen to be Her Highness
the Crown Princess' maids.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I haven't seen you before.
She must be new. Look at
how pretty her hands are.
Unfortunately for you, the only ones
capable of serving the crown princess
are us, with our three years of
experience working in the palace.
Can you stand?
Hey!
Listen when we're speaking to you.
If you intend to work as a lady's maid,
learn to respect those with more experience.
Those curtains. It would be better
not to start washing them now.
What?
The days are long in the spring.
There's enough time for them to dry.
There will be a little rain later.
What makes you so certain?
The type of clouds. The
birds are flying low, too.
If you wash large articles now,
it might make more work later.
Nothing a novice like you says
could possibly be accurate.
Enough of this. Let's go.
This nice weather is definitely
going to last all day.
Are you hurt anywhere?
No.
Thank you... very much.
My name is Elsie. Thank you for saving me.
That's gotten dirty, hasn't it...
And when they were kind enough
to provide me with it, too.
It will be all right if
we wash it right away.
What?
I did say that it would rain,
but that fabric dries quickly.
Mud gets deep between the threads,
so please try tapping at it
with this brush to wash it.
Who are you?
Come! We have to hurry
before it starts raining!
Traveling to see every
country in the world...
That was the dream I had
when I was a merchant.
In lifetime after lifetime, I
tried to fulfill that dream,
but it never came true.
And now, the one country I
was never able to visit...
I've finally managed to make it here!
Should you really be doing this?
Slipping away in the middle
of your official duties?
Truly, you surprise me every time we meet.
I've suppressed my presence.
To think that you could
sense me at such a distance.
That wasn't kind of you.
I know you adjusted the strength of your
presence, testing to see when I would notice.
What were you looking at?
The city.
What's that large building over there?
A library.
Books gathered from every other country
are held there for safekeeping.
Every country?
And that beautiful little tower over there?
A church.
It also serves as a clock tower.
Its bells ring at appointed times.
Oh, how lovely!
And there's a large marketplace
over there, isn't there?
It's the largest shopping street
in the imperial capital.
The stalls there handle wares that
they receive just that morning.
How splendid!
Then, Your Highness, what
about that pretty—
Wh-What is it?
I was wondering what you
find so entertaining.
You were pressured into a marriage
to one of this country's royals.
Would it really inspire such curiosity?
It's something I've longed for.
Longed for?
I've wanted to come to this
country for a very long time.
The final push that made
me agree to the marriage
might have been the admiration
that I've felt for this country.
This country doesn't possess anything
worth your admiration or longing.
That's not true.
Even in the information you just gave me...
There are so many fascinating places here!
And the faces of people in town shine
so brightly! And there's also—
Have I said something strange?
I've never seen a person like you before.
The substance of your statements, your
knowledge, your physical ability...
A simple nobleman's daughter would
have no need of such things.
You've been born to a duke's family.
Your personal feelings are unnecessary.
But, Mother!
Your happiness lies in marrying into
the royal family and bearing an heir.
There are things I wish to learn!
If you have enough knowledge to maintain
appearances in social situations, that is enough.
Focus on the homemaking arts,
not academic study.
Even if others may deem
such things unnecessary,
I treasure every single one of them.
They are riches which I will never lose,
and each is a precious piece of my life.
Whether something has
value or not in my life...
I will decide that for myself!
I know.
You should do whatever you
wish, without constraints.
I swear to support you in your wishes
and continue to assist you.
Why?
I told you.
I've fallen completely in love with you.
Lies, as usual.
And these immeasurable abilities of yours...
I don't find them pointless. I find them
delightful, from the bottom of my heart.
I thought I'd conveyed
that much to you at least.
Think of something you want.
My agreement not to lay a finger on you.
This time, I truly did break it.
I can't read him at all!
Arnold Hein...
what are you plotting?