Thank you.
I heard that Sir Kamil and
Elsie won't receive punishment.
It's nothing to thank me for.
While I'm thinking of it, I heard that
the policies for improving the slums
are going to move forward under
your leadership, Prince Theodore.
My brother asked me if I wanted to do it.
Then, does that mean the both of you
will be attending to official matters?
Well, I suppose it does.
Now, you didn't take the trouble to
come here just to say that, did you?
Actually, I have a favor to ask of you.
What?
This is something which will be
essential for your brother as well.
What do I do? I have no idea
what my sister-in-law is saying.
Please, Prince Theodore.
The preparations are complete.
I'll be off now.
Yes, my lady!
An official letter from the
Kingdom of Coyolles has arrived.
Come in.
How are you faring, Prince Arnold?
Thank you for granting me your
time in spite of how busy you are.
What sort of business brings you here?
You seem too tense to have come
simply to see your fiancé's face.
A room has been prepared for you
at the villa, Your Highness.
What?
If you have the time, may I
show you the room now?
Why would this errand make you so nervous?
My maids have worked
eagerly and diligently on it.
It's almost like a graduation exam for them.
However, I can confidently assert that the
room they've prepared is quite lovely.
I had thought it was your wish
to live in that villa alone.
Of course not!
I want to live there with you, Prince Arnold.
I see.
It seems you're plotting
something amusing yet again.
You make me sound awful!
Very well.
I'll go along with your scheme.
Thanks to you, my mood has improved.
Your mood?
Let's go.
Thank you.
This is your private bedroom, Your Highness.
What do you think? It's a
splendid room, isn't it?
Very impressive.
This villa has been left
abandoned for many years.
You've been here a mere three weeks.
To think you've already
improved it this much.
Thank you!
You taught the novices starting
with the basics, didn't you?
Yes. Once they've learned a trade, they'll
be able to make their living anywhere.
And they'll gain something else, too.
Pride.
When they accomplish their work
and earn the praise of another,
it will give them a sense of pride.
That sort of pride can help a person
make the most of themselves.
You have a talent for giving
people a sense of self-respect.
That's the expression you
make when I compliment you?
You're teasing me, aren't you?
It may not seem like it,
but it's heartfelt praise.
Well, it's just too bad for you.
Even if it's a lie, receiving a compliment
from you makes me very happy.
Out of the whole villa, this
room gets the best light.
The wind feels wonderful
when you open the window,
so it's perfect for an afternoon
nap, don't you think?
I never return to my chambers during the day.
This room is next to yours, isn't it?
Yes. I thought that would
make it easier for the guards.
And for me.
What?
Because I'll get wind of your
reckless behavior beforehand.
I'm planning to spend my time lazing about,
so I won't be doing anything reckless.
Not much, anyway.
Idiot.
You're free to do what you want,
but don't do anything as reckless
as you did the other day.
I'm very sorry.
Speaking of which, do you remember what we
talked about at the party the other evening?
What do you mean?
When you said that you wanted
to try sparring with me.
It might be worthwhile for me to
try sparring with you one day.
I would like that very much!
Yes, we did say that.
Just once would be enough.
Would you instruct me?
Teach me using the special training methods
Your Highness and the imperial knights use.
What makes you say that they're special?
Since coming to this palace, I've watched
everyone train a number of times,
but Your Highness' and the imperial knights'
movement is clearly different from the rest.
All right.
What? Are you sure?
I did promise to do anything
you wished, after all.
Oh, um... Thank you.
That makes me incredibly happy.
Happy?
As far as I know, your sword work is the
most beautiful, most powerful in all the world.
In all the world, huh?
Th-That's just a turn of phrase, of course!
A skill that's only meant for killing
people can't possibly be beautiful.
Your Highness...
I'll head to the practice
grounds ahead of you.
Change into some clothes
that you can move in.
Is this how you always practice?
Not always.
Once you've acquired an incorrect habit,
it's too late to do anything about it.
The arm and leg restraints are meant to
help closely mimic battlefield conditions,
so that you can continue to fight
even if you've lost a limb.
That's what this training is for, isn't it?
As usual, your observations are impressive.
Even if my arm is ripped off,
I'll keep swinging my sword.
Even if my leg is shattered,
I'll continue to advance.
And even if I should lose both my eyes,
I'll keep looking, to the very last,
for a path to cut down my enemy.
Doing that will lead to
a way for me to survive.
I've heard that a knight's path
pursues nobility and beauty.
However, they will find a way to survive, no
matter how unsightly their struggles may be.
It's to survive that they kill their enemies.
That way of thinking comes from
Your Highness, doesn't it?
It's no wonder I was no match for him.
Don't worry.
I have no intention of injuring an opponent
who's preparing for their marriage ceremony.
If I win, will you give me an answer
to one question, no matter what it is?
In exchange, if I lose, I'll grant one wish
of Your Highness', no matter what it may be.
Very well.
Then, if you would.
Begin!
The longer our exchange of blows lasts,
the greater my disadvantage.
A frontal attack!
What's wrong? Is that all you've got?
My center of balance is unstable.
My instincts are trying to make me move
the way I do when I can use my left arm.
If I adjust my center of
balance... my reach will change.
I'll have to step in closer!
Your movement's dulled!
Don't rely on strength alone!
Your footwork is growing careless!
Make use of your nimbleness.
Step in farther!
Another step.
Still not there.
You see?
He really is impressive.
In this short exchange of blows,
he's telling me exactly what
points I need to improve upon.
It's only been a little while since Lady
Rishe crossed swords with His Highness, but...
You're right. In the blink of an eye,
her movements have already improved.
Next, he'll come from above!
The same move as back then.
But even if I understand what's
happening, my body can't keep up.
Earlier, you said that my sword
was the most powerful, didn't you?
But that movement just now was that of
someone who knows of a person stronger than me.
Even as you're sparring with me, you're
thinking of that person, aren't you?
How enviable.
I'm on the verge of becoming jealous.
You jest.
As I told you, you are the strongest
person I know, Prince Arnold.
It's true. The prince of five years in the
future was even stronger than he is now.
He was cruel and overwhelmingly formidable.
Come at me.
Focus on me a just little more.
I'm not done yet!
Very impressive.
I wasn't planning on moving a single step.
It seems you limited yourself
quite a bit for my sake.
Though it appears I greatly
underestimated you.
Thank you for your instruction.
You'll do any one thing
I want, is that right?
Yes. Ask whatever you like of me.
I won't go back on my word.
Then, clear your afternoon
for two days from now.
We're going into town.
Into town? To do what?
I'll tell you when the time comes.
What's wrong? Stand up.
Um...
I'm going to stay like this a little longer.
Please go ahead and return without me.
Why?
The truth is... due to our sparring just
now, my arms and legs are shaking.
What?
It seems my body wasn't able to keep up.
So I'm going to rest a little.
Your Highness?
I'll only be touching you through my
gloves, so it won't be a problem, right?
What?
What? Wait, Your Highness!
Stop struggling. You'll fall.
Um, it's just that this is...
You can't stand, right?
I can stand! I will stand!
Please put me down!
I can't go back and just leave
my fiancée behind, can I?
That may be true, but...
While I'm thinking of it,
what did you want to ask me?
What?
You said that if you won, I'd have
to answer one question, right?
Do you really think I
can ask you like this?
You're laughing?
I knew it! You're having fun
watching my reactions, aren't you?
Am I?
Then, when is your birthday?
The 28th day of the 12th month.
Oh, so you were born in the winter!
Next, what are your interests?
I don't have any in particular.
What sorts of things do
you like, Your Highness?
I've never really thought about it.
What type of woman do you prefer?
And what are you planning
to gain by asking that?
Master Oliver.
Well, well. Lady Rishe.
Are you moving the office now?
Yes. Thank you for preparing such
a wonderful room for His Highness.
Not at all.
By the way, where is the prince?
Actually, last night he suddenly had
to take command of the night watch,
so he hasn't slept yet.
What?
I've implored him to take a nap, but
he has his official duties to perform.
He doesn't show any signs of resting.
Please rest, Your Highness.
Oliver said something unnecessary, didn't he?
Staying up all night
will take its toll on your body.
I won't be able to sleep anyway.
During the day, I can feel all sorts
of people's presences in the palace.
All right.
Then I shall lull you
to sleep, Prince Arnold.
What?
Now then, I will stay by your side,
so please don't worry, just rest.
Sometimes you say things
that make no sense at all.
If I'm here, I don't think you'll
be distracted by far off presences.
You're right about that.
Then please, get some rest.
This doesn't seem to be working.
May I lie by your side?
Pardon the intrusion.
What are you doing?
Imitating a heartbeat like this is a
technique for calming the heart and mind.
In my life as a maid, I
often used to do this for my lady.
If you do this for a young child,
they'll quickly fall asleep.
A young child?
You're probably the only person
who would treat me like that.
If you're curious about
it, do whatever you like.
Stop that.
You really...
I-I'm sorry. That must have tickled.
If we were going to do this,
then I should have worn gloves.
If I had, then I could
have made a counter-stroke.
It isn't as though touching me with gloves
or through cloth makes it all right!
It was a joke.
His Highness is so sincere
and oddly conscientious.
While I, on the other hand...
Please go ahead.
And do what?
I felt I wasn't being fair.
If it would make Your Highness feel better,
then you should touch me
and have your reven—
Are you doing this on purpose?
Honestly, Your Highness!
For my revenge... I'll show mercy and
settle for that expression of yours.
You're a strange one.
You think nothing of sleeping beside me,
but meeting my eyes when we're
this close unsettles you.
I wanted to put a charm on you.
A charm?
This palace isn't a battlefield.
It's Your Highness' home, isn't it?
That's why I hoped you would feel even a
little more at ease so that you could sleep.
Then stay here until I fall asleep.
It's far more pleasant than an empty room.
All right.
You're awake?
Your Highness...
Prince Arnold, why are you here?
Don't you remember climbing
into this bed yourself?
W-Were you able to sleep?
That's the first thing you want to know?
In any case, I do beg your pardon.
I'll leave your room right
away. Please don't worry.
Wait.
Huh?
Wha—
Excuse me, Your Highness!
Stay quiet for just a little while.
Come in.
What's wrong?
We've received reports. Were you sleeping?
Lady Rishe spoke to you, then.
If you're able to spend time
comfortably in your new chambers,
then that's wonderful.
Keep it brief. I'll listen to it here.
As you command.
Then, I'll go back to work.
Please be sure to rest thoroughly.
Stop nagging.
I understand, so hurry up and go away.
Yes, of course.
Well then, good night.
It's all right now.
I-I know.
I know, but...
Welcome back, Lady Rishe.
Thank you, Elsie.
A package has arrived from
the Aria Trading Company.
Thank you.
Starting tomorrow, I'm going to be very busy.
That will be the ten day training schedule
for all of you knight candidates.
I have high hopes for your progress.
Yes, sir!