You're falling behind, Lucius!
Sir!
Please, Prince Theodore.
Don't you think you're
making use of me in the wrong way?
You said you want to join the knight
candidates' training as a man, right?
I'm not sure that's a good idea.
Why should I help you?
You sent me a letter the
other day, didn't you?
It said I could rely on your help.
Yes, I wrote that! I wrote that, but...
But why do you need to
sneak in to begin with?
You could just have a knight
assigned to instruct you.
If I did that, they'd surely
try to be considerate of me,
and I want to be trained without any mercy.
Unbelievable. To think you'd willingly
choose to go and be treated harshly.
I could never do it.
Hold on.
Your Highness?
Very well! I shall assist
my lovely older sister.
I will exert every effort
to make your wish come true.
Um, why the sudden change?
Well, it seems entertaining, doesn't it?
I think that even my older brother
would never be able to anticipate it.
Who'd ever think, "My wife is going to
dress as a man to infiltrate the knights"?
How could I not take the opportunity
to surprise my brother like this?
It isn't as though I'm doing this
to shock Prince Arnold, you know.
I would love to see the look
on my brother's face, whatever it is.
That's enough for today! Dismissed!
Thank you, sir!
This is Galkhein's basic training?
Are you all right, Lucius?
Fritz. Thanks, but I'll be all
right after I rest a little.
I'll join you.
Even if I head back to the
inn, I'll just be alone.
Inn?
I came here from Ceutena.
Have you heard of it? It's
a port town in the north.
That's where ships from
Coyolles dock, isn't it?
Yes, it's a great town.
If I didn't look up to that person so much,
I'd never have aimed to be a knight, and I'd
probably have lived my whole life in that town.
That person?
Prince Arnold!
The war hero!
Master of the sword!
He's just so amazing, don't you think?
Yes...
I want to become a great knight,
just like Prince Arnold.
You there.
You mustn't refer to members of the
imperial family in that manner.
You must be careful to call him
His Highness, the crown prince.
Y-Yes, sir!
As long as you understand.
Raise your heads.
You're... Count Lawvine!
His Lordship, Count Lawvine?
He's the guardian of the north and a loyal
retainer to the Galkhein imperial family.
But three years from now,
Prince Arnold, who will have become emperor,
will declare him a monstrous
criminal, and he'll be slaughtered.
H-Has he noticed
I'm only dressed as a ma—
Do you like to eat chicken?
Huh?
Y-Yes, I do!
I see. In that case, you
should eat more of it.
From what I can see, you have less
muscle mass than the average man.
Y-Yes, sir!
Starting tomorrow, I will
be joining your instructors.
I look forward to working with you.
What?
Your Lordship, it's nearly time for your
audience with His Majesty, the emperor.
Yes, I'll go immediately.
If you'll excuse me.
Thank you, sir!
Elsie, I'm back.
Welcome home.
Prince Arnold.
Good morning.
Were you able to sleep last night?
Yes.
Your Highness?
Tomorrow afternoon at two,
come to the western back gate.
Don't let anyone see you.
Should I dye my hair?
No, that isn't necessary.
I see. Then, I will arrive in clothes
that will look natural in town.
Um, Lady Rishe?
Yes?
Why were you speaking
secretly with Prince Arnold?
The truth is that the prince and
I are going into town tomorrow.
What sort of business is taking you there?
I'm certain it must be some
sort of official business.
It would be best to wear
something that won't stand out.
A brown linen dress and a
simple gray robe would—
Lady Rishe!
Please leave it to me.
What?
L-Leave what to you?
I promise I will make you lovelier
than anyone else ever could.
What?
Now that we've made it this
far, we should be all right.
You can lower your hood.
Don't worry. None of the
citizens here know your face.
Th-That's true.
I know exactly what you want to say!
I had guessed that this must
be official business...
but being dressed too plainly
would stand out, too!
Since it's you, I thought you'd come
in a linen dress and plain robe.
Am I really that predictable?
Is this your maid's doing?
Those clothes pose no problems.
Truly?
I must give your maid my highest praise.
Let's go.
What?
Please wait for me!
The marketplace!
It's just a marketplace,
the kind you'd find anywhere.
That's not true!
Those are Coquito's famous grapes!
Those are rare saloof bird eggs!
And could those be—
A-A marketplace does, of course, show
the current economic conditions,
but it also reflects the public
peace of the surrounding areas.
A pocket watch?
Your Highness? Is there something over there?
You want to see the marketplace, don't you?
Thank you!
What do you think? These are fresh berries!
These are a specialty from Coyolles!
They've just come in from Ceutena!
Young lady, I'll give you a discount!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Wait.
What is that disquieting object?
A fruit from Coyolles.
It looks a little unusual, but it's very
nutritious, so it's good for the body.
I said, wait. No matter how I think
about it, that appearance is—
It's good for the body.
How do you like it? It's sweeter
than it looks, I think.
It tastes like it's nutritious.
My, what a bitter expression!
We should get moving.
If we stay in one place for too long,
Oliver's deputies will find us.
He isn't executing official duties today?
The proprietor here doesn't
come to the palace.
Thanks to that, it becomes
necessary for me to come here.
We've been awaiting your arrival.
To be employed by Your Highness, the
crown prince, brings us great joy and—
No need for speeches. Raise your heads.
It's an honor to meet you.
I'm the proprietor of this
store, Mihaela Laure Wehrmann.
Pleased to meet you. My name
is Rishe Irmgard Weitzner.
How beautiful!
We are humble jewelers.
Lady Rishe, among these stones,
which do you think is a fake?
What?
Rishe.
Try answering her.
I don't know.
What a clear answer.
Being able to answer so
honestly is a wonderful—
So, Madam Proprietor,
may I borrow some appraisal tools?
Pardon me?
Each one has a high degree of transparency,
and the cuts are very fine.
However...
These stones...
all three of them are
imitations, aren't they?
I failed to recognize your skills.
You are the first to request appraisal tools.
That said, they truly are beautiful.
Even knowing that they are imitations,
I'm sure there must be many people
who love and care for these stones.
You are...
I find myself admiring you more and more.
What? Oh, but I haven't done
anything to warrant it!
Our merchandise in this store
is only sold to a select few.
I would very much like to show you our wares.
If you've approved of her, then
give her exactly what she wishes.
Yes, we will ready our wares with pleasure.
What? What is going on here?
I thought I was accompanying Your Highness
to fulfill your wishes, wasn't I?
The one thing I wish from you...
is for you to allow me to
gift you a ring. That's all.
What? A ring?
His Highness, the crown prince,
seeks a ring to give to his bride
during the wedding ceremony.
Now, I will prepare a few things and return.
Ring? Bride?
Why? For what purpose?
In Galkhein, a ring shouldn't be necessary.
But more importantly...
How did our sparring
match lead you to this conclusion?
If I said, "I'll buy you a
ring, so pick what you'd like,"
I can't imagine that you'd
quietly make your choice.
You wouldn't accept others buying
things to give to you, would you?
The stones they have here are first-class.
I have no intention of letting
money be an obstacle.
But, Your Highness, I don't think that
I can readily accept such a valuable—
If you have a ring made here,
then my idle wealth, which I have no
means of using, will fall to the town.
It will help the economy.
I see. In that case...
I shall make my choice!
With utmost sincerity and
with everything I have in me!
The ring will be put on me
during the wedding,
so maybe a diamond would be best?
Or, perhaps, to match my eyes... an emerald?
I ask out of solicitude, but
may I offer a suggestion?
Yes, please do.
Putting on a favorite piece of
jewelry and wearing it proudly...
Just that simple action can
fill a girl with courage.
This will become your very
own protective amulet.
Pick something you genuinely like.
For example, Lady Rishe,
what color do you like?
What color do I like?
Like crystal clear ice from a
frozen sea in a cold country...
That sort of color...
Do you have a stone here that
is the same color as his eyes?
Wait...
Oh, my! My, my!
No, it isn't like that!
What I just said didn't
carry any unusual meaning!
I really have no hidden purpose,
it's only that I've always liked
the color of Prince Arnold's eyes,
and thought that it's pretty, that's all!
You've always thought that, have you?
If you'll wait just a moment please.
I have something I'd like
to recommend to you.
Madam Proprietor!
Please, forget what just happened here.
Oh, this beautiful sunset
is illuminating the palace!
Why the third finger of your left hand?
What?
When they measured your ring size, you
indicated that finger, didn't you?
I suppose you say it's a
notion I've always had.
Putting a ring on the third finger
of the left hand during the wedding
is the custom in the country I was born in.
But, Your Highness, why did you
decide to give me a ring at all?
No particular reason. And the fact that
it's a ring holds no specific meaning.
But you often work with
your hands, don't you?
To have an ornament I gave
you on those fingers...
I was certain that it
would make me feel good.
That's...
Then, the morning that it's finished...
I'll show you before anyone else.
Good.
Could it be?
Come to think of it, I heard
that Count Lawvine had arrived.
Whose guest is he?
I called him here.
He's the best qualified person to
instruct the knight candidates.
Your Highness...
who are you waiting for in this place?
That's quite an abrupt question.
Count Lawvine protects a
very important location.
I can't imagine that you'd call him
here simply to train the recruits.
And what made you think that
I'm waiting for someone?
Your Highness frequently
checked your pocket watch.
I thought that you were concerned about
what time to return to the palace,
but since we arrived here, you
haven't once taken out your watch.
Additionally, this is a spot where one
can observe people entering the capital.
The other day, a letter
arrived from another country.
It said that the sender wouldn't
be able to attend the wedding,
so they would come to celebrate in advance.
Before I could send a reply to say that
wouldn't be necessary, another letter arrived.
It said that they wanted to
celebrate as soon as possible,
so they'd leave without awaiting a reply.
At the marketplace, someone was selling
fruit that had just arrived from Coyolles.
The sender of the letter
was on that same ship?
Given the information from my scouts and
the time it takes a carriage to travel...
Weitzner,
I want to protect this kingdom.
Prince Kyle...
Earlier, Kyle had an audience
with His Majesty, my father,
and he was given permission to stay.
As I thought, he must have a
particular aim in coming here.
The Prince of Coyolles, His Highness Kyle
Morgan Cleverly, is here to see you.
I congratulate you on the occasion
of your marriage, Prince Arnold.
I, Kyle Morgan Cleverly, representing
my father, King of Coyolles,
hastened here to in hopes
of celebrating the event.
You have taken many pains
to travel all this way.
For that I offer my heartfelt gratitude.
There is a great difference in strength
between this empire and Coyolles.
Coyolles is a country which
produces gems, gold, and silver.
They're wealthy, but...
for most of the year, they're
virtually cut off by snow.
For food and other necessities of daily life
they must depend upon trade with
their neighboring countries.
And five years from now,
they are destroyed in the war
that Prince Arnold instigates.
Rishe.
Yes, Prince Arnold?
This is Rishe, who will be my wife.
I'm honored to meet you.
My name is Rishe Irmgard Weitzner.
I am extraordinarily delighted to meet you.
I knew that anyone who would become Prince
Arnold's wife must surely be a magnificent lady...
but I never imagined anyone
of such a caliber as yourself.
You are a warm, beautiful goddess.
I am undeserving of such words, Prince Kyle.
More important than these
empty social pleasantries...
Even the gold which my
kingdom is so proud of,
Prince Kyle has far too
little color in his face!
is no match for the brilliance
emanating from you, Lady Rishe.
Even flowers at the height of their
beauty, blooming in profusion,
His skin is already pale to begin
with, but he looks nearly blue now!
would feel shamed in your presence.
Did you learn something?
I can't quite grasp it.
Everything he said was innocuous.
He didn't show even a sliver
of his true intentions.
What?
Then, earlier, the look you had, like you
were about to kill with your gaze...
What was that?
More importantly, Kyle seems to have brought
a number of academics from Coyolles.
What?
Your color has improved tremendously, Kyle.
It couldn't be.
If you want to hear what they have
to say, too, I'll make arrangements.
I would be happy to!
Actually, I've heard that
Prince Kyle is very weak,
and I have a medicine
I'd like for him to try!
If the scholars he has
with him will permit it,
then there won't be any need
to slip the drug into his food!
That was a joke.
It didn't sound like a joke.
First, tomorrow there will be a welcome
feast for him, though it will be a bother.
Of course. I will have the preparations made.
I'll have Kyle and Lawvine
meet face-to-face there.
Whatever Kyle might be plotting,
that should serve to keep him in check.
Hey, why are you making that expression?
Oh, it's nothing!
If Count Lawvine comes to the
party tomorrow evening...
the fact that I'm Lucius will be revealed!