There is no value in a country
that has lost all its power.
When a nation's collapse
is only a matter of time,
the only question is how
to deal the final blow.
I have a request to make of you, Prince Kyle.
Won't you first form a
modest alliance with me?
In order to avoid a future in
which Coyolles is destroyed,
I've formed an alliance with Prince Kyle.
However...
If it were Arnold Hein, then I have the
feeling that he'd use it quite effectively...
this compound I've created,
which I call black powder.
Professor Michel's aim is to find out
how large an effect black
powder will have on the world.
To achieve that end, the professor
will surely point out black
powder's power to Prince Arnold.
I must find a way to stop the professor's
experiment, no matter what it takes.
These are leto fireflies.
They're so beautiful!
G-Good evening.
Indeed.
What are these?
They're fireflies.
Fireflies.
If you wish for them to be
exterminated, I'll give the order.
What? Why?
If they're fireflies, then
they're bugs, aren't they?
Yes, they are bugs, but you mustn't
thoughtlessly exterminate them.
All animals, humans included, are
part of one large cycle, you see.
Besides...
You see? They're so beautiful!
Yes, indeed.
What a strange feeling.
All of the things I'm worried about
stem from His Highness, and yet...
Somehow they all seem to be flying
toward Your Highness, don't they?
Then you should just come over here.
I suppose you're right.
This much would probably be...
Hey. You wouldn't—
Prince Arnold...
I, um...
If I startled you, I'm sorry.
But I, um...
You do know, don't you?
I can jump a distance like
that with no problems.
Yes. After all, you can jump down
to the ground from a palace balcony.
Then, why...
Even though I know, I moved
reflexively. I couldn't help it.
Thank you.
You do realize that you could have gone out
into the hallway and come through the door?
Through the door?
Through the door.
You're right!
The way you cut across via the shortest
route is just like that other time.
Whatever could you mean?
By the way, why do you have your sword?
I mistook the light of the
fireflies for torches.
Now that he mentions it,
their light does resemble the
torches you see on a battlefield.
Memories of the war are vividly,
deeply embedded within him.
They truly are...
such beautiful eyes.
These eyes are the same color as my father's.
They serve as proof that I carry the
same blood as my father, the emperor.
When I was a child, I very much
wanted to gouge both of my eyes out.
Your Highness...
They aren't something you
should gaze at in that manner.
There is a deep hostility between Prince
Arnold and his father which seems boundless.
The day you first came to this palace, you
said you had an admiration for this country.
I am unable to feel admiration
in the same way that you do.
The light of fireflies looks
like the fires of war...
and looking down from here,
the view of the capital is infuriating to me.
Perhaps it's because of these eyes
I've inherited from my father,
or perhaps it's because of my nature...
Either way, it doesn't change the
fact that it's repulsive to me.
Lights seen from far away might look like
wartime fires or like firefly lights.
The values inherent to such a perception
aren't inherited from one's parents,
they are gained through all the
things a person has experienced.
In which case, you just need to learn.
Learn about the beauty of this nation and
the magnificent things that live in it.
In the future yet to come, you
can do that as much as you like.
I have no need of such things.
As long as there are things I can use
to achieve my aims, that's enough.
Your Highness...
I've even killed people I
held dear with my own hands.
Even you. If you ever become an
impediment, I'll discard you.
On the matter of Coyolles, I don't
know what you might be thinking,
but don't make me have to get rid of you.
I can't promise you that.
Should I become your wife, I will
still move to achieve my own aims.
Even if that means you cast me aside.
However...
when that happens, I'll
simply return here again.
What?
Even if you cast me aside and
declare our engagement broken,
I'll interview to become a maid
and return to this palace.
If that doesn't work, I'll dress
as a man and become a knight.
And if that doesn't work,
I'll come as an herbalist.
I'll acquire whatever skills seem like
they'll let me slip back into the palace,
and I'll come to see you again and again.
So please, don't worry.
I won't stand by and allow you
to get rid of me, Your Highness.
To me, these eyes are
your eyes, Prince Arnold.
Even if you, yourself, detest them,
I want to tell you this
over and over again...
I think your eyes are the most
beautiful in all the world.
It's late. Go and rest.
Good night.
Yes.
When I was a child, I very much
wanted to gouge both of my eyes out.
Please look these over.
Coyolles' techniques truly are splendid!
Thank you.
And the finely powdered metals you
requested are right here.
To be honest, I'm surprised.
Even the trading company I patronize
has difficulty obtaining all of these.
We've formed an alliance.
Naturally, I should
do everything in my power.
Thank you.
You feel that way because
you've built honest relationships
with so many traders, Prince Kyle.
I've managed to obtain an appointment to
speak with Prince Arnold one more time.
But will this really be
enough to convince him?
I don't know.
But I'm confident it will be
enough to entice him to listen.
How can you say that with such certainty?
It is, of course,
because I am Prince Arnold's future wife!
Wh-What is this?
What's going...
Thank you for granting me your time today.
I will say this in advance.
I have no intention of having
the same conversation again.
I still feel that there is no value
in an alliance with Coyolles.
I understand your position.
However...
I assume you've brought a
somewhat worthwhile proposal?
Of course, Your Highness.
I can't allow myself to be daunted.
This is a negotiation. It's a battle.
You sit, too. Let's begin.
Before that, Your Highness...
can you tell exactly how I differ
from my usual self today?
Earrings. Bracelet.
Necklaces.
None of them are familiar to me.
You've never worn them
with me before, have you?
It's just as you say.
All of these pieces are
jewelry made in Coyolles.
In addition to producing metals and gems,
my kingdom is cut off by
snow for over half the year.
Given the aforementioned conditions,
we have advanced the craft of jewelry
making, which can be done indoors,
and we have cultivated
many brilliant artisans.
Even those items, which other countries
have difficulty producing,
can be completed quickly
and exquisitely by our artisans.
We in Coyolles stand proudly before the
entire world and say that this is our treasure.
I will make a declaration here...
You recognize this item, don't you?
Well, it does belong to me.
What of it?
This is—
Wait.
It can't be. I never imagined
that you would notice.
This isn't the piece that
Your Highness lent to me.
It is a reproduction of that watch.
Prince Arnold, your watch is here.
We borrowed jewelers' equipment
and were able to cast all of the parts.
The one who created this reproduction
was a jeweler from Coyolles.
Intricate metalworking was used
to create the gears and screws.
As my kingdom's artisan has accurately
reproduced the piece,
we are now able to repair it as well.
Prince Arnold, you are already aware of the
magnificence of this ware called a watch.
These watches are rare in the world,
but have you never wished you could
possess them in large numbers?
Or perhaps you've imagined turning the
skills used to produce them to other uses?
Research into technologies which might use
gears and clockwork has already begun.
Carriages that can move
even without horses...
Ships that can sail even without wind...
In the not-so-distant future,
people may dream of such things.
However, when that time comes,
the only country with the skills to make
those dreams a reality will be Coyolles.
And, Prince Arnold...
I'm certain that you will want them.
You will want to bring their
technical prowess to Galkhein!
Is that all?
Kyle Morgan Cleverly.
What are you trying to do here?
I acknowledge that the skills your
country possesses are exceptional.
It is something which my nation lacks.
Which is why, all the more, I
find your naïvety revolting.
There is no need to form an alliance
to obtain another country's technology.
Because everything can be taken
through military force, you see?
Did you come here without a single thought?
Did you simply do as my future wife said...
and come here as ornamental royalty?
Rishe, you're no better.
Say that I obtained this technology.
Did you never imagine
what I might use it for?
Using metalworking technologies
as a piece in negotiations...
When this was suggested to me,
I thought you might not be pleased by it.
However, Lady Rishe believed.
"The power to make the future
a more wonderful place..."
"It isn't possible that Prince
Arnold won't want that," she said.
I, too, came to this country because
of my belief in you, Prince Arnold.
You are an outstanding ruler.
And during the war, you showed even
enemy nations a form of respect.
The reality is that you're kind enough to
be here, like this, in discussions with me.
That is a naïve way of thinking.
My foolishness lies in thinking to
rely on you, to have you protect us.
But my decision, the thought that I
wanted to form an alliance with you,
I don't believe that that was a mistake!
The intellectual power
of Coyolles' scholars...
and our metalworking technologies...
If we continue to research these
two things together with your country,
then this future that Lady Rishe
speaks of won't be simply a dream!
If it will gain your trust,
I will spare nothing.
I'm terribly sorry to interrupt
your conversation, Prince Arnold.
I hope you are doing well, Prince Kyle.
I offer my deepest apologies for my
rudeness in disturbing your conversation.
Brother, I am very sorry to interrupt.
An emergency?
I'm terribly sorry. I will excuse
myself here for a moment.
L-Lady Rishe?
I'm really very sorry.
If you'll excuse me!
Everyone I had shadowing the
target was given the slip.
We were last certain of his
whereabouts three hours ago.
He was in a back street in Section 17.
What was the situation when
they lost sight of him?
Apparently, there was
some sort of sweet smell.
When they woke, the target's
whereabouts were unknown.
Which means that the surveillance
of Michel Hévin has failed.
Well, that seemed hurried.
I offer my apologies as well for my future
wife and younger brother's rudeness.
Not at all. If we could continue—
Oliver.
Prince Arnold.
What is all this?
Prince Theodore.
I know.
Just as you thought, that man
was carrying a large bag.
I've already mobilized
everyone in from the slums.
They're looking into the contents.
Thank you.
But there is one thing that's bothering me.
Prince Arnold.
Yes.
I may be the second prince,
but that isn't enough to allow
me to barge into a meeting of his.
And he didn't seem at all surprised.
Sister!
We know where that man is.
Professor!
Hey there, Rishe.