Allow me to congratulate you
on your upcoming nuptials.
I am Kaine Tully, from
the Aria Trading Company.
I'm Rishe Irmgard Weitzner.
Thank you for coming such
a long way to meet with me.
This really is a lovely
time of year, isn't it?
He's as impressive as I remember.
Just meeting his eye makes me
feel like he's seen through me.
Lady Rishe, did you say your wedding will
be in the middle of the eighth month?
But since I know him well, I
should have the upper hand.
That means you'll become a
bride under the summer skies.
To have such a beautiful lady as
the future mother of the country...
In order to avoid the war,
and to live a long life,
I must say I'm jealous of
the people of Galkhein.
I will have you lend me your aid, chief!
I'm sure you've already heard, but
I want everything used in my wedding
to be procured by the Aria Trading Company.
Well, well! You have no idea how
much I appreciate such a statement.
Then, would it be possible
to see your wares right now?
Lady Rishe...
I haven't a single item I would sell to you.
Oh, pardon me. It seems you've misunderstood.
However, it's just as I said.
A lady such as yourself simply
cannot become a customer of ours.
May I ask why?
The items which we are able to procure
aren't in keeping with your level of resolve.
Resolve?
It seems that, for some reason, you're
staking your life on this transaction.
I've seen many different people in my time,
but you seem to have a stronger
resolve than any of them.
This despite the fact that you're only
buying wedding goods from a simple trader, you see?
Well, it is a once-in-a-lifetime event.
I've allowed myself to
become overenthusiastic.
I'm so inexperienced.
It's quite embarrassing.
Please, rest at ease. I'm certain your
wedding ceremony will be splendid.
However, unfortunately, our wares
seem to be inadequate to the task.
Thank you for your offer. It's been an honor.
Ch-Chief Tully!
All else aside, Galkhein is quite
an impressive country, isn't it?
We're thinking of forgetting our work for a
while and spending a few days enjoying the sights.
Please wait! If we could
speak a little longer!
Farewell, beautiful future crown princess.
Listen well, Rishe.
Become a merchant who can pick her customers.
Offer wares or other value that
they can only get through us.
When you do that, then we're the
ones who can choose our customers.
I couldn't make the chief choose me.
But I'll need his connections when the Aria
Trading Company spreads across the world.
Um, Lady Rishe?
Why is the future crown
princess working in a garden?
Prince Arnold gave me this plot, so
I thought I'd grow medicinal plants.
Depending on how I mix them, I'll be
able to make all sorts of medicines.
I see...
Still, was he simply being wary of me?
He is a cautious man, but he also
loves an all-or-nothing gamble.
Have I overlooked something?
We're thinking of forgetting our work for a
while and spending a few days enjoying the sights.
That's the end of my
gardening this afternoon.
A-Already?
I'm going to rest in my room. I'll
leave guarding the halls to you.
Y-Yes, my lady!
Still, are you sure about this, chief?
You're kicking aside a way to make
huge money from the crown princess.
You dummy. If we took that lady on
as a customer, we'd see heavy losses.
Welcome back, Chief Tully.
I can't drink any more.
You win, miss.
I did think you might deign
to visit us soon, but this?
Then, that was an invitation after all.
I'm honored.
I'm astounded.
To think you'd outdrink
my men while you waited.
Since they're such enjoyable company,
the drink just kept flowing.
Setting that aside, that dye has
taken quite beautifully to your hair.
My hair color tends to
stand out a bit, you see.
If I told you I'd sell you the method,
would you be open to negotiations with me?
I would never!
After all, you've brought something
even more lucrative, haven't you?
And now, just as you wished,
we will begin our negotiations.
Let's start with a drink.
Just one thing first.
While we're here, please speak freely.
When he speaks so formally to
me, it sets me off-balance.
Well, if you insist.
So, milady, no more of this "I want a
dress for my wedding" charade, all right?
Of course. It's obvious that trying
such tricks on you won't work.
Good.
My intuition is telling me something.
Lady Rishe, it says that I should take you
on not as a client, but as a trading partner.
I won't help with a plan
if I don't know the full scope of it.
But don't worry, despite appearances,
I'm very dedicated to my work.
I can promise you whatever profits, no,
even greater profits than you've imagined.
Now, how about you spill every last detail
of this money-making scheme of yours!
I can't tell you.
What?
I can't tell you about my plan.
Even so, I want the Aria Trading
Company to become my ally.
You say the most interesting things, milady.
You want me to enter into a contract
without being told anything,
and it isn't even certain
that I'll profit from it.
This is the type of offer
that traders hate the most.
I will, of course, prepare compensation.
You're telling me to just trust you when
you say I'll make a profit? A fine idea!
Within the next few years,
the crown prince of this nation
will wage wars on other countries,
and I'm formulating a plan to stop him... but
it's not as though I can tell him that.
Listen well, milady,
I trust my intuition a great deal,
but what I regard as even more
important is results and—
Results and proof of performance, right?
I will think of a business which will
prove successful here in the capital.
If you deem me worthy of
your trust because of it,
then may I ask that you reevaluate
this decision at that time?
I like it!
You're saying that if your idea
seems likely to turn a profit,
you want me to acknowledge you.
That's exactly the sort of thing I like.
Yes, I know that very well.
You have a week. I'm looking
forward to this, milady.
Then it's a promise.
Thank you for your time.
And when everyone wakes, please
have them drink this medicine.
What is it?
I think you'll understand
quickly once you use it.
It isn't a simple thing to
sneak out of this place.
You were out late.
Your Highness, why are you here?
I heard that your offer
of trade was turned down.
It's a strange story.
A simple trader rejecting a request
from a future crown princess?
I'm the one who said to
spend your time as you like.
That's why I believe it would be
unreasonable of me to criticize your actions,
so I awaited your return instead. However...
So, even you look like that
when faced with a man alone at night.
I... am very sorry.
Sneaking out of the villa alone at night is
unbecoming of my position as your fiancée.
If your reputation were damaged because—
I don't care about that.
You're not hurt, are you?
What?
No, I'm not.
From now on, whenever you visit
town, I will go with you.
What?
I told you. You're free to do as you like.
I also told you that I
would help you in that.
Oh, but... I couldn't possibly ask Your
Highness to go along with my selfish behavior!
I said that you're free to do as you like.
I didn't say you're free
to put yourself in danger.
What is it?
You're much too indulgent with me.
Well, as it's you,
if I try to restrict you by saying that
you're never allowed to visit town again,
you'd just slip out quietly
again, wouldn't you?
Even if it meant dyeing your hair.
Giving permission with conditions attached
seems more likely to work as a restraint.
Am I really so easily understood?
Not at all.
You're the type that's so difficult to
understand that I can't predict you at all.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
You and the chief both.
The chief?
What has passed between you
and the Aria Trading Company?
Your Highness?
Yes?
Do you happen to be hungry?
Um, Y-Your Highness?
There's something I must apologize for.
What is it?
I'm terribly sorry, even though
I'm the one who proposed it...
I, um...
I'm a terrible cook!
I see.
I'm very sorry.
Well, it's unusual to find a noble
lady who has experience cooking.
In my past lives, meals were just a time
when I prioritized putting food in my stomach.
I don't think this soup will
suit your tastes, Your Highness.
It's good.
What?
This soup will do just fine.
I don't think he can tell
good flavors from bad.
Hey.
You're thinking something
disrespectful, aren't you?
No, not at all!
Thank you.
It's your fault that I'm hungry.
Let's hurry up and set out the dishes.
Of course!
Which is why...
I now have to propose a new
business idea within a week.
I understand.
Which means?
I said I understand.
I comprehend what it is you want to do.
You're not going to ask me what I plan
to use the Aria Trading Company for?
You kept that a secret from the
trading company, didn't you?
Then, I can't imagine that you'd tell me.
It's just as you say, but...
Have you figured out this business
or whatever you're thinking up?
I have several ideas.
It's just that I don't know
if any of them will work.
What kinds of people live in the capital?
What sorts of things do they love?
There's a mountain of
things I need to research.
You're saying this will be a difficult fight.
Yes.
You really are enjoying this, aren't you?
You should do as you like.
I have to get back.
Yes, of course. Good night.
Is something wrong?
Have you met my younger brother?
Your Highness's younger brother? No.
That's good.
If he approaches you, don't entertain him.
Is there something I should know?
There's no need for you to know.
This town's population,
its male to female ratio,
and its age distribution are
the minimum information I need.
Changes in its economic development...
the state of the surrounding regions...
information on traders and travelers
entering and leaving, too...
I garden in the morning, check
teaching materials in the afternoon,
and I have to prepare for the
wedding ceremony as well.
I won't be getting any
sleep or rest for a while!
A midnight snack? You, my lord?
What of it?
Nothing.
Lady Rishe must be an excellent cook.
She said she's terrible at cooking...
but it was good.
Hey.
Is adding medicinal herbs
to soup a standard practice?
To soup?
No, that isn't usually done.
I see.
Were you unable to get much rest last night?
I was doing a little research.
Please don't push yourself too hard.
Lady Rishe! Please stand back!
Let's return to your room.
Black hair is rare on this continent.
Lady Rishe!
Rishe?
Oh no!
You are my older brother's...
Pleased to meet you, my lovely older sister!
Finally, we meet!
I've sent so many letters
saying I wanted to meet you,
but my brother hasn't sent a single reply.
Isn't that just mean?
There's no need to be so tense.
I'm Theodore.
Theodore Auguste Hein.
I'm second in line to the throne
and Arnold Hein's younger brother.
I've been told not to spend
time with him, but...
I'm honored to meet you.
My name is Rishe Irmgard Weitzner.
A twist of fate has allowed me to fill the
lowest position in the imperial family.
I hope that we will get on well together.
I was wondering, what are you
doing out here, dear sister?
This garden plot is one that I've created.
You made this?
That's amazing!
It's rare to find a bed so fluffy!
But there is one thing bothering me.
Will you look here for me?
Is something the matter?
See? Right here.
Well...
I want to save you.
You poor thing. Dragged all
the way to a place like this.
You aren't truly a bride. You're a hostage.
I'm aware.
You are?
Prince Arnold is more than
satisfactorily considerate toward me.
I see.
I'm glad I was able to meet
you today! I'll see you again.
Second in line to the throne?
That's not something you say as an
introduction to your older brother's fiancée.
This may seem apropos of nothing,
but earlier, you didn't
seem your usual selves.
Do you have orders not to let
me near his younger brother?
That isn't something we
would be able to tell you.
Then, do the brothers get along well?
We can't speak to that either.
I'm sorry for asking such strange questions.
Not at all.
I'll have to deal with
this matter eventually,
but right now, my negotiation
with the chief comes first.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Our military force will be
turned to the protection of the people.
The decision has already been made.
Ignoring the regional lords in order to
tenderheartedly protect the commoners?
What's the meaning of this?
The nobility has their private armies, and
the nation provides the funds to maintain them.
You can say whatever you like.
Your Highness, please reconsider!
I can't say that your father
will be pleased by this order.
I will not argue with you. Know your place.
Um...
I'll have separate notices sent to the lords.
Notices?
Our protecting the people just needs to
end up being in their favor, correct?
If our forces are turned to protecting the
people and they are able to live in safety,
that will ultimately lead to increased tax
revenue which should benefit the lords.
If that's the case, then the lords
will likely accept the change.
This conversation is over.
The indemnities gained through war
are invested locally in revitalization
and creating employment.
This policy was created by Arnold Hein.
He is forcefully introducing
policies which benefit the people.
He really is very different from the
impressions I have of him from my past lives.
Well then, good night.
Good night, my lady.
I will confide a secret to
you. Be at the chapel
tonight at twelve.
Arnold Hein
Good evening,
Prince Theodore.
my lovely older sister.