Good evening, Prince Theodore.
Good evening, my lovely older sister.
Impressive.
From your demeanor, I take
it you knew it would be me?
If you would like to speak,
I ask that it be brief.
Continuing from this morning,
you don't know my older brother
very well yet, do you?
So I'll tell you about him.
My older brother thinks
nothing of killing people.
That's the kind of person he is.
I know that.
Arnold Hein committed massacres
in other countries...
and invaded every nation in the world.
And, of course, I'm not
speaking of times of war.
What do you mean?
You see, my brother...
killed his own mother.
A horrifying story, isn't it?
Striking down his own mother?
There's nothing decent about that, is there?
And one day, you'll be killed, too.
Is there something wrong with that?
For my part...
I am fully aware of the facts, and I
choose to become Prince Arnold's bride.
Did you hear what I said?
I'm not surprised.
He's the person who will one day kill
his father and usurp the throne.
You don't understand anything!
My brother is a heartless man
who neither cries nor bleeds!
It seems our talk is at an end. You should
continue this conversation with your brother.
Brother...
Why is my brother here?
This is a misunderstanding! What I said
just now isn't what I really think!
It's all a misunderstanding!
Theodore.
I believe I ordered you
to stay away from Rishe.
I'm sorry, brother.
Let's go, Rishe.
Please wait, Your Highness. Speak with
your brother for a moment or two.
There's no need.
But...
Rishe.
Yes, Your Highness.
It truly is just as I thought, my sister.
I'm really sorry, brother.
I won't say anything mean
to your dear bride any more.
Good night.
It's been a while since I've seen you
up close like this. It made me happy.
And I believe I told you as well.
Since your name was used to call me here,
Prince Arnold, I couldn't simply ignore it.
Though, I did take a bit of
a gamble on your coming here.
I received a reply to a letter I never sent.
Thank you for your
invitation. I will go to
the chapel alone at
half-past twelve as
specified.
I would have been crazy to sit
back and relax after that.
Thank you for coming for me.
What's wrong?
Why do people say you're a cruel person?
Probably because it's the truth.
In the last war, Your
Highness took many lives,
but from what I've seen of you in this
country, you are a considerate, kind person.
It seems I've looked after you too well.
If you wish to survive in this palace,
discard that naïve mindset immediately.
I trust what I've seen.
You've never seen me on the battlefield.
You don't know what you're saying.
The person who has shown me such care and
consideration was also undeniably you, wasn't it?
Don't be ridiculous.
I brought you here to use you.
Even so, I can't think of
you as a cruel person...
my husband.
What is this resolve you carry within you?
Resolve?
I see it in your eyes sometimes.
They're the eyes of someone
standing on a battlefield.
"If it means that I can stay true to my
convictions, then I don't care if I die here."
You have the eyes of someone
with that sort of resolve.
Even then, you haven't given up on surviving.
You will fight until the very last.
The moments when I had
to kill such a person...
were the most terrifying moments of the war.
He has things that frighten him, too?
I have dreams where I am killed.
When I wake, I know that
I'm alive, here and now.
But sometimes, I feel very afraid.
Afraid?
I worry that the truth is I've died
and that the world I'm living in now
is just a long dream I'm
having after my death.
I didn't realize I had
these feelings inside me.
Pay it no mind. What does
it matter if I'm scared?
Even so, I've made up my mind.
No matter how this life may
end, I don't want to run away.
What I carry within me now is the
resolve to live as your wife.
No more than that.
You fool.
The resolve to be my wife?
There's no need for that.
What was that yesterday?
And...
The resolve to be my wife?
There's no need for that.
What did those words mean?
Lady Rishe, did you not
sleep again last night?
Elsie.
You've been working too
hard the past few days.
I'm all right. No need to worry.
I say that, but I think I've
finally reached my limits.
So sparkly and smooth...
This is the merchandise I'm
proposing to Chief Tully.
And what perfect timing!
Will you sit there for me?
In the east, they have a custom of staining
their nails with dyes made from flowers.
I used that as a hint and tried adding
color to nail-strengthening medicine.
I thought that this way, you could enjoy
being stylish even while scrubbing and washing.
This will make my nails stronger?
Mine always split right away.
This should make them less likely to split.
But the most important thing
is to eat meat or fish.
Meat. Fish.
I'll remember that.
From now on, I'll be able
to use my pay to get some.
Elsie, if I remember
correctly, your family is...
Yes, my family is poor.
It's all I can do to feed my
younger brother and sister.
So this nation has a deeply
rooted poverty problem, too.
There are households like Elsie's here.
It's so beautiful.
I've never seen anything so sparkly.
Elsie, do you have a favorite color?
I'd like to give you a present.
I-I couldn't possibly!
If I accepted something
as wonderful as this...
I believe I should restrain myself.
Not at all! Elsie, your using
this would make me happy, too.
What color would you like?
Any color would suit you very
well. Won't you tell me?
Elsie?
Wh-What's wrong? Does something hurt?
I'm... happy.
I don't know how to thank you.
I'm just... so very happy.
Elsie.
My family is very poor, and our
clothes are always in tatters.
We could never dress fashionably.
And now, I've not only become
your maid, Lady Rishe,
I'm to be given something so beautiful...
I'm just so happy!
That's amazing! It's so pretty!
There are other girls in this
country doing what Elsie did,
suppressing their own longings and
dreams for the sake of their families.
That's right.
Right now, I'm not a merchant.
Right now, I am...
Most of the people coming in and out of the
capital are working men in their prime.
So, I thought this would
make the perfect souvenir.
And it's a small bottle,
so it won't be unwieldy.
Magnificent!
What genius conceived of these wares?
I'm certain that many women will want it.
Please allow our trading
company to handle the sales.
All right! Let's start promoting
it to our clients right away!
Now, just wait.
If this product were
entrusted to us right now,
we'd sell it as a highly priced
product intended for nobles.
But it seems that Lady
Rishe has a different idea.
Yes. This is where our
business discussion begins.
Three years ago, Prince Arnold established
a minimum wage in this country.
I see. So, that policy
was the crown prince's?
However, this boon is granted only to
those who can find employment, I believe.
Yes.
This item isn't costly or difficult to make.
However, it will require a lot of
manpower to create large amounts.
I have a suggestion in that area.
Please allow me to hear it.
Large scale hiring from the slums.
If you promise me that this will
be done, and only if you promise,
then I will provide you the
technique to create this item.
What a magnificent idea!
However...
I'm disappointed in you, Miss Rishe.
Kaine Tully, how dare you be so insolent!
It's all right.
If you wish to perform charitable acts,
please feel free to wait until I change
professions and become a clergyman.
Chief, this is a business proposal.
After the war, Galkhein created a number
of policies to benefit its people.
And thanks to those, people's income increased,
and their lives became more extravagant?
Yes. However, there are people
who don't receive these benefits.
Unless some method is provided for them to
access these means, the economy will stagnate,
and one day, it will lead
to a drop in tax revenue.
In other words, we share a common destiny
within this cyclical loop known as the economy.
So basically, this is what
you're trying to say...
Keeping riches isolated in one
place won't create abundance.
In which case, we should
share them with the poor.
Is that right?
A long time ago, someone said this to me...
"First-class merchants can
choose their customers."
But, Chief...
instead of choosing our customers,
why don't we produce them ourselves?
I see! I like it!
So, what you're saying is, "Don't choose
your customers, cultivate them yourself"!
What's that mean?
If the people of the slums can earn an
income, they'll become our customers.
As their number increases, merchants'
sales will increase as a result.
That's the hidden motivation here.
All of your company's wares are splendid.
The ones who will see the greatest profits
in this market of newly created customers
will be the Aria Trading Company.
So that's what you mean!
So their lives aren't only
about having enough to eat
Sounds good, doesn't it, Chief?
and so they don't have
to give up their dreams,
Creating our own market...
I think it's an intriguing idea.
I'd like to be a part of that!
I want this country to become one that
turns the despair of the slums into hope.
Honestly, you're both getting
ahead of yourselves.
Right now, what I should be
doing as the crown princess
is creating businesses that will bring
prosperity to the people of this country.
This is one of the few proposals I can
offer you in my current circumstances.
Not bad.
You seemed to have seen through me, right to
my convictions, so this has been entertaining.
But, Miss Rishe, you're still immature.
Your behavior is much too earnest.
It seems you really want
to work with our company.
I could use that fixation of yours to wring
you dry. I've already started plotting how.
Chief, you're going too far.
Now, shall I begin finding
faults in your proposal?
A proposal made by the likes of me?
I never believed that you'd
unreservedly approve of it.
Really? We've only met a handful of times.
It makes me happy that you
already understand me so well.
I wanted to avoid using
this if possible, but...
Well! What will appear from
your bag of tricks next—
Chief?
How?
How do you have this?
I'm very sorry.
I used a rather special
method to look into this.
And into your younger sister,
Aria Tully's, illness.
There's nothing strange
about word of Aria leaking.
After all, I've gone around speaking
to different doctors about her.
At the moment, I am cultivating
a number of medicinal plants.
Compounding the plants according
to the method written there
will create a medicine from the
large eastern country of Renhua...
a medicine effective against
Miss Aria's illness.
If she takes this medicine for a year,
she should make a profound recovery.
And you think I'd believe you?
You're not a doctor. No
matter what you say, I—
Did the medicine I gave you
the other day help all of you?
When everyone wakes, please
have them drink this medicine.
It did. I had a horrible hangover,
but after I drank that,
I felt better right away.
That was something I concocted myself.
"Become a merchant who can
choose your own customers."
That's what I've told my
subordinates all this time.
You've turned the tables on me, Miss Rishe.
Up until now, this maneuvering was all
about whether I'd choose you or not.
But now, it's about whether you'll choose me.
Chief...
I'm begging you. I'll give
you everything I own.
Please, give this medicine to—
Please don't misunderstand me.
I'll give you the method and the medicinal
herbs needed without any conditions.
I have no intention of using
your sister to my advantage.
But I would like for you to understand.
The people of the slums care
about their families, too.
To make sure their younger
siblings don't fall ill...
to make sure that they can feed them...
so many older brothers and sisters
sacrifice their own dreams.
This clumsy method was the only way
I could bring my proposal to you.
I don't believe that the tables have turned.
Please, will you help me, Chief Tully?
Won't you please enter into
business with me?
Please, lift your head, Lady Rishe.
Chief Tully! Please don't do that!
Trade is meant to bring abundance
to everyone involved,
but I thought to choose my customers.
It is I who am truly immature here.
Until now, the fates of people in the slums
have never meant anything to
me. That's the honest truth.
But there are many children
like my sister living there.
Your business idea is worth far more than
anything someone like me could think up.
Even aside from the matter of my sister's
medicine, I feel ashamed of my own arrogance.
Then, Chief, you'll...
From this moment on, the Aria Trading
Company, in the name of Kaine Tully,
will prepare everything you have asked for.
Thank you so much!
It was like walking a tightrope.
I'm so glad it all turned out well.
But I can't just sit here pleased with myself.
I must prepare for what comes next.
Lady Rishe!
Are you all right?
Are you feeling unwell?
I'm sorry.
Could you call Elsie back for me please?
Yes, my lady!
How is Lady Rishe faring?
Her condition seems very poor.
Kamil and her maid Elsie
are seeing to her now.
Lady Rishe!
We've awaited your arrival.
It's just so perfect for us that she
became indisposed and collapsed!
Thank you, Kamil, Elsie...
for abducting the future
crown princess for me.