Whatever it is you want to see,
I want to help you see it.
If there's something you
don't know, I'll teach you.
Though, when you want to achieve something
solely through your own efforts, I won't interfere.
What kind of scholar will you become?
I'm very much looking forward to finding out.
Why do you take such good care of me?
Perhaps because this may be the only
good thing I am able to do in my life.
Professor!
Hey there, Rishe.
Please stand back!
This suspicious person has declared
he will cause an act of violence
in town at six this evening!
It's just as he says.
And you think that by doing so, Prince
Arnold will hear of the power of black powder?
That's right.
Such an action will affect people
unrelated to this matter!
Yes, I understand that.
Professor!
Well, its unveiling demands as much.
As it's something I have created...
I must take responsibility for it.
Even if it means causing
misfortune for someone else.
My own existence is just the same.
I'm sorry, Rishe.
The words of a person like me... shouldn't
be taken at face value.
Taking you on as my student was
no more than a whim of mine.
Sister!
I once asked the professor...
Is it truly impossible for a poison
to bring someone happiness?
But instead of asking...
Professor, I may only have been
your student for a brief time,
but I can say this with certainty...
even a poison can bring happiness to someone.
My alchemy teacher once told me,
"If one fails to take all variables into
account, the experiment will fail."
No matter how great an
alchemist you may be,
your results will not always
be as you anticipated.
That is because...
it was impossible for you to
comprehend the variable that I am.
What are you saying?
What is that?
Professor, the things you
create aren't only poisons.
Even if you can only think of them as
things which bring misfortune to others,
if their method of use is changed,
many other types of value appear.
Colored flames?
The black powder exploded in the sky?
What is all this?
I once looked for a simple way to
differentiate between types of metals.
At that time, someone showed me the
beautiful aurora, and I remembered...
When fire is applied to metal,
it gives off a beautiful light.
That's true.
When metals are burned, the
flames turn different colors.
Yes.
However, that wasn't all.
With a new perspective,
I obtained a method to
change the colors of a flame.
Tiny lights, floating in the darkness...
they may look like the torches of
war, or like the lights of fireflies.
Each and every material and phenomenon
holds more than one meaning.
So does the black powder, and
so do you, Professor Michel.
There is nothing which exists solely
to bring misfortune to others.
And you plotted all of this
to make me understand that?
Why would you go so far?
Because I am your student.
If you wish to repudiate
someone else's research,
you must show results as counter-evidence.
If you're an alchemist, that is.
Without substantiation, the professor
would never change his thinking.
That's why...
I will devote all of myself
to trying to persuade you.
Observe with your own eyes.
Something which you have created...
is exhibiting a value
which you did not know of.
Just look at it!
I understand flame reactions and the
effect of black powder, and yet...
I never imagined a use like this existed.
You're amazing, Rishe.
No, you're the amazing one, Professor.
I'm sure that there are other things
which you thought could only be poisons
which have other splendid uses.
After all, you're the most
brilliant alchemist in all the world!
I see.
So, I was able to create the source
of something that beautiful.
It seems they all launched safely.
Thank you.
It was really a lot of work.
Could you give this to everyone for me?
This? What is it?
The amount of black powder
and where it was set...
Because I saw his experiment
planner in my third life,
I could narrow down the possibilities,
even in this large capital city.
After that, I took the
professor's area of activity,
and looked for spots that
matched the right conditions.
The rest was all thanks to everyone involved
in this matter doing their jobs perfectly.
Your Highness's retainers really
are exceptional, aren't they?
Lord Lawvine?
As you ordered.
Good work.
Michel Hévin.
This incident. You will
have to explain yourself.
Wait, Lawvine!
I will take charge of that person.
I cannot allow that.
What?
This individual declared that he
would cause an incident here,
on land governed by His Majesty, the emperor.
Even though the order comes from
you, Prince Theodore,
I cannot hand him over to you.
What is this commotion, Lawvine?
Prince Arnold.
I received a report of an individual
making nefarious declarations.
Believing him to be connected to the
large flames seen in the air just now,
I've captured him and
intend to interrogate him.
I see.
Prince Arnold, earlier, those—
Rishe.
That is unnecessary.
That phenomenon just now...
it was no more than a scholar of Coyolles
demonstrating a new technology.
Why would a Coyolles scholar unveil a
new technology here, in our country?
Our empire will be forming a technological
partnership with Coyolles.
In exchange for providing military
instruction to Coyolles,
we will be borrowing their precision
machining techniques and academic knowledge.
Those flowers of flame we saw earlier...
served as proof that Coyolles possesses
technologies unknown to our empire.
Do you understand?
Go.
Sir.
Lord Lawvine.
I apologize for hiding my
identity all this time.
Michel!
I'm happy for your help forming this
alliance, but that took me completely by surprise!
Kyle.
If you wanted to unveil the
results of your research,
there must have been methods which would
have caused less trouble for others.
You have it wrong.
The truth is that lives would have—
Professor Michel.
Right now, please just stay quiet
and let him be angry with you.
I'm sorry, Kyle.
I'm sorry, Rishe.
Michel?
I won't do it any more.
My theory was hugely flawed.
I understand that now.
I promise you that I will never do it again.
Then, I shall make the proper arrangements.
I will say this: I am not acting
out of kindness towards them.
It's abundantly clear that he
was plotting something unsavory.
However, if he were publicly
treated as a criminal,
my father, the emperor, would hear of it.
That's why I made use of your plan.
Yes. Thank you.
After I explain the details
regarding the professor,
I look forward to your
judgment on the matter.
How commendable of you.
If I choose to kill and
dispose of him in secret,
I will hear no complaints from you.
Prince Arnold.
What is it?
The truth is, the person who invented
the pocket watch was Professor Michel.
If we will be conducting joint
research with Coyolles,
won't Professor Michel's knowledge be needed?
What will you do?
You...
No matter how I look at
this, you were confident
you could convince me
from the very beginning.
How could I be?
The only thing I was confident of was that
Your Highness would be
interested in the professor.
The people in town will
have seen those fireworks.
When people learn that
they were from Coyolles,
I think they will support the alliance, too.
They probably will.
Yes.
So, those are called fireworks?
Yes, that's what I've named them.
I wanted you to see those
fireworks, Your Highness.
The black powder used in fireworks
is a dangerous substance.
However, depending upon how it's used,
it can also create a beautiful sight the
likes of which no one has seen before.
If you learned that, then you would
carve a path to many more possibilities.
That's my thinking on it.
Right now, he may still believe that
all of his abilities are meant for war,
but one day, I'm certain...
This medicine will help with
seasickness on your journey home.
The flavor is as awful as ever, though.
Compared to the suffering of
seasickness, it's nothing.
Lady Rishe.
Truly, thank you so very much.
It's only because you lent us your strength
that Prince Arnold formed an
alliance with our kingdom.
No, it was Coyolles' sound technological
prowess and support of academic research.
This is all the result of you doing
everything in your power, Prince Kyle.
I think that your husband
is far too magnanimous.
Not at all, Professor.
He's telling you that in this joint venture,
you should continue producing
the very best of results.
It's a severe punishment which the average
person wouldn't be able to shoulder.
Yes, I suppose it is.
"Create things which will make
the world more wonderful."
I've never done any research
in that area before...
but I'll do my best.
I wanted to apologize to you.
I was mistaken when I said that you
weren't suited to being an empress.
You're more than suited to it.
But it's true that I see it as a shame.
You won't regret it?
A life as the bride of Arnold Hein.
Right now, what I most want to know about
is the man who will become my husband.
I want to know him more than I want
to know any research result or theory.
And so we part for a time.
Let's meet again, my student.
Yes!
Professor Michel was taken aback.
He said Prince Arnold is "too magnanimous."
Rather than making a fuss over
something which ended in failure,
making good use of him makes
more sense. That's all.
Thank you.
I have one more thing to report.
It's finished?
Yes.
I wanted to see the finished
piece with you, Your Highness,
so I haven't opened it yet.
I'm sure it's lovely.
Rishe.
Showing me that you're wearing
that ring is unnecessary.
By unnecessary, you mean...
I told you.
The only thing that I requested of you
was to allow me to gift you a ring.
I have no right to wish
for any more than that.
You may have allowed me to gift you with it,
but you needn't wear something
which doesn't meet your standards.
You should wear only that which you like,
with no regard for the gazes of others.
Choose freely.
No.
What?
When they were measuring my size,
I chose the third finger
on my left hand, didn't I?
Yes.
In my country, when people are married, the
husband places a ring on the wife's third finger.
I long to experience that sort of ritual.
I want to wear this ring
for the marriage ceremony,
and I will chose my dress to match it!
You say that it's unnecessary,
but I'm going to wear this ring everywhere!
Rishe.
If anything, I've been restraining
myself from putting it on immediately!
So, Prince Arnold, please
put it on my finger for me.
I'm not wearing gloves right now.
It's all right, even without them.
I just really want it to happen right now.
So...
Please, Your Highness.
Rishe.
May I touch you?
Yes.
Hey, don't hold your breath.
I'm not holding my breath!
I've simply forgotten how
to breathe, that's all.
He laughed!
Have you remembered how to breathe?
Yes, somehow.
Rishe.
It's done.
It really is exactly the same
color as Your Highness's eyes.
Just wearing this ring makes me feel
like I can accomplish anything.
What do you think?
Yes.
It puts me in an even better
mood than I'd imagined.
Your Highness...
What is it?
The number of things I want
to ask of you has increased.
Tell me. Right now, I'd grant you anything.
I want to go on a journey
with you, Your Highness.
A journey?
Yes. A journey to see all of the
beautiful things in this world.
Not just fireflies and fireworks...
I want to go and find many more things
that you think are lovely and beautiful.
Thanks to you, I've found
one more of those things.
What?
What could it be?
What indeed?
If you don't know, then I won't tell you.
Th-That isn't fair!
Do you really think an average person
can measure up to one of your riddles?
An average person would not explode
a mysterious compound in the sky
over their betrothed's home.
Though, I don't think this riddle
is so very difficult to solve.
Right now, they may only be
the slightest of changes...
but as one piles on another, little by
little the future should change, too.
I hope to see a beautiful future
together with Prince Arnold.
In this life, that is the great
objective I have found for myself.