I have to make it through
the evening party without
Count Lawvine discovering my double identity.
And...
I'd like to somehow find a way to get
Prince Kyle to take this medicine.
If he doesn't receive treatment,
in the near future...
his illness will keep him
from even being able to stand.
What a surprise.
I thought that anyone caring for
an herb garden of this sort...
must be someone in a profession
similar to mine, but...
Good evening,
person who seems to be akin to me.
Professor Michel!
What do you think of the aurora?
Has it given you a hint to your research?
Yes! Very much so!
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm sorry, Professor, asking you to
travel all this way to bring me here.
Why are you apologizing?
You're my student,
so whatever it is you want to
see, I want to help you see it.
If there's something you
don't know, I'll teach you.
Though, when you want to achieve something
solely through your own efforts, I won't interfere.
In my third life, this man was my teacher.
Pardon my insolence, but may I ask your name?
Oh, my apologies if I've startled you.
I am Michel Hévin.
I'm here from Coyolles.
If you've lost your way,
we can escort you back to your room.
How kind of you.
But I'm not lost.
I'm interested in the young lady there.
This individual is our empire's—
It's all right.
My name is Rishe Irmgard Weitzner.
Master Hévin, might you be a scholar?
A scholar, you say?
That may be the simplest way to put it.
Your nails.
You used sap from the
gelwood tree, didn't you?
Though, it seems you've
used dyes to add color.
What method did you use to harden it?
I took lish grass and gibi
nectar, added labed leaf,
and compounded them together with glue.
Did you refrain from using kirith
leaf in order to prevent air bubbles?
You seem to know everything about it already.
It's no more than a logic-based theory.
What do you think would happen
if you mixed in some estoma sap?
I think it might harden even further.
Though, that's only a hypothesis, at most.
The actual results would
require verification.
You're quite an admirable young lady.
So admirable that were it possible, I
would like to take you as my apprentice.
If you wouldn't mind, just for the
time that you're staying here,
may I receive your
instruction on various matters?
Yes. I don't mind at all.
Thank you so much!
Then, Master Hévin, this means
you'll be like a professor to me!
A professor, is it?
That sounds like fun.
I never imagined the day would come that
I'd be able to call him "Professor" again.
By the way, my student,
the herbs in this garden lie
slightly outside my expertise,
so this is only a guess,
but are you perhaps intending
to give Kyle some manner of medicine?
Lady Rishe, I never imagined I'd have the
good fortune of seeing you twice in one day.
Please, don't hold to formalities
for my sake. Speak as you wish.
Then, if I may take you at your word...
Michel, what are you doing?
I've found this amazing girl!
I thought you might want
to meet her, too, Kyle.
This individual is His Highness,
the crown prince's fiancée.
Really? Is she?
But she's become my student, you see?
What?
The herbal medicine she's compounded
seems like it would work for you, Kyle.
Herbal medicine?
It's outside my field, but I felt you
should be used in this experiment, Kyle.
Professor! You shouldn't use the
prince of a kingdom in an experiment!
Oh, have I made a blunder?
Common sense is such a
difficult thing, isn't it?
But I truly do, from the bottom of
my heart, want Kyle to get well.
All right.
Are you sure?
The greatest scholar in my kingdom
says he wants me to try this medicine.
From the beginning...
I have been resolved to use any method
necessary to cure this disease.
Then, I will prepare it immediately.
Here it is.
The truth is that there is one
problem with this medicine.
Please, tell us.
This medicine...
is incredibly revolting in flavor.
The flavor is incredibly revolting?
Oh, is that all?
Kyle will be just fine.
After all, he's a very strong boy.
He's earnest and hard-working, too.
Right?
Lady Rishe, if this is the ordeal
which has been bestowed upon me,
I need only face it down with
all of my strength and spirit.
I know. I'll feed it to you!
Professor! You mustn't! At
least ready some water first!
Here you go.
Wait, I—
Are you all right?
I am.
So, Kyle, what does it taste like?
What is the flavor like?
Bitter mixed with sour, and
mingled with the two...
a particular stench, like that
of a horse stable, swoops in.
Th-Then, after swallowing, a strange
sweetness wraps around the tongue like a slimy—
There's no need to explain each stage!
Shall we try to get a clearer
grasp of the flavor?
Excuse me! Please bring some water!
Y-Yes, sir!
Here. One more sip.
Professor!
Now, my student, would you like to look
at this until your escort arrives?
Professor, this is—!
My research records.
They're too difficult for Kyle.
He said that no one would
be able to understand them.
You truly are a most intriguing girl.
Rishe, you truly hate
this medicine, don't you?
You're an intelligent girl.
If you have a flaw,
it might be that you only want to use your
knowledge and skills to make people happy.
I think it's a mistake for you
to determine others' happiness.
If something is born into this world
as a poison, then its reason for being...
would be to fulfill its role and bring
misfortune to people, don't you think?
Is it truly impossible for a poison
to bring someone happiness?
The idea that someone is born
to bring misfortune to others...
that preconception in itself
isn't like you, Professor.
There's no need to worry.
This compound hasn't been perfected yet.
It's complete, but I've been unable to obtain
the human resources necessary for testing.
Someone who will use this
compound exactly as I wish...
Such a person doesn't exist.
The professor and I...
we just couldn't come to understand each
other when it came to that compound.
I wonder if the professor has met the
kind of person he was looking for.
P-Pardon the intrusion!
Lady Rishe, your escort has arrived.
What?
Rishe, we're leaving.
Prince Arnold...
Your Highness, why are you here?
This is Michel Hévin, a scholar.
He is incredibly knowledgeable
and he'll be teaching me all
sorts of things while he's here.
I am honored to receive such an introduction.
I suppose I should present
myself as well as possible here.
Good evening.
You're this empire's crown prince, I assume?
It seems you've granted permission for
us to enter your imperial library.
Thank you.
If you should require anything for your
exchange of knowledge with my future wife,
I will procure it.
Ask for whatever it may be.
Then, I won't refrain from
making many requests of you.
Why did you suddenly come to escort me?
I was on my way back anyway.
Are you always out and about this late?
When I become absorbed in my work,
I find myself forgetting the time.
Oh, but I slept until this afternoon,
so please don't worry.
Here.
Use that.
What? But this pocket watch
is such a precious item!
It doesn't bother me. Since
it's easy to carry around,
I found it convenient to have for battles.
By "battles," do you mean
in strategizing for battles?
Yes. There are some who doubt them
because they haven't existed for long,
but it's just a tool which
accurately tells the time.
His Highness's thinking is flexible
enough to adopt new technologies.
Someone who will use this
compound exactly as I wish...
Such a person doesn't exist.
What is it?
It's nothing.
I'll take you at your word and
indulge myself by borrowing this.
Now that I think about it, my master
in herbalism found these useful, too.
Your master?
Yes. A truly incredible
herbalist from Renhua.
How does that man compare
to this master of yours?
Professor Michel isn't an herbalist.
Though, he does use herbal medicines in
his research, so he has the knowledge.
Then who is he?
He researches all the substances in
the world and creates new substances.
That's the sort of scholar he is.
He creates new substances, you say?
In Professor Michel's case, he says that
his objective isn't the creation of gold,
but if we were to call him by the title
which most closely describes his work...
it would be "alchemist."
At tonight's party,
I have to act cleverly so that Count
Lawvine doesn't notice anything.
Lady Rishe.
A letter has arrived for you.
Thank you.
Madame Mihaela.
I said that the piece would
take a month to complete,
but I've made a request of an artisan
visiting Galkhein from Coyolles,
so it's likely that the date of
delivery will be much sooner.
Changing artisans makes
this much of a difference?
How beautiful!
Your Highness.
The fact that you find
this tedious is showing.
I'm showing that on purpose.
It isn't a problem.
Prince Arnold.
For you to prepare an event
such as this for my sake...
I am entirely unworthy of it.
Lady Rishe, tonight you are
indescribably beautiful.
Thank you.
How do you find you've
been feeling since then?
Thanks to you, I'm feeling much better.
That's the most important thing.
Prince Arnold, I'm going to
go and speak with the ladies.
Prince Kyle, please do enjoy yourself.
I've finished giving my greetings,
so I've met my most basic obligations.
All that's left is...
Now... focus.
I found him.
It's been a while, but that went very well.
I never imagined that experience from my fifth
life would prove useful in a place like this.
I must keep my focus...
and keep anyone from noticing
that I'm avoiding Count Lawvine.
How are you, Lady Rishe?
How are you?
I'm honored to meet you, Lady Rishe.
No, the honor is mine. I'm very happy
to speak with you, Lord Weilman.
After hearing what happened from my mother,
I've been looking forward to meeting you.
Your mother?
I heard that you were kind enough to
visit my mother's shop the other day.
He can't mean that that
difficult proprietress...
Even Her Majesty, the empress
wasn't accepted as a client.
Oh, could you mean...
I'm the proprietor of this
store, Mihaela Laure Weilman.
I merely picked out a stone.
The one who sought to purchase
something there was Prince Arnold.
My!
Prince Arnold giving a woman jewelry?
I was surprised, too.
Speaking of which, I was informed that the
delivery date will be much sooner than anticipated.
I understand that it's because an artisan
from Coyolles was entrusted with the work,
but would that really make
this great a difference?
Coyolles' jewelry artisans
possess superior techniques.
The speed they can complete fine,
detailed work at is completely different.
Really? I suppose I should expect no less
from a country which produces gems and metals.
Count Lawvine seems to be standing still.
Prince Arnold,
please, will you lend Coyolles your strength?
Instead of aid through money or medical care,
we would like to receive Galkhein's
support through military means.
As you know, Coyolles' military
strength is all but nonexistent.
Our kingdom is allowed to exist
because we provide gems and metals.
If our neighboring nations so wished,
they could destroy us at any
time, and they threaten to do so.
I want to extricate us from this situation
and obtain a method to protect our citizens!
You're saying that Coyolles wants
to forge an alliance with Galkhein.
It's just as you say.
I've been wondering what
you were going to say.
You pushed your disease-weakened body on
that long journey to come here for this?
The value of the existence of a royal family
lulled into naïvety by peace is questionable.
Even if, hypothetically, we
moved this discussion forward,
what does Coyolles intend
to bring to our empire?
We will promise to give exports of gems and
metals to your empire the highest priority.
Even if our kingdom makes
no profit whatsoever.
That won't work, Prince Kyle.
You aren't suited to telling lies.
Don't make me laugh.
If I were in your place, I would be sure to
attach a period of effectiveness to that offer.
The gems which serve as the
kingdoms greatest source of funds
cannot continue to be supplied with
no regard to profit indefinitely.
That's...
It's clear why you've come
here with such a suggestion.
Coyolles' mineral resources have
already nearly run dry, haven't they?
Yes, that's right.
It's incomprehensible to me.
Your actions are nothing more
than the actions of a fool.
My life... isn't likely to last much longer.
A new life is about to be
born into my royal family!
For the sake of that child's future,
and for the sake of our people...
I must do whatever I can right now.
From what I've researched, Prince
Arnold, you care for your people,
and run a government which
extends a helping hand to them.
If it were you, then—
This isn't worth discussing any further.
Please wait!
Please, Prince Arnold!
Please help Coyolles!
You seem to be mistaken about something.
Rather than joining hands with another
country, invading and taking control of it...
that suits me much better.
Five years from now...
Prince Arnold will have become emperor
and will wage war on the world.
Coyolles will fight Galkhein.
And so many lives will be...
But Prince Kyle has confronted Prince
Arnold and proposed an alliance.
This is a branching point in history
which could change the future.
Weitzner, I want to protect this kingdom.
To accomplish that, I intend
to do whatever it takes.
As someone born into this, someone who has
lived beyond his time, I have duties to perform,
and this is the greatest of them all!
Prince Kyle may be prepared for Coyolles
to become a vassal state to
Galkhein if it means an alliance.
But...
that would only change who
is in control of the nation.
Unless a relationship of
equal standing is created...
But how?