Has something happened?
There's absolutely no hope in sight.
Is this about His Highness?
Apparently, it's more in his nature to invade
and take control of another country
instead of joining forces with them.
Really?
He said that?
At last, I've found him.
Someone who understands poison...
a sovereign who might use it the right way.
If the negotiations with
Prince Arnold fail like this,
Coyolles might be invaded.
And if that happens...
You're enthusiastic for
this early in the morning.
Lord Lawvine.
But I see hesitation in your sword.
The truth is...
my thoughts had turned
in an unworthy direction.
By unworthy, you mean...
If one day we go to war with another country,
everyone here will go
into battle, won't they?
They will.
I find myself afraid of a future like that.
It's only natural to find it terrifying.
What?
My son lost his life in the last war.
I'm proud of my son for fighting so bravely.
However...
in equal measure to that sense of pride...
I wish that my son had lived.
Lord Lawvine.
A war means that people will
be robbed of their futures.
Others will steal them away.
To conquer the fear of that,
one can only stand and fight.
Stand and fight?
I mean that you shouldn't deny
your own hopes and feelings.
You should use them as fuel to move forward.
"What is it that I can do?"
Find the answer to that question.
Thank you, Lord Lawvine!
Then, I shall see you later.
I don't want to die in some war.
I don't want Coyolles to fall into ruin.
But that isn't all.
Rather than joining hands
with another country,
invading and taking control of it...
that suits me much better.
You aren't that kind of person.
I want you to understand that, Prince Arnold.
And so, we have a special
observer for your training,
the Crown Prince of the Empire,
Prince Arnold Hein.
Why is Prince Arnold here?!
No matter how you look at
this, I've been found out!
I want to see the trainees move.
Sir.
Could this mean that he'll
overlook my actions?
Of course not.
So, what exactly are you trying to do here?
Well, um...
I am most pleased to meet you, Your Highness.
That you would personally speak
to a mere knight candidate
makes me feel both humbled and delighted.
Really?
If you are not the person I think you are...
then that would mean there is
no issue with my touching you.
Come now. Quickly, try to refute it.
Prince Arnold, please step away for a moment!
I refuse.
If you continue, someone is sure to see!
Is there some problem with that?
Yes, there is!
How so?
Y-You have a fiancée, don't you?
Well, yes, I do.
You do, don't you? I thought so!
Still...
your manner of speech is quite disrespectful
for a mere knight candidate.
My deepest apologies.
I don't know what it is
you're apologizing for.
Tell me with your own lips what you've done.
I-I didn't tell Your Highness
anything and dressed as a boy
so I could join the knight
candidates' training!
I am truly, very sorry!
Well done.
But why are you doing this?
Because...
this training you've thought up...
I wanted to undergo it, too.
If you wish to continue,
there are conditions.
You must be sure to rest.
And make sure that no one
finds out your gender.
What?
Can you keep to those?
Yes! Thank you!
Are you enjoying this training that much?
Yes!
Prince Arnold, the training you've
thought up is truly magnificent!
Your intention to carefully help the
knights to grow comes through clearly!
Capable people are the empire's treasures.
But sending these knights into
battle in the future will be...
I overheard your conversation
with Prince Kyle.
I'm sure you did.
I believe I can predict what you're thinking.
You believe that we should
form an alliance with Coyolles
and you're going to try to
convince me, aren't you?
But there is no value in a country
that has lost all its power.
When a nation's collapse
is only a matter of time,
the only question is how
to deal the final blow.
Prince Arnold, from time to time
you are the most incredible liar.
You're free to think
whatever you like of me,
but remember this...
For this empire, war is not a cruel choice.
It's simply one means of politics.
The first time I met Prince
Kyle was when I was a trader.
In this rain,
protecting your wares on the road
must have been very difficult.
Our kingdom lacks material resources.
It's traders like you who support us and
allow us to preserve our daily lives.
I wish to express my deepest
respect and gratitude to you.
Though he was a member of the royal family,
he was someone who treated people
of different stations with respect.
The second time I met him was
in my life as an herbalist.
Then, too, he was someone who acted
from his heart when dealing with me.
And the third time...
I will speak with my father
about the research funds.
Because I know that
you two will produce results.
I swear that I will make him agree!
It worked?
Congratulations.
More than anything else, the fact that your
unwavering hard work has been rewarded
makes me truly happy.
It's because Prince Kyle is like that...
that I...
Your Highness, starting today, I'd like
you to start taking these pills as well.
Though, the flavor is just as awful.
If it means that this body
of mine will move properly,
then it's nothing to me.
Prince Kyle, the truth is that
at the party the other evening,
I happened to overhear your
conversation with Prince Arnold.
You saw me in a most embarrassing situation.
In truth, the polite thing to do would
have been to leave the country after that.
However, I cannot afford to give up.
Didn't you think that it might be dangerous?
During the war, Prince Arnold beheaded
members of royal families of enemy nations.
You're aware of that, aren't you?
Everything from the fruits of Prince
Arnold's battles to his political measures...
I've investigated everything I could.
It seems to have been
camouflaged very cleverly,
but the care shown for the common
people in domestic policies...
I'm certain that it's his
intention at work there.
Killing the monarchs of enemy
lands in the last war...
it was done to prevent the seeds of further
trouble. It was a form of compassion.
That's how I think of it.
And, the reality is...
even if His Highness is a
cruel and barbarous person,
it doesn't change what I must do.
I have a request to make of you, Prince Kyle.
Won't you first form a
modest alliance with me?
An alliance?
In order to convince Prince Arnold,
I will need your strength.
Thank you so much!
Everything in it was incredibly intriguing!
You love to learn, don't you?
Yes, very much so!
Learning new things, whatever they
might be, makes me very excited.
The world gets wider and wider,
and even the view I saw yesterday
looks different to me!
That settles it for me.
You aren't suited to be an empress.
Professor...
You should just come and join me.
If you did, then if there were anything
you didn't know, I would teach you.
Thank you for your invitation,
but I am here to marry Prince Arnold.
Arnold Hein, is it?
I understand why you're drawn to him.
I'm interested in him, too.
It seems he's turned down Kyle's request.
And the reasons he gave for his refusal
were exactly the sort of thing I love.
If it were Arnold Hein, then I have the
feeling that he'd use it quite effectively...
this compound I've created,
which I call black powder.
I've been looking for so long!
I never imagined that I'd meet
the right person in this country.
Despite his appearance, His
Highness is a very kind person.
Even if he said some harsh
words to Prince Kyle,
it's likely that he didn't truly—
Say, Rishe!
Will you help me meet with him?
Of course.
I'll see if he can make
some time for you soon.
Then, let's go and see him right now!
His Highness is very
busy, so a sudden visi—
If he's as kind as you say,
then I'm sure he'd forgive us.
Well, that's...
I understand.
The truth is that you don't want
me to meet with him, right?
You...
haven't asked me what
black powder is, have you?
The professor told me all
about black powder...
back in my third life.
So, you won't cease your
experiments, no matter what?
I'm sorry, Rishe.
Not even if it means that many
people will lose their lives?
"That which humans have created
must be used the right way."
There's a problem with this warning.
Which is that no one can accurately
define what "the right way" is.
If this black powder of
mine is used the right way,
I'm sure that this world
would easily be destroyed.
But would that really be wrong?
"How will the things I
create change the world?"
Is wanting to see that
really such a bad thing?
Professor...
Farewell, my student.
I sincerely hope that your life
will unfold in a way that you feel is right.
I couldn't accept this black powder.
It will turn the world on
its head and scramble it.
I've been looking for a leader capable
of using it for so very, very long!
A leader like Arnold Hein.
I must find a way to establish friendly
relations between Coyolles and Galkhein.
And with Professor Michel in that state,
he'll stop at nothing to
approach Prince Arnold.
If he does, then His Highness will
use black powder in the war and—
Prince Theodore?
I heard he found out. About
you dressing as a boy.
I'm very sorry.
I had mixed feelings about you being
able to completely deceive my brother,
so I don't particularly mind.
Still, the news reached you very quickly.
Well, my retainers are
outstanding, after all.
Whatever my brother does, no matter
where he is, I know about it right away.
I have a perfect information network set up.
And it isn't just my big
brother I hear about.
I've got my sister-in-law in there, too.
I've already looked into the
backgrounds of the knight candidates.
If anything happened to you, I
wouldn't know how to face my brother.
Thank you!
It's nothing. And it's not
that I'm worried for you.
I'm doing this for my brother.
I understand.
Actually, I have a favor to
ask of you, Your Highness.
May I borrow your outstanding
retainers for a short while?
Is it something that will help my brother?
No. In fact, it would be an act of
rebellion against Prince Arnold.
I like it.
Since it sounds like fun, I'll join you.
Then, we've come to an understanding.
Because you were born,
my wife is dead.
Which is why you must atone.
You were born to bring us misfortune,
you harbinger of death!
Whether I was hungry...
or I was lonely...
the field of learning always accepted me.
Knowledge swiftly entered my
mind and settled into my body.
It was just like breathing,
or drinking water.
This child has inherited my genius.
Use him as much as you like in my place.
After being allowed into the
laboratory, my world expanded.
If I wanted to know something and
performed enough experiments...
my efforts would always be repaid.
What is going on here?
To think he'd be so adept at making
something that would kill people...
After some time, a war broke out.
Everything burned.
All of the alchemists in the laboratory...
everyone, including my
father, lost their lives.
It was by chance that I created it.
A compound capable of destroying everything.
That was black powder.
You truly are a harbinger of death.
It's just as my father said.
It seems I've been born to
bring misfortune to others.
In the past, I was unable to
convince Professor Michel.
Professor...
Well, hello, Rishe.
Have you managed to find a
way for me to meet with him?
Professor, do you truly intend to
give black powder to Prince Arnold?
If something has been born as a poison,
then only in fulfilling its task
will it find its true place.
Everything, no matter what, must fulfill
the role for which it was born.
My own existence is the same.
A person who was born to
upset the ways of the world
must act in accordance with that duty.
Even back in my third life, the
professor said these same things.
Even if many people will
lose their lives for it?
That's right.
Black powder's reason for being...
is to bring misfortune to others.
I'm sorry, Rishe.
It isn't that I want to
say mean things to you.
That's the honest truth.
This is the calling I've been given.
I'm certain that the professor will
use any means necessary to give
black powder to Prince Arnold.
Good night, Rishe.
If things keep going this way...
I won't be able to stop the professor.