I was up late the night before the
world as I knew it came crashing down.
Are you stupid?
Takagi...
You always run off to the same
spot whenever you have a problem.
It's like you're a little kid.
Yeah...
Until then, everything had been normal.
It's only the beginning of the semester.
There I was out in the sunshine...
...having a great time telling myself that
out of all of the 2nd year students in the world,
I was the 4th most miserable one.
But at that time, everything...
...was more or less over.
Whoa, Tejima-sensei!
Don't resort to violence...
Looking back on it...
...we should've just made our way outside.
Instead, we scrambled to the observatory.
Back then, it seemed like the best thing to do.
Rei!
Why...
Why is this happening?
There must be a reason.
If we knew the reason, we could figure out what to do.
Hisashi is always right.
I wanted to believe that too.
But I had this gut feeling that
our world had already fallen apart.
So...
I...
Gotcha!
Eat this!
Yeah...
During that time,
it was too risky for us to think
that the world was still normal.
Go away!
Then it hit me.
We were walking through our school hallway
carrying weapons, expecting to face danger.
It wasn't a hallway anymore.
Yeah... This is...
I'm sick of these things! I want my mom!
...the country of the dead.
Do you think someone will come and help us?
No.
But why?
How can you say that?
It's just like the helicopters we saw
from the school rooftop this afternoon.
No one can be bothered to help us.
In fact, we might never...
Never?
We might never get any help?
Then how are we going to make it through this?!
We just have to do what we can.
That's just the situation we're in.
You're always like this...
You always say the wrong thing at the wrong time.
It's been this way since kindergarten—
I was just stating the truth!
So?! You could say it different—
We should go.
Yeah...
Should we act only in our own
self-interest, we stand not a chance.
Let us act as a team.
Let's go!
Our actions at the time meant...
...that we were ready to take on the real
problem and fight these animated pieces of flesh.
We ran through our school that was
filled with noises, screams, life and death.
They're not humans.
They're not humans anymore!
It's dangerous outside!
Don't get out of your car under any circumstances!
I repeat!
We progress at roughly one kilometer an hour.
I wonder if we can even make it over
the bridge before morning at this rate?
Oh shut up! Put a lid on it!
Put a lid on it? But... I'm hungry...
There's no need to cry.
We're safe in here.
We'll be okay.
Sensei...
There's nothing to worry about.
We'll be okay....
Well that's that.
I've become the leader based on a majority vote.
Rei!
Screw it!
No way in hell am I going to be anywhere near him!
Wait!
You just have to put up with him until we get to the city.
Didn't I tell you that you'd regret this?!
Look, now's not...
Dr. Marikawa!
In other words, I didn't know yet...
...that this world had already ended.
Komuro-kun! Are the two of you unharmed?
The police station!
We'll meet at the East Police Station.
At what time?
7 PM!
If it doesn't work out today,
then we'll try again tomorrow!
There's... no one here.
Either they ran away, or they died.
If they died, they'd be walking around!
Then they went to chase after... living people...
Look, Takashi!
License? Nope. Helmets? Nope. Bike? Stolen.
He's gonna arrest us.
Don't tell me you're afraid of a police car after beating up so many of the undead.
Of course I'm not.
Are you serious?
Rei!
There's gas leaking from the car.
Don't get close!
We might find something useful.
What are you staring at?
You should help too!
Do you know how to use a gun?
I've seen some cop shows.
You only put your finger on the
trigger when you want to shoot, right?
Something wrong?
It... feels kinda heavy.
Well duh. It's not a toy.
I only have five shots?
Takashi.
Here.
It's from the other officer.
His gun wasn't in working condition,
but you can still use the bullets.
Wow, I'm amazed.
I've seen the one my dad uses.
And do you think I'd be afraid of
blood after what we've gone through?
Wanna throw these away?
Guns aren't exactly reliable if you don't know how to aim.
But you feel a bit safer now, don't you?
SELF-SERVE
I wonder if they still have some gas.
Every gas station has at least
enough gas to fill up 1,000 cars.
I'm sure they do.
Shit.
What is it?
This is a self-serve station.
We need to slide a card or put in some cash.
Then do it.
I bought a juice earlier... I only have 30 yen left.
You suck.
Well excuse me for not being Hisashi!
What the hell's your problem?
When did I ever compare you with Hisashi?
You told me that I suck.
That would mean there's someone awesome to compare me against!
You're obviously thinking of Hisashi!
Honestly, you suck so much.
What do you want?
Cash! Can I borrow some?
Well, my purse is back in my bag.
What, and you just told me that I suck?
Wait right here.
Just scream if something happens.
Is... anyone here?
Like that would open it...
Well, I've always wanted to try this.
What was that?
Wow, sounds like someone's having fun...
I should probably quit giving him a hard time...
Rei?
Hey! Stop moving!
Rei, what's wrong?
Hey bro! Your girl is pretty cute!
Let her go!
You dumb? Like hell I'd do that.
If I want to survive in this monster filled world, I need a woman.
Are you... insane?
Am I insane?
Damn right I am!
My family all turned into
those things right in front of me!
I...
I had to smash every single one of their heads!
My father, mother,
grandmother, little brother...
Even my sister, who's still in grade school!
How the fuck could I stay sane?
Takashi!
Rei!
Her tits and her voice are mighty fine!
And these are p-pretty big.
Hey...
You fuck her, right?
Every night, don't you?
Or... wait...
You don't?
Are you an idiot?!
Takashi!
Hey, toss me that bat!
If you don't, she's dead.
And...
I'm taking your bike.
It's out of gas.
You busted the cash register!
You've got tons of money!
Refill the damn thing!
Please place your hand on the static
discharge button before you begin.
Hey...
Can you let us go?
We're on our way to see if our parents are safe.
Weren't you listening to a thing I said?!
If they're in town, then your
parents met the same fate as mine!
Done.
Then go!
Just go!
Hey, can you—
Shut up! Do you want me to kill you too?!
Hey, please—
Shut up!
Or I'll seriously fucking kill you!
I've never fired a gun before,
but I can't miss at point-blank range.
Wh-What if it ignites the gasoline?
It's a lot better than giving you my girl.
Fuck!
Bl-Blood... Blood!
How... dare you...
Don't do it, Rei.
But!
We don't have time to deal with him.
After all...
That noise we made was loud.
Hey!
You're just gonna leave?
You're gonna leave me here?
Come on! Help me!
Please, help me!
Hey!
Hey...
Once the sorrow dissipates,
aa yami ga owaru to
buds sprout out of the darkness and begin to grow
kuroku yodomu kimi no me ga tsubuyaku
I'm in a world that has fallen to ruins
tada kuzureta sekai
I had lost my way toward tomorrow,
ashita e no ikiba sura nakushite dakedo
but the voice of the one I must protect guides me
mamorubeki hito koe ga michibiku
When I swore to never see her cry again,
namida wo mou minai to kimeta toki
I freed my heart of its shackles
kokoro no kase kowashite
and grasped a burning blade
ima todaeru kodou wo
A blade that would melt my heart into fire
honoo de tokasu ha wo nigirishime
As my fingers tremble,
ima fureru yubi wo
I firmly place them on my heavy, black trigger
hikigane no kuro ni tsuyoku ategau
and turn my life into a shot of air
kono inochi wo tada kuuki no tama ni kaete
Is something wrong, Takashi?
You've been quiet.
As we keep moving, we'll probably see that same thing happen over and over.
Really?
Yeah... You're right.
Forget about it.
Let's hurry.
Of course, I never forgot about it.
The first day after the world came to an end,
I was responsible for someone's death.
I couldn't possibly forget that.