...against the outbreaks that
have been occuring all over the place.
However, all the political parties have been expressing their uncertainty about the SDF's security operations.
The number of deaths in the Saitama prefecture already exceeds 10,000.
Emergency News Coverage
The prefecture governor has—
That was gunfire!
Just now, the police opened fire!
But what are they shooting at?!
No! What?! Stay away!
Help me!
Emergency News Coverage
Please Stand By
There's been some sort of problem.
F-From now on, we'll be
broadcasting from the studio here.
As you can tell, the situation outside has become grave.
We advise you stay in your home unless it is absolutely necessary to go outside.
Once it's safer outside, we'll bring you
information about the on-going situation.
That's all?
Why aren't they saying more?
Because they're afraid of causing panic.
Even now?
Because of what happened just now!
Fear leads to chaos, chaos leads to anarchy.
How would you expect the government to
deal with the living dead in a time of anarchy?
This unusual phenomenon has spread throughout America...
...and has yet to be brought under control.
The government authorities
have evacuated the White House...
...and will relocate to a command
center on-board an aircraft carrier.
There are reports that this transfer...
...is in preparation for the
possible use of tactical warheads.
We have currently lost contact with Moscow.
Beijing has been set ablaze.
London has maintained order,
but in Paris and Rome, there are reports of looting.
Government officials have declared...
So they're all over the world...
But how...
When I was surfing the web this
morning, it was business as usual...
I can't believe that it only took a few hours for the world to come to this.
Don't you feel the same?
But there must be some place that's safe, right?
And soon, things will be back to normal.
Keep dreaming.
Do you really have to say it like that?
This is a pandemic. What am I supposed to say?
A pandemic?
It's when an epidemic of infectious disease spreads.
So, the same disease that's infected people here is spreading throughout the world.
Like influenza?
More like the Spanish Flu of 1918.
Over 600 million people were infected
by it, and 50 million people died from it.
Think about recently when people were
worried about that new type of influenza.
Isn't this more like the Black Death of the 14th century?
Europe's population went
down by a third during that.
How did those diseases stop?
There are lots of theories, but...
The disease usually stops when too many humans die,
because there aren't enough
people to spread the disease further.
But...
In this case, the dead are moving around and attacking people.
Then you are implying it has no reason to stop spreading?
But it's so hot outside!
Maybe their flesh will start decomposing and they won't be able to move!
And what is the duration of this process?
Well, during summer, it takes around 22 days for some parts of the body to decompose.
But during the winter, it can take months...
Anyway, if we go to our homes—
How do we know they'll even start to decompose?
Why do you say that?
Don't these things defy our knowledge
of medicine? So why bother relying on it?
It could be hopeless. Just how long...
What is important is having a location to
make use of after we check on our families.
Should we act only in our own
self-interest, we stand not a chance.
Let us act as a team.
We should help survivors as our ability allows us to.
Got it.
How do we get out?
The front door is closest to the parking lot.
Let's go!
Just so we're clear...
There's no need to engage in a fight unless it's necessary.
Avoid fights whenever you can.
They only respond to sound.
Additionally, they're powerful
enough to break down a normal door.
So once they get a hold of you, you're dead.
Be careful.
Takuzo!
Shit...
Stay back!
Th-Thank—
Not too loud.
Is there a person among you with a bite?
Nope!
They really do look fine.
Wanna come with us? We're getting out of here.
Y-Yes!
A bunch of them are down there.
What's the point of hiding here?
They use their ears, not their eyes.
Then why don't you prove that for us, Takagi?
Regardless, if we remain inside of the school as such,
we will be unable to move once attacked.
No way out but through the gate, huh.
We require someone to validate
the truth behind Takagi-kun's words.
I'll go.
No Takashi, I'll—
It would be more preferable if I were to go ahead of you.
You should stay back in case
something happens, Busujima-senpai.
But why, Takashi?
Who knows?
"Who knows"?
Really, who knows?
Takashi—
I understand how you feel.
Regardless, this decision was made by no one but himself.
They really can't see me?
In that case...
Run!
Why'd you do that?!
If you hadn't yelled, we'd probably only
have to worry about the ones close to us!
No way! Didn't you hear that echo?
There are more of them!
Don't talk.
Run!
Takuzo!
Naomi!
Run!
Takuzo!
Forget him!
You can't save him if he's already been bitten!
Wait—
Why?
I told her it's useless.
Why is she going back for him?
I... understand.
With the whole world gone to hell,
I'd much rather die with the one I love.
What kind of doctor are—
Watch out!
Please calm down, Takagi-san!
You filthy nerd!
Who gave you the right to interrupt me while I'm talking?
Well...
I don't know.
I envy your close relationship.
Sensei, the key!
Target? Check.
Public safety? Check.
Ready to rock and roll!
Oh hurry up and shoot them already!
Komuro-kun, they're all in!
You first, Senpai!
This isn't like my car!
Uhm... The gas, the brake, the clutch...
Help us!
Who's that?
That's Shidou. He teaches 3-A.
Shidou...
We're ready to go!
Hold on a bit!
There are some swarming in the front too.
I can't drive if there are too many of them bunched together!
So run them over!
If we do that with this bus, we'll end up rolling over!
Don't save him!
Rei, what's your problem?
You don't need to save him!
We should leave him to die!
Everyone! Hurry!
I guarantee you'll make it out alive.
Okay, Sensei!
Despite what I said, I wonder if they'll even make it to the bus.
I sprained my ankle!
Oh...
Is that so?
Then it's the end for you.
The world as we knew it has come to an end.
In this world,
it's the survival of the fittest.
Shizuka-sensei!
We're off!
To the gate!
I know!
They're not humans.
They're not humans anymore!
Looks like we made it.
Yeah.
Thank you for saving us.
Are you the leader, Busujima-san?
We are without one.
Our survival is simply the product of our teamwork.
Well that's no good.
A leader is required in order for us to survive.
One who manages everything.
You're going to regret this.
You're definitely going to regret saving him.
Our city!
Look!
We'll never make it if we keep going!
First off, why do we have to do
whatever you guys planned to do?
You all decided to go back to the city without asking us.
Couldn't we have just looked
for a safe place inside the school?
He's right!
We should find a place to hide,
like that convenience store we just passed by.
I've had it!
I can't drive with all of you yelling!
What... the hell?!
Then what do you wish to do?
I can't...
I can't stand this guy!
Why?
What did I ever say to you?
You...
You suck.
Splendid work.
Komuro-kun, Miyamoto-san,
that was some excellent teamwork.
However, the fact that this conflict arose in
the first place simply proves what I stated earlier.
We really do need a leader.
Do you understand?
And there's only one person who can do the job?
Well Takagi-san, I'm a teacher
and the rest of you are students.
That alone should be enough to say who's more qualified.
If I was the leader, I would prevent conflict.
What do you all say?
Well, that's that.
I've become the leader based on a majority vote.
Rei!
Screw it!
No way in hell am I going to be anywhere near him!
Rei...
If you're saying that you can't get
along with us, then we'll just have to split.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Komuro!
Wait!
You just have to put up with him until we get to the city.
Besides, it's too dangerous...
Didn't I tell you that you'd regret this?!
Look, now's not...
Dr. Marikawa!
Now we're split...
Komuro-kun! Are the two of you unharmed?
The police station!
We'll meet at the East Police Station.
At what time?
7 PM!
If it doesn't work out today,
then we'll try again tomorrow!
Dr. Marikawa, we are unable to advance.
Okay, I'll turn back and find another route.
Crap. Let's get out of here!
You...
You piece of crap...
Takashi.
Let's go.
Under the sky that has lost its light,
kuroku somaru sora no shita
I was left behind, trembling in the big shadow
kage ni obie nokosareta
The blood, burning in scarlet red,
akaku moeru chi no iro ga
melts away in its blotted color
nijinda mama tokete yuku
It's not remotely possible
mou ichido mayowazu
for us to go back to who we used to be
ano koro no bokura ni modoreru hazu mo nai
return to destiny
I found those sweet words and added them to my prayers
ai suru kotoba mitsukete inori wo komete
I learned how to fight for my loved ones
dareka no tame ni tatakau sube wo shitta
If I'm unable to remain with you,
soredemo kimi wo nakusu to shitara
I'll give up my life
boku wa kono inochi wo
so I can be by your side
sasagete demo kimi no soba ni iru yo
Are we going to walk to the city?
If we don't have another way, yeah.
Wait, he was wearing a helmet...
I didn't know you had a license.
High schoolers have the right to drive without a license!
In other words, I didn't know yet...
...that this world had already ended.