Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Sagashita amai negai, kyou mo
Kizuite to, watashi no naka kara
Dare ka ga kimi e to sakebu yo
Mitsumeau, modokashii kyori ni
Abaredashita samishisa
Kamishimeru hitori
Suki toiu omoi o
Iitai demo ienai
Itsumo soba ni kimi ga iru no ni
Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Tomoshita tsuyoi omoi
Mayowanai mayoitaku wa nai kara
Shinjite ima, ippo fumidasou
For the sake of myself
Big Sister Shino...
Their many walls of defense are easily penetrated...
This is exactly what is expected
of Odin's number one spear.
And yet...
Her power is...
You are an eyesore, Einheijer!
What are you doing?
Are you not going to protect Einheijer?
Why must I do something like that?
I am the spear.
I am only meant to gouge the life from you.
So it turned out to be instant love, eh?
Roskva.
Yes, ma'am.
In that case, don't hesitate to come crush Us!
If I don't keep coming back unashamedly
when I've yet to destroy you,
I couldn't bear to face that weakling
who's finally shown he's a man in some way.
You should have noticed this.
As for my beloved sisters,
they are connected and understood
through the red string of fate.
The restraints have been lifted...
it's time for the counterattack!
Takuma!
Danger
Drop
Natsuki-san!
Takuma!
Kiss with Lover, confirmed.
Kiss with Lover
Confirmed
Sacred Blade third form constraints, released.
Siegrune invoked.
Siegrune
Blade
All of you, return!
You will guard Roskva and Us with your souls!
Do you think I'll let you go?
No, no, no!
At this rate...
Our Lady...
Please, tell me your decision.
No! That is one thing we must not do!
Our Lady!
Understood.
The akuma disappeared.
O, Rune. Please grant us your power.
Unleash the maximum Sacred Blade!
Takuma, get behind us!
I wanted this settled before it got to this point...
What's going on?
It's coming...
the galdr!
O, Rune; Please lay waste to our enemies.
O, Rune; Please grant us this victory.
There is no need to take note.
Etch this into your minds.
All living creatures who gaze upon this form
will be slaughtered, down to its very soul.
Roskva, how are you doing?
There are no problems here, Our Lady.
Please use as much power as you see fit.
Takuma! Under no circumstances
must you leave this space!
Okay.
This is a very firm wall... But,
not too much for the Captain's spear!
Great!
Huh?
Valkyrie...
Einheijer...
castle wall...
barrier.
You're all such a nuisance.
Hagar.
I'm sorry, everyone...
Master...
Am I alive?
Takuma...
Listen, Takuma-chan.
The Norn is eager for this battle.
She'll set up a surprise attack,
then immediately come and assail us,
and I can't be sure why,
but if we can just get through it
a chance for victory will surely arise!
That's much easier said than done...
What's going on? Are they hurt?
Was Shino's barrier broken?!
All of you, get away!
Huh? What happened?
A soul-devouring akuma?!
This is bad!
Hagar.
Our Lady...
Takuma!
I will protect everyone with my soul!
Takuma-chan...
Our Lady...
You truly are too kind.
But it's precisely due to that I am here.
Please,
I beg you, stay well, Our Lady.
The Norn's transformation... broke?!
We thought they were being hasty in battle,
but Snorri was the reason for that, huh?
Don't hurt Roskva!
My father's orders were to avoid killing
as best as I could.
However, it's already past that point.
You... your eye!
Shino...
Takuma! Stay with me!
He pushed his ability too far.
His soul is worn down.
He continued using his ability
until he was coughing up blood.
Hey! Is everyone safe?!
Hurry!
We're too noticeable here, so we'll carry him home.
O-okay.
Oh no!
How did you fair, Our Lady?
I am sorry. I missed my shot at Einheijer.
Once Roskva showed signs of illness,
so we're retreating at once.
However, the minimum duty has been fulfilled.
There are no complaints, are there?!
Of course not, Our Lady.
Thanks to you drawing the attention of the Valkyrie,
and destroying the barrier
and the castle surrounding them
we have gained control of the situation.
This is an unbelievable number
for the run-of-the-mill dwarf.
There are as many as hundreds of millions
of aether crystallizations.
This is undoubtedly the work of misteltein.
Hey, I can't break this cocoon.
The thread, huh?
Our target has been captured.
We are getting out of here right away, Garm.
When the spear and the castle get here
it will be a nuisance.
You're ordering me to "stay" again?!
You... Give back the misteltein!
Well. I guess it's okay if I have one of these, right?
That was delicious!
Big Sister Misa!
Are you awake, Futaba?
Is everyone... Is everyone okay?
Misa took the Fang head on.
That would normally result in instant death, but...
of course that's not the case for my little sister.
The threads that she had set up throughout her body
instantly stitched her wounds back up.
Right now, Lover is working on healing her.
Her body is back to normal.
But the problem is...
Sister! Wake up, Big Sister Misa!
She's stopped bleeding, so why...
Big Sister Misa!
When I healed Natsuki-san and Ichika-san, there was
a sense that I was touching both body and soul.
But...right now, I can only feel Misa-san's body.
There's no soul left inside of Misa-san.
It can't be true...
Did I actually... die?
I'm freezing.
This is the darkness of
the furthest reaches of the aether.
Is this what they call Niflheim?
My soul is being dragged in.
Is this where my battle ends, then?
My little sisters are probably crying.
But my big sisters may be
the ones crying the most...
They're both fairly sensitive.
I guess I won't see the others again...
Big Sister Misa!
Someone...
help me!
Takuma!
You transformed!
Wait... Did you die too?
I'll explain later!
He's really saving Misa's soul?
If it doesn't go well, he loses his too.
It's okay. I'm sure he can do it.
Do you know the way out of here?
I've got this!
Wait... wait...
This is strange.
Mom died, and I was afraid of everything,
so I've spent the past few years
only staring at them in my hands.
Complete Preparations in 30 days
Common Questions on the Exam
And now in these few months,
it's become a light that illuminates the darkness.
He was exhausted after combat
with the Norn, wasn't he?
Leave me behind.
You'll get trapped here too at this rate.
I can't kill Einheijer.
Yeah... Ichika-san said that too.
I can't fight directly.
The least I can do is make every effort
to support you all in the background.
And that's exactly why I will become a strong man.
I never want you to see me looking so pathetic again.
I've said goodbye from my old self.
A man that can be relied on
and put everyone at ease...
I will become a man worthy of you all!
Takuma's body...
it's so warm.
Is this love?
It's not an emotion I understand well, but...
this warmth might be it.
Takuma.
Natsuki-san?
B...
Big Sis Misa!
Guys... This hurts. I'm gonna die.
I'm sorry, Big Sister Misa.
Sob
Sorry!
Thank goodness, thank goodness!
Oh dear.
Bounce
Misa!
Sorry, Big Sister Ichika, Big Sister Futaba...
I couldn't protect the misteltein.
You did what you could!
More importantly,
thank you for protecting everyone.
She's right, Misa!
Thanks, everyone.
Thanks, Takuma.
Er, uh...
Well, what do you think, Big Sister Ichika?
Are you referring to Lover?
Yes. He opened the door to Niflheim
and brought back a soul...
I think he's already beyond just healing territory.
It was a mystery as to why Father had
chosen that guy as Einheijer, but...
You were really great, Takuma!
The summer day that Takuma-chan
saved Natsuki-chan...
I knew you could do it!
The summer day that Takuma-chan
saved Natsuki-chan...
U-uh, really? I didn't know if I could.
no, the day Takuma-chan's mother
died eight years ago,
You were worried, right?
no, the day Takuma-chan's mother
died eight years ago,
Yeah, but I'm glad it went well.
no, the day Takuma-chan's mother
died eight years ago,
Yeah, but I'm glad it went well.
his fate was probably already decided.
So, do you want something to eat?
Right, Shino-chan?
Big Sister Shino!
Big Sister... Shino?
It's a pleasure to meet you, Master.
I'm the fourth of the nine Valkyrie sisters,
Shino Waltraute.
I hope we will get along from today forward.
Why are you here?
Is it okay for you to leave the storehouse?
I'm sorry, my dear sister.
I'm concerned for your well-being,
but we need your strength now, Shino.
We need the power of "Waltraute,"
the strongest Valkyrie.
Shino-san...
Where was she...
I'm sorry!
Yamada!
Akuma...
Are you okay, Takuma?
I-I'll be fine.
Recently, the symptoms of my
fear of people have hardly shown up,
so I was able to solve
all of the problems in every subject.
It's thanks to all of them.
Academic
Achievement
I want to escape from being the lowest
ranking student and getting the booby prize...
No, I pray I can get into the top 300 in our grade!
Takuma-kun! Natsuki-chan!
Come look at this!
It's Akuma!
We're gonna die! Run!
That was my promise.
The dearly held promise I made to my mother,
Ta-
1 Takuma Akutsu
2 Itsuyo Saotome
etched into my memories.
1 Takuma Akutsu
You did it!
Hug
This is amazing, Takuma!
And just as your symptoms have gone away!
Er...
Student Council President
Well done, Takuma-san!
As student council president, please allow me to
bestow upon you the highest of compliments!
Gleam
Oh my, President!
You have done...
JUST LOVELY!
It's so amazing that you're
the top student, Takuma-kun.
No... There must be some mistake.
No, there wasn't.
We've been watching you the entire time.
We know how hard you worked to get there.
You were at your desk every night, without fail.
Yeah, it's true.
It is indeed!
You've finally fulfilled your promise
to your mother, huh?
Sorry, Mom.
I didn't do very well on the test today.
B-but, I'll ace the next one for sure, okay?
I'm looking forward to it, Takuma.
Akutsu Family Tomb
Sorry it took so long, Mom.
Let's get Big Sister Futaba to make us a feast.
Yeah!
To celebrate Big Sister Misa's recovery, too!
E-excuse me!
Takuma... You are unbelievable!
I love all of you!
Huh?
Takuma-kun...
This is very sudden...
I-I'm sorry!
But... just once, I wanted to tell you
how I feel using the proper words!
I need to say I love you all, as women!
Even if you do, you're really going to say that
out of the blue in a situation like this?!
Moron!
I'm sorry!
Disgraceful...
Takuma-kun...
He loves us?
I-I already knew that.
I knew that you love not only me,
but all of my sisters.
I'm not so foolish as to take him seriously.
If anything, the competition starts here...
As for me, I love everyone.
And Itsuyo, and Mutsumi...
However, someday...
I hope he chooses only me.
The myths speak of goddesses known as Valkyrie,
in the Valhalla of Asgard.
These goddesses become stronger
as long as they are in love.
And that is because...
Love is the source of a maiden's power!
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Koi o shiranakucha you and I, hajimaranai no yo?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
We wanna share your heart!
(How do you tell me?)
Amai kotoba o input
Shippai - Cancel - Zenzen hibikanai kedo
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch shite todokete yo
Seikou - Complete - Saisentan ga ii darou?
(Hold me tight)
Naze koi to itte kurenai no?
Ai ni yukou
Motto keiken shite level up otome gokoro
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Oshiete ageru wa, koi wa otome no power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Jucchuuhakku kitto mou lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Tokimeku mune dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Akuma de shy na mind, kiss for you!
Kaete shimau yo na, kiss for me!
Koi o hajimemasho!