You told your mother that you'd
"become a respectable person."
Yes.
However, if the world itself is no longer,
you can't fulfill your promise to your mother.
So it's a deal, then?
You can become the hero that will save the world.
That's impossible for someone like me.
This isn't about "someone like you."
This is possible because OF you.
Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Sagashita amai negai, kyou mo
Kizuite to, watashi no naka kara
Dare ka ga kimi e to sakebu yo
Mitsumeau, modokashii kyori ni
Abaredashita samishisa
Kamishimeru hitori
Suki toiu omoi o
Iitai demo ienai
Itsumo soba ni kimi ga iru no ni
Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Tomoshita tsuyoi omoi
Mayowanai mayoitaku wa nai kara
Shinjite ima, ippo fumidasou
For the sake of myself
Hey, look at that!
It's the three Saotome Sisters!
They're always so cute.
And he's always so scary-looking.
Shh! He can hear you!
Akuma looks scarier than ever today!
The semester exam results are announced today!
Student Council Room
Inukai-san, can you copy the documents for me?
Will do.
You've been really gung-ho lately, President.
Yes. We don't have much time
before the school festival.
As a student council president
that just transferred here,
I'm worried about being accepted by everyone.
It will be okay!
Matsumura-san?
Fără lanțuri la Academia Hokuou!!
Chains are something that bind the heart!
An innovative school reformation!
An improvement in student autonomy!
That inauguration speech will soon be legendary!
Oh no. The reason someone
so unfamiliar with the school like me
got so very far and became president
is solely because I had the support of all of you.
Matsumura-san. Inukai-san. Nishida-san.
I am so very proud that I can rely on so much.
Ba-dump
Superior! You are superior, President!
I will follow you all the days of my life!
Aaah
By the way, President, you did amazingly well
on this semester's exams.
President!
By the way, President, you did amazingly well
on this semester's exams.
Second Semester Midterms Exam Results (11 Subjects 1100 Points)
Itsuyo Saotome
Yusuke Matsumura
Number 1?!
Itsuyo got number 1?!
She got a perfect score in all subjects.
That's so impressive. My math score was bad.
Natsuki-chan, did you solve question three?
The Student Council President is amazing,
she got number one!
Mutsumi-chan's also in the top 30.
And Natsuki-chan is... what?
She must not have felt well that day.
And she still took the test?
Those sisters are so outstanding!
What is up with that excessive praise?!
Stop it, it's embarrassing!
It's okay! Natsuki-chan, you're... um...
Seventeen chains!
Natsuki, you're so good!
You were number one in
the gaming tournament we did yesterday!
Sorry, Mutsumi. I'm not happy to be praised for that.
How did you manage to get a good grade, too?!
You're busy with work, aren't you?
I had Big Sister Misa help me study.
I hate studying. I don't see the point.
By the way, how did Takuma-kun do?
Takuma's ranking has always been...
Huh?
What's going on?!
You're by far the worst in the entire grade!
That's how it always is.
Whoa
I can't concentrate on the exam
when there are people around me.
eep
rumble
twitch
omg
shake
panic
rumble
fidget
I can't solve the problems that I always get right.
It's your phobia of people, huh?
And the entrance exams are next year...
What do I do...
Grab
You can't just be depressed forever!
That will make your affliction even worse!
Natsuki-chan, calm down!
It's an akuma!
Help me!
Yamada fell out of the window again!
Call an ambulance!
That was awful!
C'mon, we made a decision about that, right?
We're not going to talk about Takuma-kun's illness.
I know that! I know, but...
He's just...
working so hard, but still...
Takuma Akutsu-kun, please come to
the AV room immediately. Once again...
Camera audio-video
E-excuse me.
I wonder who it is and what they want with me.
I did badly on the test,
and I caused a huge commotion...
Am I being expelled or something?
My stomach hurts.
U-uh, is anyone here?
Chains?!
There's no difference between humans
and Valkyries who are not in their battle forms.
However, I am able to summon
my "Sacred Sword" level one version.
S-Student Council President...
What in the world is this...
Obviously for your date with me.
According to my father's oracle, we still have time
before the next demon is summoned.
I have to level up now.
B-but... killing monsters and stuff
is a lot of responsibility for me,
and I have studying to do...
I saw the test results.
Everyone has their own personal inclinations.
Things like studying are quite trivial...
You're someone who will become
the hero that saves the world.
But...
Or, Takuma-san...
...is it that you hate me?
I-I-I-I don't hate you or anything...
Really?
Okay...
I don't care either way.
I'm so glad.
I couldn't care less about Takuma-san.
Our father, Odin, is the head of the gods.
It is precisely due to that diginified position,
that he is the only man I will love.
He will defend the human world...
defend Midgard, from the hands of the akuma.
That power was given to me by my father,
and as the fifth Valkyrie, it is my mission.
Therefore, I have only one goal.
I will date you, level up, and become
the strongest of the Valkyries!
Once I do that... Yes! I am certain...
Ta-da
My father will give me a pat on the head!
Itsuyo has a "father complex."
"Father Complex"
Ta-da
Student Council President?
Takuma-san, when it's just the two of us,
you must call me Itsuyo!
Oh no, this isn't good.
I'm subconsciously getting excited... or not.
It's just that I have so much respect for my father!
Please relax.
I am aware of the illness you are suffering from.
Let's just move things one step forward.
I am simply fulfilling my duties.
By the way, Takuma-san,
have you already had your lunch?
N-no, not yet.
If that's the case...
I mistakenly packed enough lunch
for two people today.
If you don't mind, would you like to eat with me?
Uh, but...
Now, now, no need to be shy.
Say "ah"!
Val love, "Have Lover Eat
Something Homemade," initiated.
Val Love
Have lover eat something homemade
Initiated
Failed.
Failed
hack
shake
Th-there's a wiener octopus in my eye!
I-I'm sorry! I was so nervous
it wouldn't go down my throat...
So we're doing this the hard way, are we?
Relax, Takuma-san.
Everyone has had at least one instance
where they couldn't get something down.
Yeah!
We're going on to the next one!
Er...
Val Love, "5-minute massage"
Val Love
5-minute massage
Încordat
He's stiff... his body's so stiff!
Sorry, I'm nervous.
Failed.
Failed
Val love, "Link Arms for One Minute"
Val Love
Link Arms for One Minute
Strain
Your arms won't open!
Sorry, I'm nervous.
Failed.
Failed
Val love, "Gaze at Each Other for 30 Seconds."
Val Love
Gaze at Each Other for 30 Seconds
Tremble
Quit rolling your eyes into the back of your head!
Sorry, I'm nervous.
Failed.
Failed
gloom
H-he's difficult!
To think that Takuma-san is this incompetent...
What do I do?
You must think, Itsuyo Saotome...
no, Schwertleite!
You can surely come up with something brilliant...
Okay, I'm going back now!
all alone...
Girls' Changing Room
At this rate, I won't raise my level at all!
Student Council President! How do you-
Just lovely!
She told us she was lovely!
Does he not find pleasure simply in being bound up?
And Father was so pleased by that...
You say we still have time before the next battle,
so why are you in such a rush?
That's rich coming from someone who did what she
wanted with reckless abandon the other day.
I-I had to, that was an emergency situation.
I'm sure you did.
Even so, you've been rather active lately, Itsuyo.
And you used to be such a cry baby.
That's right. I'm different now.
There are still plenty of chances left!
I cannot lose heart after that!
An akuma?!
It can't be... It shouldn't have been summoned yet!
There's no way Father's oracle could be wrong again.
Moreover...
That akuma is...
What is that?
A balloon?
There was a message from Valhalla a little while ago.
It said an increase of aether
has been observed on the Bifröst.
Then it's the real thing...
Yes.
An akuma is here.
Itsuyo! What's with that akuma?!
That akuma is strong beyond the limits of your blade.
Finally... my turn has come!
When I succeed here,
my father will surely pat me on the head!
I'll do a splendid job binding you in my chains.
Student Council President, hello!
A lovely day to you!
The barrier has been successfully deployed.
We're safe for the moment.
Before looking into the reason why
Father's oracle was wrong,
we must defeat that akuma.
It seems I'd have trouble dealing with
this one without my chain.
Unfortunately, with my level so low,
I don't stand a chance against it.
This is definitely a lot to deal with for my sword.
Alright. I'll lure the akuma away, so once you
raise your level make your way there.
Um... What about me?
You're not suited for battle, so standby!
O-okay.
Now hurry up and transform.
I-I'm going to!
C-close your eyes!
Huh?
Just do it!
A LXX-a valkirie
"Siegrune"
Sabie: Nivel 22
Uau
Okay, I'm heading out.
Make your way there as soon as you raise your level.
I'm off!
I've won!
What was with that childish kiss of Natsuki's?
If that were me, I'd be able to showcase
a much more adult kiss!
Um, Itsuyo-chan.
Is there anything I can do to help?
I want to help you two.
C'mon, Takuma-san! Let's go!
Dash
Have you seen the President?
Secretary
There's a joint gym class with Class D,
but I haven't seen her for a while.
I'm sorry, I don't know where she is.
Where in the world could she be?
Inside the barrier is a different dimension
separate from our reality.
No matter how violent it gets, it's okay.
Physical attacks aren't effective against Frosti.
To defeat him, we must first bind him with chains.
I can create up to fifty swords at my current level.
That's what I'll do until Itsuyo gets here.
I'll just have to ride this out.
Gym Storage Room
Val Love, "Get Intimate in
the Gym Storage Room," initiated!
You can't escape me again!
Um... Er...
To satisfy this condition, we must make out.
We can't call it "getting intimate"
if only one of us is excited about it.
I can't be the only one taking the lead.
I have to make Takuma-san feel like
he wants to as well!
Please relax, Takuma-san.
Mort de frică
There's nothing here to be afraid of.
We have no choice but to do this
in order to save the world.
So...
will you hold me?
I kind of have a headache...
Speriat
I want to escape from here as soon as possible!
But it'd be awful if the world were destroyed.
I have to do what the President says...
O-okay.
Score!
Takuma-san has finally been captivated by my charm!
And now, at last...
I can take the first step towards
becoming the strongest Valkyrie!
It's alright.
I don't have to worry about anything.
I'm a different person than who I was.
All of this...
is so my father...
will pat me on the head.
She's so slow! What are they doing over there?!
If she doesn't get here soon...
That was careless...
I'm so sorry.
There was a mosquito on your cheek.
Well, let's move on to the next...
to the next...
Th-this isn't... I am... well...
She's completely petrified.
What should I do about this?
Dad, is it true?
Will a war start soon and will everyone die?
I don't want to be away from everyone.
Do not worry.
Schwertleite, I will protect you all no matter what.
So please become strong as well and support me.
If you do that, everyone will undoubtedly survive.
I'm counting on you.
Okay!
What's so different from how I was?
I haven't grown in any way at all.
I'm the same as when I couldn't do
anything on my own...
Huh?
O-oh, uh, w-well... I'm sorry!
A long time ago when I would cry, my mom would
do this and it'd c-c-calm me down, and uh...
Er, s-s-sorry... if it b-bothers you, th-th-then I...
Such big hands...
This is just like... when my father
would pat me on the head.
Val Love, "Get Intimate in the
Gym Storage Room," accomplished.
Val Love
Get Intimate in the Gym Storage Room accomplished
Experience Points Entered
Experience points entered,
Schwertleite level up confirmed.
Schwertleite level up confirmed
I'd be able to showcase a much more adult kiss!
The protective barrier...
is being destroyed!
Itsuyo!
What's that?
Stand back!
There's no use struggling.
Everything is sealed when you're bound with this.
Your body, your heart, and your abilities.
That's how my chains work.
I'm leaving the rest to you, Natsuki!
Fifth Valkyrie
"Schwertleite"
Chain Lv. 14
I was so sick of waiting for you!
I do apologize for that.
I can't believe you came looking for me!
This is such a large campus I lost my way...
It's okay. The classes moved in practically no time,
and I had informed the teachers
ahead of time anyways.
I figured that guy must be the root of all this.
Now, now.
Er, I didn't do anything...
Matsumura-san, let's go.
Huh? O-okay.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's our job.
You two got pretty close, huh?
I-is that how it looks?
I hope you can keep this up
and cure your phobia of people
and improve your grades as well.
Huh?
Let's go too.
S-sorry!
Dammit.
Is that seriously the Valkyries' lover "Einheijer"?!
Presenting himself in front of them in that pitiful state...
Here they say you have to take
what they give you and so on,
but in my case, before it's even set before me...
I'm going to devour it.
Watchdog
"Garm"
Fang Lv. 65
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Koi o shiranakucha you and I, hajimaranai no yo?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
We wanna share your heart!
(How do you tell me?)
Amai kotoba o input
Shippai - Cancel - Zenzen hibikanai desu wa
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch shite todokero yo
Seikou- Complete - Saisentan ga ii deshou?
(Hold me tight)
Naze koi to itte kuremasen no?
Ai ni yukou
Motto keiken shite level up otome gokoro
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
Oshiete ageru wa, koi wa otome no power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Jucchuuhakku kitto mou lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Tokimeku mune dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Akuma de shy na mind, kiss for you!
Kaete shimau yo na, kiss for me!
Koi o hajimemasho!
You did see that, right, Natsuki?
I leveled up the power of my chains!
Fights with the akuma are going to get
even more intense,
so it'd be a problem if you didn't
at least do that much.
By the way, it took you way too long to get it done.
What in the world did you do?
Without telling you the specifics,
underneath it all Takuma-san is surprisingly wild...
Wh-what?!
While I was desperately trying subdue the akuma,
the two of you were...
Shameful!
Next time: "The Secret Maiden."
Data viitoare: Fata secretă
I can't tell Natsuki that all I could do
was give him that kiss!