I can't seem to concentrate on my studies,
and final exams are coming up soon...
It has to be this restlessness...
What is everyone doing?
Not much...
I don't know if it's the sore muscles from
the fight at the festival or we're just out of it,
but you know, at times like this,
nothing beats taking the kotatsu out
and loafing around under it.
Yakumo, do you want a rice cracker?
Nope.
Takuma, have you been studying since early again?
Uh, kind of.
Um, by the way, shouldn't we do a date today?
What's up, Takumacchi? You want to go on a date?
T..Takuma-kun! Do you want to take Sue for a walk?!
In that case, Takuma-san, would you like
a home cooked meal by yours truly?
W-well, I-
I did it!
What did you do, Kururi-chan?
Well, I've got a major invention!
A special Kururi-made, fully automatic doctor set!
It took three months of persistence,
but Midgarr doesn't have many
raw materials so it took some time!
It's been a bit since I've seen a Kururi gadget.
What'd you make this for?
I asked Kururi-chan to make it.
Big Sister Futaba!
We'll have more battles, and we can
take care of our bodies at the same time,
I thought it'd be a good chance to have that.
Yakumo, do you want a mikan?
Nope.
Huh?
We're doing Val Love, "Play Doctor!"
So by playing doctor, you mean...
Takuma's the doctor, and we're the patients?
That is correct.
In other words, Takuma can examine
our entire bodies?
That is correct!
I refuse! I absolutely will not do this!
M-me neither...
I'm sleepy, though.
Um, I'd rather not.
Oh dear.
I'll do it.
Let's play doctor! Please allow me to do this!
Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
The sweet desire I found is here today as well
From inside of me
Someone screams at you to notice
We stare at one another, at an irritating distance
Alone, I endure
The onslaught of sadness
Though I want to tell you this feeling of love
I can't say a word
Though you're always at my side
Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
A strong emotion set aflame
I won't hesitate, I don't want to hesitate
I'll believe in now, and take a step forward
For the sake of myself
Since I caused so much trouble
for everyone at the campus festival,
I have to do what I can to tend to their bodies!
Because I am... their lover!
Val Love "Play Doctor," initiated!
Val Love
Play Doctor
Initiated
For Futaba
Well then, I suppose I'll go first.
I'm in your hands now, Doctor.
I appreciate your trust!
Just relax now.
Let's see...
I want to put the stethoscope
against your chest, so... er...
I should take off my clothes, right?
Okay, go ahead.
I'm not as big as Mutsumi-chan, though.
U-um... P-pardon me!
This is as awkward as I thought it'd be!
What kind of decent conversation can I have
with her right now as a lover?
Doctor? Do you think it's necessary
to put your stethoscope there?
I-I-I'm sorry!
E-Er, y-you know, i-in the past, we used to think
that the Kamakura shogunate started in 1192,
but recently it's been found that
the Kamakura shogunate was formed in 1185.
Formed in 1185
Well then, I'll be going now.
Oh, okay.
You're perfectly healthy.
For Misa
Now then, Misa-san.
First, take off your clothes.
Absolutely not!
There's nothing wrong with me at all!
See ya!
N-no!
I have to do an examination!
O-okay! Okay, get your hands off me!
Um... Are you itchy anywhere?
Shut it, moron!
And what the heck are you spreading on me?
A restorative oil specially made by Kururi.
To complete the exam,
I have to rub this oil on her...
entire body... her entire body.
It... tickles...
I-I-I'm sorry!
I mean, thank you!
That's enough! You idiot!
For Itsuyo
Well now! I'm ready for anything!
Let me see.
For you President...
You get a urine test.
Urine... test?
My schedule is completely full,
so I apologize but will you please
fill this in the corner of this room?
I have to make sure he doesn't hear me.
I've finished.
Then please give it to me.
Give this... to you?
Yes, that's right.
B-but...
If you don't give it to me I can't proceed!
Hurry! Give it! Give it, Give it!
Menace
Takuma-san, you're acting so...
sinister!
President?!
For Mutsumi
Let me see, for Mutsumi-san...
I'll check if you have any cavities.
O-okay!
A dental exam, huh?
Is my breath okay?
I should have had a piece of gum.
Now then, can you open wide for me?
It's so dark I can't see much of anything.
I'll go in a bit further.
Alright, looks good. Your teeth looked very nice.
Takuma-kun...
I wanted you to at least turn the lights off!
The lights?
And for Natsuki-san...
For Natsuki
What is it?
I'll be measuring your bust, waist, and hips,
so please take off your clo-
How shameful!
Oof
Why is it always me doing things like that?!
I-I'm not the one who can answer that...
But it looks like I can take your
measurements over your underwear.
Oh really?
In that case, I guess...
Why would I agree to that?!
I-I-I'm sorry!
H-h-here I go.
But I'll do it
Just for the record...
This is pretend!
Don't you dare look at the numbers!
She's extremely threatening!
What? Hurry up and do this!
Oh, uh...
I was just thinking about how cute
your underwear is today.
Childish
Y-you think so?
Wh-what's wrong?
Nothing, I'm just glad that I changed into
some that I liked just in case.
Just in case?
Shameful!
For Yakumo
First, I'll take your temperature.
Can I put this under my armpit?
Y-yes, please do that.
I somehow feel like I haven't done
a successful exam yet...
I have to hang in there..
If you want to examine the condition of a body...
I think it's best if you listen to
the beating of the heart.
Uh, well...
What? Big Brother, your heart is
thumping away in there too.
It's so loud...
Why's that?
You're so...
perverted.
S-sorry about that!
S
Oh yes, I see.
For Kururi
So basically, Big Brother, you were
trying to take care of everyone's health,
but you kept letting them get away
and you can't do any exams.
Dejected
What in the world could I be doing wrong?
Well.
Guess I've gotta. Kururi's gonna help you out!
I just gotta push this...
What's this?
I'm a genius inventor, you know!
I've gotta at least add a super examination mode!
Super examination mode?!
A device built into the clothing
stimulates acupressure points,
and the doctor can do the work of 100 people!
I feel like I can treat any serious illness now!
Go get 'em, Big Brother!
This time you can go crazy and do all of the exams!
Roger, Kururi-san!
Th-this can't be happening!
An explosion due to overheating?!
What?!
It must be because I didn't use
materials from Asgard...
I'll take off this suit for now...
Uh, what?
I can't get it off!
Oh no... If I don't do something,
Kururi-san will get caught in the explosion!
Takuma-san was kind of strange today.
You think so?
I thought he was his typical shameful self.
I agree! He may have been
more aggressive than usual...
Takuma?!
Ba doom
Big Brother Takuma!
Good grief, how could this have happened?
Takuma-kun, are you okay?
Oh dear.
I'm sorry, Big Brother!
Don't worry about it.
A doctor hurting himself is pretty ridiculous.
Besides, bluntly speaking, you were creepy today.
Oh my.
He was as creepy as he always is, though.
I didn't really mind...
He was gross and shameful.
And an idiot!
I'm sorry about that.
But you know...
I appreciate your concern about our health.
Well, there you go, we've played doctor now.
Here, Takuma, open your mouth.
Say "ah!"
Val Love "Play Doctor," accomplished, somehow.
Misa's Room
I'm starving.
C'mon, Takuma-san!
Here's your beef stroganoff snack!
Uh, I just ate lunch...
Okay, bon appetit!
What do you think? Delicious, right?
Right? Right?
How is it, Takuma-san?
I'm sorry!
No need to rush things, Itsuyo.
If you're too forceful, even a fully motivated
Takuma will keep running away.
I-I don't need you to tell me that!
Oh really? Sorry.
Now then...
Big Sister Misa, I have...
a small favor to ask of you.
What?
You want me to show you
an example of a date?
I-it hasn't been that long since I came to Midgard!
And I was just thinking it's necessary to study
what kind of date is prevalent in this world!
What do you mean you haven't been here long?
We both got here on the same day.
B-besides, I heard that in the past...
in Asgard, you were a super popular
and gleeful master of romance.
Who did you hear that from?
Well...
In Asgard, I was told that if I'm having problems,
then I should talk to the romance master!
But I'm not necessarily having problems
or anything, you know!
Good grief. Where could she have
heard that rumor from?
I've never even fallen in love or anything!
And even though I was popular, I only got hit on
by other girls and that went nowhere!
I mean I basically didn't even have time
for romance in Asgard!
Asgard
I can't beat a wild boar by myself!
Help me, sisters!
Since I beat one, there's no reason
you can't do the same.
And that's because you're my little sister!
You'll be fine, Misa-chan.
All you have to do is slaughter it
before you get slaughtered.
You pair of combat crazy dimwits...!
My body won't be able to handle
hanging around my sisters at this rate!
I'm sure if I had a younger sister...
they'd push her around instead!
Big Sis Misa!
Some years later
What in the world is going on, Itsuyo?
Um, well, someone in the park was picking on me!
And then Natsuki-chan...
I chased 'em away!
So why are you crying Itsuyo-chan?
Because Itsuyo doesn't want you to get hurt.
What?!
Because, because...
Don't cry about something like that!
You're my big sister, right?
And I... And I...
H-hey you three, here are some stuffed dolls for you!
Here we go, Kururi! Whee, you're up high!
Really, I miss those times
when I didn't even have time to sleep.
Big Sister Misa?
I can't. I have things I have to do.
Ask someone else.
These steps are something you have to
climb up under your own power.
I understand that you're eager to do this
because Natsuki is the only one leveling up,
but we don't know what's going to happen
with that in the future.
At the campus festival...
I couldn't do a thing.
I was manipulated by the enemy.
I'm constantly being protected,
and it's a bother to you, too.
That's why...
Okay, I'll do it, so stop making that face.
Really?! Thanks, Big Sis Mi-
Big Sister Misa!
Misa's Room
Are you going to fold the laundry?
Yeah.
Th-there sure is a lot.
Because it's for the whole family.
Val Love, "Spend 1 hour with just
the two of you in the same room,
Val Love
Spend 1 hour with just the two of you
in the same room
without informing lover," initiated!
without informing lover
Initiated
I can at least do this.
I hope she'll accept this as an example.
Well, this is something I have to do,
so I'll need you to help me with the rest.
Is that the stuffed doll that
Natsuki-san asked you for earlier?
Mole-san
Yeah.
I made stuffed dolls for her often when she was a kid.
Besides, Natsuki's been made to fight
ever since we got to Midgard.
This is the least I could do.
I see.
A seemingly nicely flowing date is unfolding!
Just as expected from the master of romance!
It looks like this one will take a while.
Meow
Huh?
I-it's nothing!
wobble
He tried really hard during the campus festival,
but his usual self hasn't changed.
How did he manage to survive this long?
Well, I do feel for him, suddenly becoming our lover
and being ordered to save the world and stuff.
I wonder what will happen from here on out?
A thread, broke?
Takuma, let me get past you.
O-okay!
Where did my spare go?
Takumacchi, did a blue box fall
somewhere over there?
Huh?! I-I don't see anything!
Found it!
Sorry! You okay?
Y-yeah, completely fine.
What happened? You stiffened up all of a sudden...
Uh, well, I'm a little dizzy...
For real?! Did you bump into something funny?
Let me take a look!
Uh, no, it's okay!
Just let me see!
You've got a little knot here.
If you just leave it alone it'll get better.
Sorry about that, Takuma.
I-it's fine.
This pressure is terrible!
I'm feeling kind of lightheaded now...
I'm going outside to get some fresh air.
What?!
It hasn't even been an hour yet!
Wait a second, Takuma!
If you want to take a breather,
then let's play the word chain game!
I'll start!
A-apple!
Play the word chain game for a break.
C'mon, now it's your turn, Takuma!
U-um...
B-boobs... Yours are on me!
And I've been able to see, uh...
some other things from the gaps in your clothes!
Oh crap! I'm going to get punched!
rumble
Oh no, I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to make you feel weird.
I'll be more careful from now on!
You're not going to punch me or anything?
I wouldn't do something like that!
C'mon, let's get back to our chores.
She's different from Natsuki-san.
I-I'm so embarrassed! What am I doing?
I'm supposed to be showing Itsuyo
an example of a date, right?!
You can't show her your disgraceful side, Misa!
Let's do this, Oltlinde!
I'm learning so much!
This is awkward.
I should've worn something that fit better.
But if I changed right now,
it'd look like I'm doing it intentionally.
He's not looking, is he? He's not, right?!
Right! Then it's okay! Maybe.
But still, this uneasy feeling...
Is this what a date is?
I don't know, since I've never really had
contact with the opposite sex.
Even so, I still can't imagine being in love with Takuma.
It's not so much love as... what can I call it...
ugh whatever, I don't know!
I need this hour to hurry up and be over!
Ugh, man, really, what am I doing?!
Misa-san.
His face is close!
Y-you can't go in there!
I-I-I'm sorry!
S-sorry!
What did you want?!
Um, I'm done folding the laundry.
Huh? Already?
That was quick.
And it's neatly done, too.
Until all of you came here,
I managed all of the housework on my own.
I lost my mother early...
His hands look so rough...
I see.
He's been living here this whole time.
In this huge house...
all by himself.
Hey Natsuki. Thanks for always,
always working hard.
Yay, thanks, Big Sister Misa! I'll cherish this!
I'm glad it made her happy.
Yeah, same.
Takuma?
Yes?
I've got one to give you, too.
Huh? Uh...
Well, I guess, er...
I think it's bad that you got involved with our battles...
And I think that it'll continue to be
a nuisance to you for now, but...
I hope you'll keep helping us in future battles.
S-same here! I hope I can keep helping!
Yeah!
You did fairly well, Big Sister Misa!
I can't believe I was witness to such a brilliant date!
I-I'm exhausted...
Val Love, "Spend 1 hour with just the two of you
in the same room," narrowly accomplished.
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
If we don't understand love,
you & I won't get anywhere, you know?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
We wanna share your heart!
(How do you tell me?)
Input sweet nothings
Failed - Cancelled - They don't resonate at all
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch me and bring me one
Successful - Complete - Isn't cutting-edge tech great?
(Hold me tight)
Why won't you say romance?
Let's bring it to love
Get more experience and level up my maiden heart
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
I'll teach you that love is a maiden's power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Nine times out of ten, they're surely already lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Fluttering in my chest, dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Your shy akuma mind, kiss for you!
Will completely change, kiss for me!
Let's begin our romance!
I guess I need to do more research to make
Kururi gadgets with the materials in Midgarr.
Big Sis Yakumo, even though we share a room,
I'm always loud, so I'm sorry.
I don't really mind.
However, if you interrupt my sleep,
you're getting punished.
S-scary...
Next time, "The Strengthening Maiden."
Next time: The Strengthening Maiden
Hey, for your next invention, will you make
something that causes Big Brother even more grief?