Massacre your weary mind with Gungnir!
"Revive the Dead" energy drink that will stab it all
to death with a single blow, matter how sleepy you are!
Now on sale!
Cut!
That's all the shooting we'll do for today.
Thanks for your hard work, everyone.
I'm going to head home.
Mutsumi-chan sure is great.
She's sweet-natured and cute to boot.
She'll be an exceptional talent in the future.
She's got huge tits, too.
I agree! I'm looking forward to her future...
and she's got huge tits.
Throb Throb
Chiruri Café Food &
Sweets Date
Colorful Seasonal Ingredients!
Date Apps Useful for Couples
Special Date Issue
I've been so busy lately
I haven't seen Takuma-kun at all.
I'm so jealous of them...
They got to go on a date with him.
A demon was summoned today
just as Father's oracle predicted,
but what will happen from here on?
Who knows...
Even if the malevolent gods
are coming down to Midgard,
since they must possess a human vessel,
they can only use level one abilities.
But the only ones who can properly fight right now
are Natsuki-chan, Itsuyo-chan, and I.
Hold your horses...
We can never be too careful.
Well then, is it finally time?
Yes.
Looks like the time to invoke it has come.
Val love: "Date with an Idol"!
Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
The sweet desire I found is here today as well
From inside of me
Someone screams at you to notice
We stare at one another, at an irritating distance
Alone, I endure
The onslaught of sadness
Though I want to tell you this feeling of love
I can't say a word
Though you're always at my side
Still unseen by anyone
In the midst of my dreams
A strong emotion set aflame
I won't hesitate, I don't want to hesitate
I'll believe in now, and take a step forward
For the sake of myself
café Katori
Thank you for taking the trouble to
come with me, Takuma-kun...
I just had to try the pudding at this place!
Ta...Takuma-kun, you take a bite, too. It's yummy.
O-okay.
Menacing
Ba-dump...
What's wrong?
I-I was just thinking about
how nice the weather is today.
Takuma-kun, you really are cool.
I absolutely have to succeed
in this chance they've made for me!
I'm rooting for you, MUTSUMI...
Val Love, "Date with an Idol"...
I mean, Mutsumi-san.
A scandal can be disastrous for an idol!
Thanks to the memories of today,
Even more so since this is a date, so I can't be seen.
I can keep going in the harsh world of entertainment...
If I can go on this date and get home
without being exposed the entire day,
then it's a success!
I have to make absolutely sure
I'm not exposed as an idol today.
Really? Yamada-senpai, you're actually friends
with the idol MUTSUMI-chan?
Yeah, it's true!
We've even exchanged contact info!
That guy must be in the same class as Takuma-kun.
She's the latest up-and-coming idol, MUTSUMI!
She's attractive, has a pure personality...
and she's got huge tits!
I'm seriously jealous you're friends with a girl like that!
You're friends with Yamada-san?
I may have talked to him in the hallway once... Maybe.
But speaking of Hokuou Academy,
that guy's there too, right?
Uhh...er... Takuma Akutsu!
Jolt!
Jolt
The murder of fifty people
in front of Tokorozawa Station,
that explosion on the Omekaido Highway...
The serial akuma incidents, etc, etc!
The Takuma Akutsu who's
the mastermind of all those incidents,
and whose parents are evading arrest
as members of a crime syndicate!
They have to be the deeds of Akuma!
Your parents were part of a crime syndicate?
They were just office workers.
I get dropped out of the window
by that Akuma every day, man...
It sucks.
But you were the toughest guy in junior high!
That's crazy!
He better show off while he still can, cuz...
Menacing
I apologize for showing off!
Yamada-senpai?!
Um...
Hey, did you see what happened?
That huge guy just threw someone
out of the window. Horrible.
He sure looks like the type that'd
freakin' throw someone out of a window.
We should call the police.
Huh? No... You didn't do anything!
It's fine.
I'm used to this.
Should we leave soon?
Yeah.
No one noticed me because all the attention
was on Takuma-kun, but...
I wonder if it's making him feel bad.
No! I can't lose my nerve!
After all that, I should give him
good memories of today!
You gotta fight, Mutsumi!
Takuma-kun, let's have fun today!
Is there anywhere you'd like to go?
Oh... since you asked,
there is a place I want to stop by.
Center Exam
Trends and Strategies
Math
Categorical Answer book
National Mock Exam?
Y-yes.
There's a national mock exam next week,
so I have to study for it.
I did a pathetic job on the last midterms,
so I need to give it my all.
That's impressive, Takuma-kun.
You decided what you would do on your own,
and you're giving it all you can...
I admire you.
But Mutsumi-san, you're...
When I was a child,
I was attacked by a very scary akuma.
Ever since then, I've been so frightened and nervous,
and I've lost my confidence.
I can't do anything on my own anymore.
Wh-what? That can't be right...
Both me and Itsuyo-chan were saved by
Natsuki-chan when we were children.
The Student Council President, too?
Yeah! It's unimaginable now, but in the past
Itsuyo-chan clung to Natsuki-chan.
What's going on? I got chills all of a sudden...
Is it a cold?
Worry more about what's going on with
your own head instead of other people, Natsuki.
And you got that one wrong.
You should be more patient
since you're the one helping me study.
Are you able to sleep by yourself now, Itsuyo-chan?
You're always bringing up the past...
Is that how you speak to an elder sister?
What do you mean "elder"?
We're triplets, so that doesn't matter, dummy!
Yell
Only dummies call other people dummy, you dummy!
What'd you say?!
Hey, you two stop fighting.
I became an idol unwillingly.
Someone needed to become an idol so that
we could get more opportunities for dates,
no one wanted to do it...
"How about Mutsumi?"
"Mutsumi would be great!"
"Okay, we're counting on you Mutsumi-chan!"
"What?!"
That's unfortunate.
If it were me, I could never do a job where
I'd be in contact with so many people...
Whoa
I'd probably die!
I really hated it at first.
But you know, now I'm glad I became an idol.
Thanks to all of my fans' support
I've gained my confidence back little by little,
and I'm able to keep going.
So I understand now.
I understand I can't just be protected all of the time.
I have to get stronger.
I have to work hard for my family.
DIE
AKUMA
GET OUT
GO AWAY
I'm sorry.
Mom...
It's all...
my fault...
Takuma-kun?
I'm going to go buy this.
Takuma-kun.
He does look similar...
He looks like the akuma who attacked me as a child.
Why? I was so afraid back then, but...
Pant
When I look at Takuma-kun, my heart kind of races...
Mutsumi-san?
Gasp
I'm done buying this.
S-sorry, I spaced out!
Smile
Oh no, this is bad! I got so excited...
I mean, Takuma-kun was just too cool!
Well then, where are we going next?
I-I'd like to go home soon. I want to study.
Huh?
Y-you need to take a break
from studying sometimes!
Menacing
I mean, it's not so much that I want to hurry home,
but I j-just don't w-want to be here anymore!
He doesn't want to spend any more time with me?!
Mutsumi-san?
No way... that's mean... but... I feel kind of happy.
Mutsumi-san?!
A-anyways, let's go hang out somewhere!
N-no. I'm going home!
Ugh. What they hell are they doing?
Well, I guess this is supposed to be a date...
And it's with that same pathetic "lover" ...
In any case...
That woman...
she's got that meat in all the good places...
I want to devour her.
What's that guy grinning at?
Scary...
Are you looking for a seat, ladies?
This table has just opened up.
Ba-dump
I should talk to them and interrupt the date for now.
Come on, let's go somewhere!
It'd be a pain in the ass to level up even more.
N-no, I can't...
But it'd be so much fun!
It'd be a pain in the ass to level up even more.
Huh?
On second thought...
Look, they're doing a live show on the street!
It looks like the show will have
some really good vibes, so...
The idol MUTSUMI-chan is here!
MUTSUMI-chan? For real?!
oooooo
She's in this area!
This isn't the time for a live show!
Find her, guys!
You can get her autograph!
Wh-why is that thing here?
Mutsumi-san, what is that?
It's the akuma, Gjallarhorn...
It's a low-level akuma with no battle ability,
but at any rate, it loves gossip
and when it finds someone's weakness,
it has the ability to rile up everyone around him
and go around causing commotions.
And you can take a picture with her, too!
it has the ability to rile up everyone around him
and go around causing commotions.
And you can take a picture with her, too!
It's commonly known as the "Loud-Ass Bastard!"
A gossip-loving akuma?!
Are you the idol MUTSUMI-chan?!
Just causing a stir won't fail Val love:
"Date with an Idol"...
Uh, well, this is my personal time...
Just causing a stir won't fail Val love:
"Date with an Idol"...
Uh, well, this is my personal time...
but if they talk to me and realize who I am,
then we're out!
What do I do? At this rate, the date that
we worked so hard for will be a waste!
Panic
I can't do this. If those people find us...
Gag...
I'm gonna puke just thinking about it!
I gotta get out of...
I have to do my best for my family.
Someone just booked it outta here!
Get 'em!
T...Takuma-kun?
Th-they'll find us if we stay here.
Let's just run away for now!
Okay!
That's right. I'm going to give Takuma-kun
fun memories of today!
If we keep this up, it's definitely...
They went this way!
Was she with a guy?! I'm gonna murder 'im!
It's definitely going to be a bad day!
But... I can't believe we're being chased by fans
while holding hands with Takuma-kun.
This is kinda... making me really excited!
SPLOOSH
Pant
Okay! If we can get outside through this rear entrance...
Hey, have you found them yet?!
Keep looking!
We're caught here!
MUTSUMI-chan is over here!
Alright! I'm gonna get an autograph!
She's here! She's here!
She isn't here...
Hey you jerk, was that really MUTSUMI-chan?
She is around here for sure!
We immediately hid, but...
What do we do now?!
Ah, but I'm being held by Takuma-kun...
Weak
Hey, did you find MUTSUMI-chan?
She's not over here...
I'm sure she came in through
the rear entrance, though.
Okay, let's look again!
Takuma-kun, are you okay?
You're not feeling bad, are you?
Y-yes. I'll be fine.
Squish
Go find her! I'm gonna murder that guy!
I can't believe things have come to this...
There are so many fans on the other side
of this thin metal sheet separating us.
If Takuma-kun were a rude person, then...
Your chest is huge, Mutsumi-san.
Shall we open the door and let your fans see?
N-no, I'll do anything...
You'll do... anything?
Anything you want!
Mutsumi-san?
Thump
Thump     Thump
Yes?!
Uh... How do you suppose we can
break free of this situation?
Oh... That's what you want to say...
What?! She seems disappointed somehow.
Did I do something wrong again?
Er, well...
I have an idea.
Depending on my sacred sword "wing" level,
it's possible to enhance my flight ability.
Right now I'm still at a low level,
but I think I can at least get through
the people outside instantly.
So, um...
I...
I want you to kiss me.
U-understood.
Hooray! I can finally kiss Takuma-kun, too.
I heard that the first kiss tastes like lemon,
but is it really true?
This is my first kiss...
Takuma-kun, can you bend down a bit more?
H-hold on a second...
There's too much of a height difference
and I can't reach his lips!
Whaaaaaa
Wh-wh-what do we do?!
Takuma-kun, will you unbutton your shirt?
MUTSUMI-chan is in here! MUTSUMI-chan is-
Is that all you can say?!
I've lost sight of her but she has to be around here!
You sure you weren't just seeing things?
Well... I did see a girl running away.
And those giant tits... It had to be MUTSUMI-chan!
No way the guy she was with could be her boyfriend...
If he is, there's gonna be a bloodbath!
When kissing your lover, the conditions for
invocation differ depending on location.
If we're kissing on the lips, then the transformation
will happen instantaneously,
but the further away from the lips we go,
the more time it takes to transform.
Anatomical Kiss Chart
min
sec
The cheek takes five seconds,
and the chest takes three minutes...
the nape of the neck should take about
one minute of kissing before I can transform!
This together with the heat is making my head spin.
Calm down... Times like this...
can be used to study!
Dangerous
Takuma-kun's
Mental Scenery
Study study
Emergency
Gotta study
Take a deep breath, fix your posture,
and start off with math!
Commence review!
Commence review!!
Ow!
T...Takuma-kun? You're stepping on my foot.
Square root of two equals 1.41421356...
Square root of 5 equals 2.2360679...
His face looks more serious than usual...
I get it! This is encouragement for me
to focus more and kiss him!
I'm sorry, Takuma-kun, I'll try even harder!
Hey was she over there?
She's gotta be over there!
Hey, there's something caught over there.
Where the hell is "over there?"
Look, at that locker.
We're dead!
MUTSUMI-chan is over there!
So this is how I die, huh?
My mom is probably gonna be disappointed in Heaven.
After all, I'm probably headed to Hell...
I don't wanna die!
There's only twenty seconds left so calm down!
Takuma-kun is scared...
That's understandable.
He does have a fear of people.
Even if he didn't have that, it'd still be scary.
But even so...
He still helped me.
He could have easily run away by himself,
but didn't let go of my hand.
Not only did he encourage me,
but he gave me such a sweet treat...
Takuma-kun...
I love you.
Ten seconds to go!
Nine, eight, seven...
six, five, four...
three...!
Oh no, we're not gonna ma-
What is that? A spear?
"Kiss with a lover"...
Kiss with a lover
Valkyrie invoked!
Valkyrie invoked
What was that gust of wind?!
This is just a space for cleaning supplies!
Sixth Valkyrie
"Helmwige"
Wing Lv. 6
It's okay now.
Relax, we're floating.
It feels like our date was a success, but...
I'm leaving Takuma-kun with
so many bad memories of today.
Even though he wanted to get home
I was unreasonable and stopped him from leaving.
We were chased around because of that, and...
I was just trying to make fun memories for him.
It's beautiful.
A long time ago, back when that shopping mall
was built, my mom and I came here to play.
All day long we went to different stores,
and we played and ran around and fell,
and ate delicious things...
and we finished the day
watching the sunset from the roof.
The sunset I saw that day looks just like this one.
Takuma-kun...
I'm so glad you're happy!
It felt really good whe...
I had fun!
Yeah...
Wh-what happened?
Um... Since I'm at a low level I may have
already reached my flight limit.
Huh?!
Good grief.
How long do I have to play
bodyguard for this weakling?
Thanks to you, Big Sister Ichika,
we can focus on dating.
I'm truly grateful to you.
Hmph. That's also my mission. I'll be patient.
By the way, can you come to the campus festival?
Everyone besides Shino who has not yet
recovered will be a part of it.
I don't care about that weakling,
but in order to protect my beloved sisters,
I will also participate.
I felt a strange presence today.
Stay alert.
The enemy was approaching a few seconds ago.
So they do have a bodyguard following them.
I was right not to head straight for them.
But this is delicious. I can't just throw this meal out.
I'm going to shoot you, you mutt.
Well, well. You've come too, have you?
How long are you going to slack off?
Do you understand the gravity of your mission?
How about you hurry up and dispose of the Valkyries?
With all due respect,
my meal has not yet been prepared.
Now is the time to enjoy my appetizers.
Would you like to have some too?
The food here is fairly good.
Fenrir has also sent a miserable coward, huh?
Relax.
There's a campus festival coming soon.
That place in particular will be the ideal
hunting ground to devour all of the Valkyries!
Val Love, "Date with a Valkyrie Idol," successful.
Experience Points acquired.
Helmwige Level Up, confirmed.
Date complete.
Date Complete
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
If we don't understand love,
you & I won't get anywhere, you know?
Nine times out of love on cloud nine
We wanna share your heart!
(How do you tell me?)
Input sweet nothings
Failed - Cancelled - They don't resonate at all
(Please don't be shy)
(How to make dream)
Touch me and bring me one
Successful - Complete - Isn't cutting-edge tech great?
(Hold me tight)
Why won't you say romance?
Let's bring it to love!
Get more experience and level up my maiden heart
Up-date! Date! Date! Please, please!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Heart! Heart! Heart! Please, please!
(Please, please show your heart)
I'll teach you that love is a maiden's power!
(Love gave the power to Valkyrie)
Nine times out of ten, they're surely already lovers!
(Please, please up-date my love)
Fluttering in my chest, dance, dance!
(Please, please show your heart)
Your shy akuma mind, kiss for you!
Will completely change, kiss for me!
Let's begin our romance!
Thank you, Itsuyo-chan!
Thanks to everyone's support, I leveled up, too!
I think I can be useful in combat now!
It's natural that an older sister
would worry over her younger sister.
But we're triplets...
You like to stress the
older sister thing sometimes, huh?
It's good your Val love was so simple.
Natsuki said the same thing.
As long as you weren't found by your fans and/or
get stuck in a locker, it was probably a snap.
Y-you're right, it'd be really rough
if those things happened, huh?
Mutsumi?
Next time: "The Serving Maiden."
Next time: The Serving Maiden