That was delicious!
Glad you liked it!
Kururi, want to get in the bath?
Yeah-yuh!
Mutsumi-chan, you hop in too.
Okay.
We all have to do our best
to deal with our disadvantages.
We must eat and rest properly, okay?
Disadvantage?
Were there people stronger than you all in Asgard?
Yes.
Our abilities are the materialization of
the bio-energy "aether," that all life possesses.
You could even call it a "soul."
In Asgard, there are higher-level gods
that possess far more aether than we Valkyries.
To tell the truth, that aether is also the reason that
these akuma are coming to attack Midgard.
The malevolent gods and the main gods in Asgard
have not gotten along for a long time now...
If this keeps up, it seems a huge war
will start amongst the gods.
From here, we will infiltrate the enemy fortress
and kill him in a single strike!
We will exterminate them
without giving them a chance to suffer.
Such is the destiny of the mighty.
As expected of Our Lady.
You may be able to redeem
your sullied reputation with this.
I truly have no words to express
my appreciation for this opportunity, Our Lady.
Now, let us go forth! It's time!
You mongrel.
Be ashamed of the fact that had you
just made sure to kill Einheijer
we wouldn't have to trouble Our Lady with this!
That's some nerve you got,
mouthing off to me at your low social status!
What are you two whispering about?
Shine
Grin
Smile
Not a thing, Our Lady.
I'm certain I tore though Einheijer's stomach.
But you're not considering that a human
would have misteltein, are you?!
Misteltein? What is that?
Are you serious right now?
I'm not interested in anything besides Our Lady.
Misteltein is one of only three pieces
of the Yggdrasil Ea in existence.
Blot
Mokkerkalfe
Misteltein
Misteltein, Blot, Mokkerkalfe...
each of those is an extremely dense
crystallization of aether!
Though we far surpass them in war potential,
what makes us incapable of a full-scale invasion
is the main gods having all three of them
in their possession.
It merely boosts that human's pitiful abilities
to one where he revives the dead.
But this may also be our good fortune!
The precious item that should be sealed in
the treasure room of Valhalla in times of peace
is in a place that is easily within Our reach.
Such ambition! You are so admirable, Our Lady!
I am, aren't I!
But Our Lady, be that as it may, why did Odin
entrust such a treasure to Einheijer, a mere human?
Indeed.
I love and respect my father,
but that alone I fail to understand.
In contrast, this is just as expected of Misa.
It's astounding how she's
ensnared the enemy at such a distance.
You're malevolent gods, right?
If you immediately turn tail and run back to Asgard,
I'll let you escape with your lives.
Among the gods are the full-blooded
and the demigods and goddesses.
Basically, there are two types of demigods.
In the current state, the biggest difference
is that the full-blooded gods
can't use their intrinsic abilities in the human word.
In the three months since the battle
in the human world started,
we've somehow managed to hold out,
but you could also say that it's because the enemy
has prioritized preserving their front in Asgard.
In the real competition there will be
demigods among the enemies as well.
You dare come here alone,
unattended by Einheijer?!
Surely, We have been underestimated.
Take a note, Roskva.
Yes, ma'am.
"One who does not understand one's position
at any given time is a fool."
Make me regret how easy
this instant kill will be, Valkyrie.
Go ahead and kill me, if you can.
Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Sagashita amai negai, kyou mo
Kizuite to, watashi no naka kara
Dare ka ga kimi e to sakebu yo
Mitsumeau, modokashii kyori ni
Abaredashita samishisa
Kamishimeru hitori
Suki toiu omoi o
Iitai demo ienai
Itsumo soba ni kimi ga iru no ni
Mada dare mo mita koto nai
Yume no naka de
Tomoshita tsuyoi omoi
Mayowanai mayoitaku wa nai kara
Shinjite ima, ippo fumidasou
For the sake of myself
Ugh, my dad sucks!
Seriously unreal that he'd send me
to go buy snacks for him at this time.
Snow?
Should you return to Asgard immediately,
your life will be spared.
That's quite generous, isn't it, Valkyrie?
My father ordered me to do my best to not kill.
If any more of us are killed by our own,
it's possible that Asgard would go to ruin.
Don't you all want to avoid that as well?
Destroying Midgard to gain power,
and uprooting the flow of Yggdrasil...
do you know just what consequences
that would bring about?
If you would just shut up and listen...
This is not a massacre; we are the future!
This is the military might that will
lead to the future of Yggdrasil!
There is nothing left to say to you.
Garm, Roskva.
Do a warm-up before we get started.
Ma'am.
Garm?
I see, he's one of them.
There's no need for us to display
our power for a Valkyrie without Einheijer.
Damned with the misfortune of being
born into this world as a daughter of Odin...
Die!
You're... You're the bastard who's been
toying with my beloved sisters, huh?!
Roskva!
Move and I'll kill you.
Don't make me go against my father's wishes.
Wha?!
Good grief. How long do they plan
to keep prattling on?
I suppose that's how Our Lady is...
Now then, what shall I do?
I can't catch that Valkyrie by surprise,
since the instant I get closer I'll be killed.
I have no choice then.
Are you going to return to Asgard
and live a long life, or die right now?
You have ten seconds to decide.
10, 9, 8...
Th-this is alarming!
Could a Valkyrie be that strong
even in her physical body?!
If I can catch her off guard for just a moment...
Our Lady.
Please get away from here on your own.
I will subdue her, even if it's at the cost of my life.
Oh, you two will subdue me?
This won't even take me a second.
Do not worry, Roskva.
You won't need to take this note.
We will never forsake you!
Tis is a complete farce.
I can sense it.
I can sense it
There's a presence sneaking up on me
from my blind spot.
According to my senses, it's a small-bodied man.
Is he the arrow user that Futaba warned me about?
Did they think they could deceive me
with something like this?
I thought I told them...
Move and I'll kill you!
Um...
A... human?!
An opening!
"Kiss with Snorri" confirmed.
Invoking Norn...
Norn
Invoked
Absurd! How can you summon
multiple akuma to Midgard?!
Someone once said:
"A goddess is the symbol of love."
Looks like the tables have turned!
The Third Norn
"Skuld"
Egg Lv. 52
This is the end for you, Valkyrie!
That will not be happening.
Itsuyo!
You were late getting home
so I came out here to see...
If you mess with my family any more,
I'll bind you up, got it?
Bind me up?
Did she always have that many eggs?!
What do I do?
Natsuki-san still can't transform, and Ichika-san
can only move for a second afterwards...
Care to show us, Valkyrie of the chains...
just how long you can hold out?!
No...
We are also wounded.
Let's have today be just our debut.
Next time, we will be sure to kill you.
We are the third Norn, Skuld.
Tremble with fear as you
wait for your death, Einheijer!
Yes... I understand.
Please be careful on your way home.
How was Big Sister Ichika?
The enemies have some demigoddesses
on their side as well.
Seriously?
From here on, we'll make a huge change
in our tactics and respond to the enemy's moves.
Now's the time to make our final push.
We elder sisters must do our best
to support the others.
Right!
And now for our next story.
For the past few days, there have been occurrences
of abnormal weather all over the world.
Even above the skies of Japan we have
already confirmed a record-breaking cold snap,
and according to an announcement
from the government,
they are making efforts to gather experts
to come up with a countermeasure.
This will be a winter unlike any we have seen before.
I brought you breakfast.
Thank you again today, Natsuki-san.
How are you feeling?
Let me see.
Thanks to everyone doing well,
I've been feeling very good recently.
Thanks to your barrier, we've always been protected.
But please, try to take care of yourself, okay?
I appreciate your concern, Natsuki-san.
By the way, this novelization of
the manga was very good.
W-was it?!
This is why I can't stand people like you!
I-I'm sorry!
Is Big Sister Ichika angry?
Yes. Takuma is still as useless as always, so...
He'd be so cool if he could
just get himself together, though.
You really do like the Master, don't you?
What?! N-no, I don't care about him!
I'd also like to meet with the Master soon.
Val Love, "Massage Chest for 30 Seconds,"
accomplished.
We did a good job!
Now, let's see, has she leveled up any?
Has she?
Brunhilde
Spear
Points until next level
Defense:
Range:  Short
Attack:
Special:
She didn't gain any experience points at all.
When Natsuki-chan was doing this
she leveled up easily.
That's because Natsuki's easy.
Most likely, this is because Big Sister Ichika
doesn't accept Takuma-chan as a lover.
What's up, Big Sis Ichika?
Are you still throwing a fit over this?
You said yourself it's too late to change our lover.
I am NOT throwing a fit!
Then will you say "Takuma is our lover" for me?
Say it!
I don't understand why that weakling is our lover.
That wasn't very accepting at all.
How can I accept a fool
who can't effectively use his abilities
even though we're closing in on the enemy?!
Big Sister, I baked an apple pie!
What's this?
Yummy! As expected from my little sister!
Well, we must make sure each of us
are prepared for battle, right?
Right!
Welcome home, Captain, Takuma.
Val Love, "Go Shopping Together," accomplished.
Welcome back. What'd you two get?
Get down to business! Create a six pack
Get BUFF just by reading!
A stupendous book that says you can
get stronger just by reading it!
The dwarves here on Midgar are truly amazing!
30 minutes to a stronger bod!!
THE FLESH BIBLE
Big Sis Ichika, you may have gotten scammed.
Wh-what'd you say?!
What did you buy, Takuma?
Probably a study book or something,
since it's you we're talking about.
Er, uh, yeah. Th-th-that's right.
Well, I'm going back to my room now, so excuse me.
We will now commence our
Norn Response Meeting!
Norn... I once heard a rumor,
but are they honestly that strong?
Basically, in Midgard, based on the specs
of the summoning stone,
the limit is one akuma summon a day.
However, as long the one capable of
creating the akuma has the AP,
they can summon as many as they want.
Most importantly, two years ago the three
Norn sisters took control of Grasil Palace,
and they are a respectable main troop
of the malevolent gods.
We can't take our time with them.
The problem is, we don't know why
the Norn withdrew so quickly last night.
What do you think, Big Sister Ichika?
R-right. Let me see...
I'm a worthless older sister,
to be taken by such a scam...
I-I told you, anyone could fall for that!
Don't worry about it!
Thanks, Misa.
Pitiful
As expected of my little sister...
About how much was it, Sis?
One was 10,000 yen,
and I bought one per person plus the dog...
O-one hundred thousand yen?!
What was going on with Takuma's attitude earlier?
That was way too suspicious!
The Captain told us what she bought,
but he wouldn't...
could he have bought something there
besides a study book?
C-could he really have bought a... dirty magazine?!
That's believable!
Nude World
Super Sexy
I mean, I can't imagine him getting anything BUT that!
And what is this?!
N-no
Nude World
Super Sexy
That's a
scripture
Just a scripture
That's how Dad acted when Mom got angry!
Takuma's dirty magazine...
I wonder if it's the type with the voluptuous girls.
Even though he's not a sociable guy,
Takuma's a boy, first and foremost!
And since he's living in a house surrounded by girls,
of course he'd think about those things!
If he would just tell me, and not rely on
something like a dirty magazine...
No! That isn't what I meant at all, I'm not dumb!
Calm down! I have to calm down!
I'm still not sure if it's an adult magazine...
B-Big Sister Natsuki, that's not...
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
What's going on, everyone?
Hey, it's Takuma!
Takuma, Takuma!
What in the world is going on?!
Actually, Natsuki-chan accidentally drank
Kururi-chan's modification gadget fluid.
If people drink it then they get drunk as a side effect!
Hey, hey, Takuma, listen to this!
Wh-what is it?
Mutsumi's boobies have gotten even bigger.
That's so shameful, huh!
N..Natsuki-chan!
Takuma-chan, I'm sorry but will you put her to bed?
Y-yes I will!
I'll tell you this, Lover!
If you try anything weird
just because Natsuki is incoherent...
B-Big Sis Ichika, hey!
This book is super informative!
I couldn't ask for a better book from Big Sis Ichika!
Thank you for buying this for us, Big Sister Ichika!
That's our Big Sis for you!
I knew it, it's a good book indeed!
Just as expected from my little sisters!
Takuma-chan, now's your chance!
O'course I'm okay!
She's not okay at all.
I have to get her in bed as soon as possible.
Na...Na...Nasuki-san?!
What?
O'course I'm gonna take my clothes off
since I'm going to sleep.
I-in any case, hurry and get under the covers!
What are you doing?
If you really want me to go to bed that quickly
then c'mon and strip me.
Uh...
Er...
I'm done undressing you.
Wh-what's wrong?
Why?! Why aren't you
frantically feeling my boobs up?!
What?!
It's because you like voluptuous girls, huh?
You like huge titties, don't you?!
Why are you suddenly yelling about this?!
I mean,
I don't want you to choose
something like a dirty magazine over me.
A-a dirty magazine?
K-keep calm. This is the perfect opportunity to study!
The founder of the Tokugawa Shogunate
was Ieyasu Tokugawa!
Second in line was Hidetada Tokugawa!
You're such a dummy, Takuma.
I'm here to serve you in so many ways...
Get turned on by me.
The third shogun was Iemitsu Tokugawa!
It feels good to a guy when they're
touched like this, right?
Yakumo told me that.
How's that? Are you excited?
The fifth shogun was Tsunayoshi Tokugawa!
The eighth was Yoshimune Tokugawa!
Takuma, that hurts.
Oh... I-I-I'm sorry!
So that's where you want to touch me.
You pervert.
Do something weird and I'll kill you in a second...
Then the Tokugawa shogunate was annihilated!
Ouch.
I-I-I'm sorry, are you okay?!
Wh-what's that?
Huh? What am I doing?
I'm sure Takuma bought a dirty magazine...
but what am I doing?!
"Get turned on by me"? What the hell?!
I shouldn't be doing something so shameful!
What is he pulling on?
A date magazine?
300 spots
for a day trip
Special advice for a two person date!
Where will we go today?
W-well, uh...
A-actually I was thinking that there were
a lot of things I should study as a lover.
And, er... I'm sorry this is so beyond my capabilities.
You don't need to apologize for that!
I-I see, it was a date magazine.
I-it's nothing!
I'm the one who should apologize.
I'm sorry for being a nuisance.
Th-this is awkward.
You should just confess already.
T-Takuma... um...
Uh, is there someone you're in love with, Natsuki-san?
I don't understand the emotions of love.
I wanted to know what kind of feelings
"love" entails, so I thought I'd ask you.
O-of course, I understand what my role is
as the lover so that's okay!
I meant to ask, did you have a lover
when you were in Asgard?
There is... someone I love!
But that person is a dimwit
who has no interest in romance,
so he doesn't realize my feelings for him,
and he doesn't feel anything for me at all.
The you that put your life on the line
to save me back then...
I want to tell him I love him.
But right now, I'm sure he'd turn me down
if I confessed to him.
I am a Valkyrie.
I am a warrior nourished and made stronger by love.
If he rejects me, I don't know what will happen.
So that's why...
I'm waiting.
Th-that...
sounds kinda rough!
But please don't give up!
O-ouch, Na..Natsuki-san!
Ouch!
This is the plan to store aether
for the Midgard invasion.
Up until now, we've been trying to intercept
all the aether from the main gods.
However, if the barrier known as
the Valkyries were not there,
we would be able to successfully
carry through with this plan unhindered.
Take a note, Roskva.
Yes, ma'am.
Tonight will be the first long-awaited victory for us.
We will kill Einheijer, and acquire the misteltein.
Now then, let us begin the rampant destruction!
Oh dear, this is quite a large family.
Are you ready, Takuma-chan?
Y-yes.
Second Valkyrie of the nine
Valkyrie sisters, Futaba Gelhilde...
will now intercept.
The Second Valkyrie
"Gelhilde"
Castle Lv. 15
Good grief, why is he so...
Did your confession to Big Brother not go well?
Y-Yakumo!
Wh-why would I confess to a guy like that?!
No use hiding it.
Your shrill voice,
the violent throbbing of your heart...
I know about all of it.
D-don't listen to me!
Put on your headphones!
'Kay.
Next time, "The Accepting Maiden."
Next time: The Accepting Maiden
I think Big Brother loves you too,
since you're so cute.
R-really?!
I knew you were easy.