Your Majesty,
we're ready to send our forces
to the demonic continent.
Good. Send aid immediately.
Hurry.
At once!
What will happen to Eclaire?
If another war were to break out...
Setsu is already on his way.
He'll take care of it.
That's who he is.
Episodul 11
Luptând pentru a doua oară cu toată puterea
This magic power...
You're safe now.
Setsu-sama!
Yuki-kun!
Yuki-kun! Yuki-kun! Yuki-kun!
I missed you!
Stop, stop!
Calm down!
Oh, s-s-sorry! I got carried away!
Nah, it's fine.
Sorry to make you wait.
It's okay!
Oh, by the way,
about my training with Master Elka...
Huh?
I'm sorry! I can't do it as well as Master Elka,
but please, have a seat!
Elka...
I don't need another masochist character.
Ow!
We'll discuss this later.
Stand back with Elka and the others.
Be careful, Yuki-kun.
Yeah, I've got this.
Sorry to make you wait.
Setsu the Hero. I've wanted to fight you again.
That magic power... You're the
guy who was at Dezas's place.
I'm honored that you remember me.
However, I am different from that time.
It doesn't seem like you're all talk.
Why do you care about the weak?
What do you mean?
From your point of view, those people
behind you must be like insects.
Does it please you to be the strong
one caring for the weaklings?
Huh? I don't care about crap
like strength or pleasure.
They're precious to me,
so I protect them. That's all.
Being able to enforce your will... I suppose
that's a privilege given to the strong.
This world does indeed need to be destroyed.
Hah! I'll just protect this
world because I want to!
None of you will be getting away!
Not a single one!
Looks like we got lucky, Big Sis.
Yes. Good to see you again, Big Sister Kuroinu.
You!
We know...
that you're not a bad person.
So I think if you can just tell us what's
going on, there'll be no need to fight.
"Big Sister" this, "Big Sister" that!
Your idiotic pretend-sisterhood
makes me sick to my stomach!
So we have no choice but to fight?
If you really think of me as your big sister,
you'll both die without resisting.
Big Sister Kuroinu...
I will protect my big sis
from anyone, no matter who.
Oh, the younger sister seems
much more cold-hearted.
I'm sorry. As a big sister myself,
I must protect Mineko.
Hah! Then I'll shred you
and your stupid sisterhood!
That's the best you can both do?
I'm so glad I got rid of you useless cats!
Mineko!
Yes, Big Sis!
Mineko, follow my lead!
I'm sorry, Big Sister Kuroinu!
It's over.
It's meaningless to keep fighting.
What's meaningless?
You filthy cats...
I'll punish you for your insolence!
Yeah, yeah, how wonderful your love is!
I'm going to puke!
I can't watch this phony sisterhood anymore!
I'll kill you both at the
same time, so thank me!
Limit Break!
Goodbye, filthy cats!
So fast!
Big Sis!
See? That's reality.
Sisterhood has no real value.
It's just a curse.
You'll never understand why my big
sister wants to call you "Big Sister"!
Oh, I understand that it's
a worthless, idiotic curse.
Big Sister Kuroinu...
The only one who thinks that's a curse...
is you, Big Sister Kuroinu!
You don't know anything.
How dare you speak to me that way?
Just die already!
Mineko!
Big Sis!
Beast Merge!
Wha—
This is our secret power.
That's your secret power?
Two useless strays mashed together are stil—
You can tell.
You don't have a chance against us.
Your ears... You're afraid.
Enough!
I am...
Wind Beast!
We destroyed all of the arms on your back.
You can't fight anymore.
Shut... up...
If I give up now...
how will I...
ever be able...
to face them?!
It's revolting...
Sisters who are so close...
Big Sister Kuroinu, did you have sisters, too?
Who knows?
Let's go, Mineko. This battle isn't over yet.
Yes, you're right.
There's only one enemy! Finish this!
What?!
That was a good charge, but...
Still not enough!
Come at me harder!
I, Virdos, invite you to attack me
hard enough to shake me to my core!
What the... How...
What's that?!
Ow! How are you so hard?!
R-Roa Leonaire-sama?!
Zoo Dorado sent me to assist you.
Reinforcements?
I've got this. You can back off now.
What a relief!
Thank you! We owe you!
Oh, I thought it was quite rude
how you suddenly punched me.
So you're actually the Beast King's daughter?
No wonder you feel good!
But that little kitty punch wasn't
the best you had, was it, kitten?
You're as tough as iron, so I guess you
don't just have regular muscle mass.
Correct! You really can tell what's
special about this sexy body!
You're actually made of iron? What a freak.
True. But I was created by humans.
I endured torturous experiments from
a very young age, over and over again.
"Created"?
That said, it did give me this strength,
and that was how I got
Toma-sama to rescue me.
So you could say it worked out.
Shut up!
Toma is the one trying to destroy
the whole world based on a delusion!
And what's wrong with that?
The strong get what they want.
Same goes for those who played with my body.
Same goes for that guy, too...
What was his name? Rouga?
He was one of yours, right?
Attacking in the middle of
our chat? What a brute.
Shut up!
Don't talk about him like
you know anything about him.
That stuff about torture and experiments
made you sound like someone I should pity,
but now I know you've been
messed with in the head, too!
I am Roa Leonaire,
daughter of the Beast King!
For toying with the pride of
the Beastmen, I will crush you!
Iron, steel... Whatever you are,
I just have to keep hitting until you break!
Ugh, idiots are so cute.
I don't need your compassion, anyway.
I'm done. I'll kill you now!
What?!
Did you think my iron body was my only power?
My true power is the ability
to control this body freely.
Like this.
Any shape or size!
Come on! Keep moving!
Oh, dead already? Maybe I went too hard.
Having pride is meaningless in this world.
Wait.
You should be dead.
There's nothing more important than having
pride in protecting what's important!
If I can protect that pride...
I'm willing to risk my life!
I've heard the stories.
Those of the Beast King's bloodline,
moments before their deaths,
burn their lives to take their
enemies down with them!
Then bring it on!
My body will crush you and your pride!
My body will never lose to some
brute who keeps talking about pride!
I win.
It can't be...
It's over!
A Beastman's pride is tougher than anything...
What a fool you are.
How did you...
You're just such a straightforward fool.
Watching you made me want to...
Why is someone like you working with Toma?
Let me ask you this.
Who else would care for a freak like me?
Only kidding. I just like hot guys.
You and your foolish pride should live on.
I'll carry your pride along with me.
Your random strikes won't do any good!
I wouldn't say they're random. Shadow Spike!
You let your guard down, Setsu the Hero.
I'll finish you!
What?!
Dude, don't underestimate me!
What a nonsensical power!
Surely you get it by now. You can't beat me.
Just give up and call for Toma.
I'm tired of playing with you.
I will wager my life in this battle, as well.
Limit Break.
This is my true power, Skia Amur.
A secret power used only in desperation, eh?
If I can defeat you, I'm willing to risk my life.
Here I come!
Not yet!
Meaningless!
This shadow armor absorbs all energy!
The sword of Setsu the Hero is no exception!
You have no chance.
I see.
I'll just slash right through
your precious armor, then!
Flying Sword, Zetsu!
You deflected the slash at the last moment.
Not bad.
Don't move. You really will die.
Death is no issue!
If I lose, I have no purpose!
You live in the light.
You'll never understand!
We were created only to fight.
There is no place for us to live!
Thus, our only salvation is to resist this
world until our last moments and perish!
You idiot!
I was able to fight my final battle
without holding anything back.
For that, I thank you, Setsu the Hero.
They've all lost.
Once again, you stand in my way, Setsu.
But this time, it's really the finale.
Let's close the curtain on this world.
So you show yourself at last, final boss.
Data viitoare
Luptând pentru a doua oară în bătălia finală
Data viitoare: Luptând pantru
a doua oară în bătălia finală.