I've got prime-grade wyvern meat today!
First come, first served!
Leoport, Continentul Semi-Oamenilor
We've got a huge harvest of Cetus over here!
Come on over!
Hey, Shironeko-chan!
What a huge backpack. Are you back from work?
Have some fish.
Thank you.
Hey, Little Miss Shironeko!
Big catch you've got there today, as always!
Take some of our meat, too!
I'm grateful.
Hey, Shironeko-chan.
Don't forget to eat vegetables, too.
You need them to grow bigger.
And don't skip the fruits.
They're great for beauty.
E-Everyone... I feel bad
accepting so many gifts.
It's the least we can do to thank you
for your help with the supply chains.
Kids shouldn't be modest.
Just say thanks and take it all away!
You have to take care of
your little sister, right?
Beastmen look after each other.
Everyone...
Thank you so very much.
I promise I'll repay you.
Hey, Shironeko! Teach me how
to beat up monsters again!
Me, too! I want to be strong like you!
No. Fighting is my job.
Your job as kids is to play.
Shironeko-chan! Have some of our milk, too!
We also have fresh soup, just off the cooker!
I-I appreciate it, but I can't carry any more.
I'm home.
Mineko, I'm home.
Welcome home, Sister.
I see everyone loves you as much as ever.
I'll go hand out the food we can't eat
to the people who need it, again.
Yes, good idea.
Mineko!
I'm sorry, Sister.
I swear I'll make you well.
So you have to do your best, too.
That's a promise.
Yes, I'll do my best.
It's a promise.
Episodul 7
Vizitând pentru a doua oară
Continentul Semi-Oamenilor
Huh? You can't just barge in out of the blue
and expect a boat to be available.
Go away, human.
No, seriously, we have urgent business.
I'll pay you, and we won't complain.
I'll ride on your back if I have to.
I'm not a boat! Just go away!
Well, you heard him.
I guess you'll have to do it.
Did you say something?
I couldn't hear you after spending the
last three days and nights swimming!
Uh, sorry.
You're just the only one I can
rely on for stuff like this.
I pushed you too hard.
You should have said that first.
Well, if you'll let me rest until
tomorrow, I can swim again.
There's a boat available tomorrow.
Oh, for real? Thanks, man.
Could you two read the room a little?!
C'mon, don't be mad.
Let's get something nice to eat
and sleep in a bed for a change!
There's an inn nearby.
Cool. Let's go, Levia.
Thank you, as always, for finding
this expensive medicine.
Don't worry. I'd do this for you anytime.
Besides, I can't help but cheer on a girl
working hard to look after her little sister.
Kuroinu-san, do you have siblings, too?
More importantly, this next
job might be a bit of trouble.
Is this...
an assassination?
If you complete this job,
you'll get paid so handsomely, you'll never
have to work a day in your life again.
With that kind of money, you'll have
no problem paying for medicine.
Kuroinu-san...
You're such a sea god abuser, human.
I'm really craving something sweet now.
Fine, fine.
Welcome. Are you looking for a place to stay?
Yeah. Two people, one night.
Any open rooms?
I'd like a room with a fluffy bed, please.
Oh, and is there anywhere around
here where I can get some good food?
Well, there's a fine diner nearby that
serves traditional Beastmen cuisine.
I want something sweet. Or fish.
Mineko, are you finished?
Yes...
I'm very full.
I'm sorry... After all the trouble
you went through to prepare this...
Sister? What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I have one more job to do today,
so you should go to bed without me.
I think they fell asleep.
Are you still hesitating?
No. I've made up my mind.
Kuroinu-san.
Um...
Can I call you... Sister?
You're the reason orphans like us
were able to survive until now.
And it's not just the medicine for Mineko. It's because you took care of us.
So to me, you're like a big sister.
After we get paid for this job,
I was wondering if the three of us
could live together somewhere quiet.
I thought that might be fun.
That's quite selfish of you.
But I guess...
You can call me whatever you want.
It's not a bad feeling, having a little sister.
Get this job done so you don't make Mineko sad.
I promise I will, Big Sister Kuroinu!
"Big Sister," huh?
Haven't heard that in a while.
Illusion magic?!
That's right.
Not bad.
Setsu!
Are you one of Toma's goons, too?
I don't know who that is,
but I must take your life.
Partial beast transformation!
Huh, that's a cool move.
Here I come!
Wha—
Don't blast that off in the middle of town!
That's dangerous!
Is this curse magic?
Yeah, no doubt.
She must have brought it from somewhere.
Hey, are you awake?
You!
Sister! Stop!
Mineko?
Setsu-san found you unconscious
and brought you back here.
Well, um, thank you for that.
I think I understand your situation.
You do dangerous jobs for
your sister's sake, right?
Just so you know, this isn't an illness.
Break Light.
Wh-What is this?
Cursed Magic.
It's not an illness. It's a powerful curse.
And for it to be this powerful...
Is it Toma after all?
For now, we worry about how to save her.
A curse?! Can Mineko... Can Mineko be saved?!
Please! I'll do anything!
Please save Mineko...
Please...
Leave it to me. I'll save your sister for sure.
This might be a bit unpleasant.
Think you can bear it?
Yes.
Please, go ahead.
Arise, Glutton!
Wh-What is that?
This is my secret trump card.
Glutton, devour this curse!
Mineko! You can do it! Hang in there!
Please don't do that without permission.
Setsu! Watch out!
What?!
Hey, Shironeko!
Not only were you unable to execute
my order, but you protect the target?
She's the innkeeper!
But I can't stop this now...
Setsu the Hero. I, Kuroinu,
will take you into custody.
How insolent of you to ignore me.
Levia!
She's pretty strong. Can you handle her?!
Who do you think you're talking to?
I'm the god of the sea.
Hah. Empty words.
That magic power... There's no doubt.
Why is a sea god working with a human?
Enough chit-chat. Let's get it on already.
Can you, a god of the sea,
wield your power on land?
Your life is mine!
Too bad for you.
Sea water?!
Wherever I am, the sea is, as well!
Answer me.
What is Toma after?
If you answer honestly,
I won't take your life.
Pleading for my life is far beneath me.
Big Sister Kuroinu...
Why would you do this?
Shironeko...
"Big Sister," huh? How revolting.
B-Big Sister?
You pathetic runt, unable to
execute such a simple order!
How dare you call me your sister?!
I've heard enough.
Toma-sama's goal is to become a god
and destroy every species in this world.
We are his faithful pawns.
A god? How could a mere human—
He can! Nobody else but him!
She got away.
Sister!
Mineko?!
Mineko, are you all right?
Yes! I'm fine. I'm fine now, Sister!
Looks like it worked out.
Yeah, thanks to you.
This is the same necklace Dezas had.
Toma is trying to be a god now?
Still a total wack job, isn't he?
But if he's trying to destroy this world...
Yeah. I'll have to stop him,
by punching him if I have to.
I thought we were finally going
to get a good night's sleep,
but last night ended up
being another big mess.
Yeah, what a waste of a good bed.
But now we really do have
to meet with the Beast King.
Yeah. Who would've thought we'd fight side
by side with them for world peace again?
Is that...
Hey, stop over there.
You got it.
If you're going to fight,
please take us along.
The two of us together
would be useful in combat.
If you're going to Regdom,
the royal capital,
you should take a Beastman with you.
I also need to repay you for helping Mineko.
Besides...
I want to see Big Sister Kuroinu
again, and talk to her.
You guys...
It's going to be a tough fight. Are you sure?
All right, then. Shall we?
Yes!
Okay, let's go.
Got it.
Just you wait, Toma.
Data viitoare
Luptând pentru a doua oară într-un duel
Next time: "Fighting a
Duel for a Second Time."