Wow, what an amazing fight!
A kaiju showdown! Freakin' awesome!
Go! Levia!
Setsu! Stop spectating and help!
Invocat a doua oară într-o altă lume
Episodul 2
Prăjind a doua oară un calamar
So, to reintroduce you...
This is Levia, the god of the
ocean and a friend of mine.
You're most fortunate to even
have the opportunity to see me.
You may thank me.
Y-You're really the legendary
god of the ocean?
Wow, amazing...
Hey, Setsu! Why didn't you help me?!
Look at all this!
Well, I assumed you'd be all right on your own.
And I don't get many chances to see an awesome kaiju battle like that.
You call me up suddenly after five years,
make me ferry you over to the
demonic continent, and then that?!
That's pretty terrible!
But, um...
What are we going to do with this?
We can't just leave it here...
We can just let Setsu deal with it.
Huh?! Me?
Inel de calamar
Wh-What is this?! It's delicious!
I haven't had Setsu's deep-fried squid
in a while, but it's not bad.
I prefer raw, though.
Anyway, we've arrived at the demonic
continent safely, for now.
Yeah.
The demonic fishing village
of Volsee is close.
And on the other side of that mountain
is Evilbarrow, the Demon Lord's castle.
The Demon Lord's castle?
Yeah. That's where your package
is supposed to go, right?
I have business with its recipient, as well.
A package, from a human to Dezas?
Oh, yeah, she mentioned sending
the brooch out for repairs.
Huh? Levia-sama, do you know this
Dezastol Serreno person, as well?
Wait, does she not know who Dezas is?
Seems not.
The destination of your package is
the Demon Lord's castle, Evilbarrow,
and the recipient is Demon Lord Dezastol.
Wha—
What?!
D-Dezastol is the Demon Lord?!
Anyway, it's all on foot from here,
so my job is done. Nice working with you.
Aren't you coming with me?
Why would I?
What do you mean, why?
It's been a while, and you know Dezas, so...
I kept my promise and
maintained peace on the seas.
Then, five years later, you finally return,
only to treat me like a boat!
You're even hanging out with another woman,
and that's what you say to me?
Well, that's... I mean...
A lot happened. I couldn't help it.
Is this a lovers' quarrel?
No matter what, the man has to
apologize. Don't you know that?
It seems like this guy doesn't
understand girls' feelings at all.
Say you're sorry.
Here, have some squid rings and go away!
What is this?
Yummy!
Squid rings are awesome!
How is it so crunchy and fluffy?!
Make some for Mom and Dad!
You came at the right time.
There's plenty more kraken left over.
Yay!
We can't just let it rot here!
Pretty lady, thanks for
making up for the no-good man!
Squid rings! Squid rings!
Damn that squid monster!
We can't go fishing as long
as that thing's out there.
Not to mention, the merchants stopped
coming here because of the war.
At this rate, we'll run
out of stored dried food.
We don't have a choice. The whole
village needs to fight that squid!
Um, excuse me.
Can I leave my squid here?
We'll be eating it right away.
The squid monster came back as food?!
Praise Levia, god of the ocean! Hurray!
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
This is our village's finest
drink. Please enjoy.
Very nice, thank you.
This is our signature seafood dish.
It pairs well with the drink.
Not bad... but isn't fish better eaten raw?
This is as raw as it gets...
Here, here! Squid rings from fresh kraken,
caught just this afternoon!
They're the best!
Setsu! Too slow!
Shut up! Don't make me do all the work!
The kraken got sliced up into
little rings straight away?!
What skill!
Yay!
Awesome!
Squid rings!
Take it out, Ruri!
Yes, sir!
Taking it!
Ruri, next batch coming up!
Yes, sir!
Ruri, hurry up!
Yes, sir! Yes, sir!
What?!
The village is on fire?
Have the humans landed on our shores?!
As the head of Demon Lord Dezastol's
personal guard, I, Vlad...
will not let this stand!
Just you wait, human soldiers!
Oh, hey, Levia-sama!
Good work out there!
Hey, are you drunk, too?
No, I'm not.
Yeah, this is just juice.
I told you so!
Anyway, come on, Levia-sama. Let's chat.
Levia-sama, how do you know Setsu-san?
You two seem to know the
Demon Lord very well, too.
Let's see...
If you phrase it like that,
what's the right answer?
Five years ago, Setsu tried to blaze
across my ocean without permission.
I fought him, and then,
he demanded I help him finish
the war and dragged me around.
That was how it started.
In reality...
All the noise of war had me so annoyed
that I went on a rampage,
and he silenced me with one punch...
But hey, technically I didn't lie, at least.
So that's how you met the Demon Lord. I see.
I thought Setsu the Hero
was famous in Distinia.
Huh?
Setsu the Hero? The person who got all
the kings to be friends and end the war?
That was...
What?!
Setsu-san is the Setsu?!
That explains how he knows Levia-sama
and the Demon Lord, and how he's so strong,
but why would someone
like that be my guard?!
I guess Setsu wouldn't talk about
his past without being prompted.
S-So the number of accidents in the
ocean suddenly dropping... That was...
Yes. I promised Setsu that I'd
maintain peace on the oceans.
Yet...
He suddenly disappeared, then reappears five
years later and treats me like a boat!
Don't you think that's pretty awful?
Levia-sama, are you mad at Setsu-san?
Well, I did get to see him again,
so I guess it's okay.
All right! Half off! It's a total steal!
Half off? That's a good deal.
Thanks!
Wow, it's so much cheaper!
Hey, don't push! Get in line!
How much?
You must really love Setsu-san!
No way!
The god of the ocean,
in love with a human? No way.
But I will admit,
I was waiting for him to return.
Everyone, are you all right?!
I, Vlad, head of the Demon Lord's
personal guard, am here!
Humans, you won't get your way!
Huh?
What's wrong, mister?
Want some squid rings?
Squid... rings?
They really are best when they're raw.
Levia-sama.
Again, apologies for my behavior earlier.
But I'm surprised that you're
in town in your human form.
Hey, Vlad, it's you.
That sword, that magic power,
and the squid rings!
I knew it was you, Setsu.
Though it was hard to tell,
given your new form.
Yeah, a lot happened.
Anyway, seeing you,
the Demon Lord's closest officer,
out of the castle at a time like this...
Is it because of the war?
Yes. I was looking for Levia-sama.
I didn't expect her to be with Setsu,
the missing hero, though.
I'm starting to see a ray of hope!
Levia-sama and Setsu!
I, Vlad, swallow my pride to implore you!
Please, save the Demon Lord!
The Demon Lord is being asked to
marry a man named Terran Sneeter.
Marriage? I don't know who that man is,
but isn't that good news?
It's not good at all!
It's being called a marriage,
but in reality, it's subjugation
through a curse.
A subjugation curse?
But Dezas should be able
to shrug off most curses.
Well, he brought a powerfully cursed
necklace instead of a ring.
A curse so powerful that not
even Dezas can resist it...
You know of the war that
started about a month ago,
when the humans invaded us, right?
What? The humans invaded?
You didn't know?
One of the coastal villages was
attacked by soldiers in massive armor.
They even left the flag
of their country behind.
A flag? Of Distinia?
We were somehow able to fend them off,
but they've attacked
several more times since.
The demon lord sent an emissary to the
human nation, but they haven't returned.
Taking advantage of the Demon
Lord's reluctance to go to war,
one man offered to negotiate.
That man was Terran Sneeter.
Oh? So that guy claims he can stop the war?
He does.
Is he really that powerful?
Sounds kinda shady, to be honest.
In a way, he's at the top of
this world, like you are.
Um, Setsu-san, he doesn't mean
Terran himself is a strong fighter.
Terran Sneeter is the world's
wealthiest merchant,
and head of the Terran Trading Company.
Most of the merchant ships at sea are
owned by the Terran Trading Company.
Ah, right, those boorish ships
that are all over the sea.
He has a grip on all of the
money and wealth in the world.
Both we and the humans need the merchants'
help to wage a cross-continent war.
That's why we believe his claims
aren't completely baseless, but...
So Dezas is willing to become a slave,
just to stop this war?
Yes.
What about you?! Are the generals of
the Demon Lord's army okay with that?!
Of course not! We will fight for the
Demon Lord until the last man standing!
Then why—
Because she promised you
she'd maintain the peace.
What a silly woman, clinging to a promise
she made with someone who disappeared.
But that's precisely why...
we can't leave her alone.
Yeah.
You're right.
Let's go!
Never thought we'd be using the same route
we used to launch our surprise attack on the Demon Lord's castle back then.
Yes, this brings back memories.
Here's our welcoming party.
Well, then, you can rely on
me to serve as your escort!
The date of the wedding ceremony
that Terran mentioned is unclear,
but given what the Demon
Lord herself wants to do,
we don't have a moment to waste.
She was never one to back down
once she'd made up her mind.
Also, Terran is surrounded by skilled guards.
The road to the castle is
also crawling with monsters.
Do try to conserve your magic power, Setsu.
You can leave that part to me.
Your words are truly reassuring. Thank you.
I'm taking the shortest route.
Can you keep up?
Who do you think you're talking to?
I'm the god of the ocean.
Well, I'm off, then.
I'll have it taken care of
by the time you arrive.
I'm counting on you, Setsu.
So what's the plan?
For what?
When we get there.
It's obvious.
I'll blow away this stupid wedding or whatever,
and that Terran guy along with it.
But how will you stop the war
without that rich merchant?
I'm actually suspecting he's behind it.
Vlad just said Distinia was the
one that attacked first, right?
But in Distinia, they said
the demons attacked first.
I also saw a bunch of big
armored guys attack,
but that wasn't Distinia or the demons.
Look, this war didn't break out by
pure coincidence like last time.
Someone set it up.
While both sides think
they were attacked first,
some shady dude comes in with
a cursed necklace to sell peace.
How much shadier can it get?
So that Terran fellow is...
I don't know who the true mastermind is,
but I'm sure Terran at least knows something.
In that case...
I guess I don't need to hold back!
Wow, you're a real beast on land, too.
Did you actually get stronger?
This is nothing compared to
what I can do in the ocean.
It's not like I was asleep
the whole time you were gone.
Yes. It's always been like this with Setsu.
We took risks, had adventures...
Until five years ago, I had no interest
in what happened on the shore.
I just spent my time doing nothing
at the bottom of the ocean.
But after meeting Setsu,
after being with him,
I realized how beautiful this world is.
That's why, right now...
Not just because I promised Setsu,
but also of my own free will,
for these peaceful seas,
this peaceful world...
I won't let Dezas take all the attention!
Oh, yeah, one thing...
What now?
Your squid rings are better than raw squid!
In that case, I'll make as many as you want.
There it is! Evilbarrow,
castle of the Demon Lord!
Do your worst, Setsu!
Yeah, count on it!
Data viitoare
Primind a doua oară un cadou
Next time: "Receiving
a Gift for a Second Time."