General!
We're approaching the landing area.
We will begin landing shortly.
Attention! This war is by
order of our great king!
Let us teach those cursed demons
the true power of humans!
I sensed a trace of Toma's magic power.
There's no doubt he's on this continent.
So our true enemy is not
the demonic nation, but...
Toma, most definitely.
But the general and the
others are all riled up.
Even if we tried to tell
them Toma is behind this,
they'd probably just treat us as spies.
But at this rate, we'll start a
pointless war with the demons.
Have we heard from Setsu-san at all?
Yuki-kun is probably doing
his best to stop this war.
To tell you the truth, this is actually the
second time I got summoned into this world.
Second time?
So, to stop this war, I'm going
to go meet an old acquaintance.
If you're going somewhere,
I'm going with you!
I want to go with you!
I promise I'll be useful! So please, I...
No. It's too dangerous for you, Yuhi.
Besides, this is something I have to do.
Then that's all the more reason...
I'm going because I don't
want to put you in danger.
I trust Yuki-kun!
So what we should do is...
Buy time until Setsu-sama arrives, I guess.
Yuhi, in this war, we have to prevent
casualties as much as possible.
You can do it.
Believe in yourself.
Right!
Let's win back the peace we once had!
Yes!
Yeah!
Episodul 10
Ajungând pentru a doua oară pe câmpul de luptă
Charge!
Aim!
Fire!
Listen! We will circle around the
flank and strike the enemy!
Right!
Magic soldiers! Fire!
Target: enemy encampment! Charge!
Here they come!
Don't let them set foot in our camp!
Now! Go, go!
Go, go!
For the kingdom!
Defeat our enemies!
Listen. Don't go chasing after
fleeing or injured enemies.
We'll wait for the enemy to focus
their attention on the front,
then charge through in one go.
R-Right.
Okay, let's go!
We're under attack!
Wh-What should I do?!
We just have to fight!
Yes, get them before they get us!
Yeah! Let's do it!
Hey, everyone!
Wait! Don't leave me!
What?!
I've got you!
Are you all right?
Yuhi-chan! Sorry! I'm so sorry! I got scared...
I couldn't do anything...
Don't apologize. I'm scared, too.
Just don't push yourself too hard, okay?
Yeah...
Retreat!
I did it... I did it, damn it!
This is war. I have to kill...
Don't blame me for this.
No!
Wh-What are you saying, Hanabashira?
That person can't move anymore, right?!
So...
Why'd you stop me?!
It's kill or be killed!
Th-That's what war is, right?!
So it's okay to kill someone
who's hurt, who can't fight?!
That's wrong!
How noble!
But you need to end their lives...
or this is what will happen!
That's...
From back then...
Who are you? Which squad—
Damn it! More enemies!
Kill them!
Are these reinforcements?
Good, we can push back the—
Ice Flower!
This is bad. Everyone's lost their cool.
Hey, Glein, are they perhaps...
Yeah... They seem to contain people.
How awful...
That red-haired swordswoman, she's—
No, it can't be...
There's no doubt. That swordswoman is...
Alizee!
What, you know her?
Oh, I guess you were all
in Setsu's party together.
What did you do to Alizee?!
She was powerful, so I turned her into a doll!
A doll?!
Why don't you become my puppets, too?
Then you can all stay together forever.
I know!
Let's form a puppet party!
Okay?
Enough!
Elka!
Marionette Magic.
Alizee! It's me, Elka!
Don't you recognize me?!
Alizee!
You two can deal with this.
Wh-What is she doing?
That's not just regular blood.
It's concentrated magic power.
So she must be...
Sorry, I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Melluar, the monster master.
Nice to meet you.
And also, goodbye.
Take care of that, too.
Pierce them, Icicle Drop!
Flying Sword, Slash Blossom!
It's not over yet! Get 'em!
There, three down.
Thanks, Thea.
I'll finish Melluar.
You two, take out the other monsters!
Thanks for waiting, everyone!
Now what? All of your toys are gone.
What's wrong with you?!
No modifications, no drugs? No fair!
It's not fair...
Damn it! Kill, kill, kill!
Alizee! Kill them!
I'm sorry, Alizee.
Alizee!
Oh, no!
I have pierced your magic organ. It's over.
That's the price you pay for
toying with people's lives.
I-I can't die...
For Toma-sama...
For Toma-sama!
Impossible! How can she stay alive
without her magic organ?!
Her magic power is rising...
My body has been modified.
I have one extra lung,
heart, and magic organ.
I know, I'm a freak.
We were created as weapons.
No! No more experiments!
Someone help me!
No... No!
No more!
If Toma-sama hadn't saved me then...
That's why, to destroy this damned world...
I have to fight for Toma-sama!
Here I go! Limit Break!
"Limit Break"?!
It allows the user to surpass all limitations.
But the price is...
Wh-What's that?!
Chimera...
It's showtime!
Perfect Marionette Doll!
She's fueling her magic power
with her own life force and hatred.
Now, everyone... Please die for us!
He's wonderful, isn't he?
My number one toy!
Are you sure you want to dodge this?
Yuhi!
R-Right!
Not bad!
But how much longer can you stand it?
This is tough...
Thea-san!
Elka, do you have a plan?
Glein!
Oof, that's rough.
But I have to break it all!
If this world won't love me...
Say your praye—
Alizee...
Amelle...
Amelle, this is a nice village.
The food is good, and the villagers are kind.
I'm growing a bit tired of traveling,
so once this issue is settled,
I'd like to stay here for a while.
Oh, please do! This house is
too big for me to live in alone.
So, during that time,
you can treat me as a sister.
Would you really be my big sister?
Sure. I mean, if it's okay with you.
Of course, Big Sis!
It's all empty now.
The healing magic is working.
Her injuries are serious,
but she will survive.
Yes, I'm truly glad.
Welcome back, Alizee.
I didn't expect her to be so strong.
We all need to take a break...
Shadow.
So they got Melluar.
More enemies!
Now, of all times...
He seems really strong.
Seems tough for us right now.
I'll fight here!
Everyone, please stand back!
No, Yuhi!
He's too much for you! Step back!
Still!
Didn't you tell me that I'm one of you, too?
Besides...
If Yuki-kun was in my place,
I think he would fight.
Yuhi...
Right. Let's leave this to Yuhi.
She's in much better
fighting shape than we are.
Glein is right.
We'll trust Yuhi and provide backup.
If you give up, I'll never forgive you.
Right! Please see how my training's paid off!
You seem quite the competent fighter.
This magic power...
You did well, Yuhi.
You're safe now.
Yuki-kun!
Data viitoare
Luptând pentru a doua oară cu toată puterea
Next time: "Going All-In for a Second Time."