What's wrong, Roa?
Is that the best the Beast
King's daughter can do?
You...
I won't accept you as my master!
Uh, I never said I was gonna be your master...
Even if you're the hero who saved the world!
Even if my dad accepted you!
You won't ever be my master,
unless you beat me!
Yeah, yeah.
Bring it on, then. Dueling is the
way of life for the Beastmen, right?
What, you're not gonna make a move?
O-Of course I will!
I'll wipe that smug look off your face!
Take this!
Good. You've got guts!
Episodul 8
Luptând pentru a doua oară într-un duel
Regdom, capitala regală
And why should we wait to be invaded?!
We should simply overpower
both the demons and the humans!
That's what I mean when
I say you're being thoughtless!
Yes! We must first think
about protecting our people.
That is where the pride of the Beastmen is!
Silence, cowards! There is no
pride in such spinelessness!
How dare you?!
Even if we were to fight,
we must prepare first!
If they attack us first, it'll be too late!
Who are you to speak of pride?
Don't you have any trust in our forces?
Roa.
We should simply strike first
and thwart their advance!
Yes, Dad?
Be right back!
Then we shall settle this with our fists!
Who could ever agree to your scheme?!
My thoughts exactly. A duel!
Like I said, I know Regulus!
I'm here on important business!
How can we trust a human who calls our
king by his first name during wartime?
We'll let you walk away. Now leave!
He is our master.
Please let us through!
N-Not that he's actually accepted us yet,
so we're just candidates for now, but...
Who are you?
What does it matter if
he's your master? Go away!
That didn't work at all.
Aw... I thought we were
getting pretty famous.
Ugh, what a pain in the ass! Maybe I'll just
leap in from here like the last time...
Setsu!
This scent, this presence...
Your appearance is a bit different,
but it must be you, Setsu!
Yeah, you haven't changed, Roa.
Roa, the Beast King's daughter?!
Roa Leonaire-sama?!
I missed you, Setsu!
You're so strong, as always!
I didn't expect any less
from my future master!
Like I said, I'm not going
to become your master.
What's wrong? Are you being shy
because it's been so long?
No!
Is she really the Beast King's daughter?
Yes.
I heard you vanished after the peace
treaty signing, so I was worried.
What took you so long? If you're back,
you should have come straight to me!
Sorry about that. A lot happened.
P-Please, you two! We're in public!
I'm jealous.
Nothing changed over the last five years.
Setsu!
I missed you, Setsu!
Regulus!
Strong as always, Setsu!
I expected nothing less from
the hero who fought by my side!
I keep telling you, I'm no hero!
We just saw this moments ago, didn't we?
Seems you haven't changed, either.
Speaking of change, Setsu,
you look very different.
But this scent... This presence!
You're definitely Setsu.
It's Setsu!
No kidding!
It's great to see that Setsu is back!
We must hold a feast!
Wait, no. Only fists can
communicate this feeling.
Let us fight a duel!
A party before the feast!
That sounds like fun,
but I actually have some pretty
urgent business to discuss.
About the war taking place between
the humans and the demons?
Yeah. Toma is alive.
He's behind all of this and
plotting to kill everyone.
I can't sit idly by after hearing that,
nor can my nation of Zoo Dorado.
No.
Toma might try to start something here, too.
Yes.
It would be best if Regulus could
stay here and provide backup.
I guess I have to go instead of my dad, huh?
Right, Dad?
Indeed, Roa is the best replacement for
me in terms of both ability and rank...
But I still think I should be the one to—
Please wait, my king!
Both humans and demons
are our natural enemies.
Given that our nation is at risk as well,
there is no way we can spare any
manpower for the other nations!
Who's this?
I am Rouga, Commander of
the Zoo Dorado Army, and...
fiancé of Roa-san!
Rouga does have a point,
but this is Setsu the Hero, my comrade.
The same "hero" who has been
missing for five whole years!
How can we know for certain
that he is still on our side?
Don't be an idiot!
Of course Setsu can be trusted!
He's my future master, after all!
But he left you for five whole years!
Just because he decided to come back
doesn't mean we can just give you up now!
Both sides have a point.
So, what do we Beastmen do to
determine whose opinion to go with?
Setsu the Hero!
On my pride as a Beastman,
I challenge you to a duel!
Yes! I, Beast King Regulus,
will officiate this duel!
The winner shall be betrothed to Roa!
Uh, this was never about
anyone marrying Roa...
I'll be waiting for you at
the arena, noon tomorrow.
Prepare yourself for your demise.
Good luck!
Sorry, Setsu. Beastmen are hard
to convince any other way.
You just had to go and make
this even more annoying.
That said, we Beastmen
are easy to understand.
You win the duel, you get your military
support and Roa. Two birds with one stone.
Setsu is the only master for me.
Please help me convince Rouga.
Ugh, fine.
When all's said and done,
you're such a nice guy, Setsu.
We also have a reservation
to make Setsu our master...
Huh? M-Me, too?
Let's not complicate matters further, okay?
Rouga, you got a moment?
Roa-san.
I'll be straight with you.
Setsu is on a whole other level.
You don't stand a chance.
I'm a warrior myself.
I don't have to fight Setsu the Hero
to know the difference in our abilities.
But...
As a Beastman, and as a man,
there are times when I can't back down.
Rouga...
Besides, I do have some chance of winning.
An Eastern mage gave this to me.
It's a magic rune that converts
strong will into strength.
A magic rune?
Perhaps the Beast King would tell me
I shouldn't rely on these things,
but if that's what it takes to protect you,
I won't hesitate to sacrifice
my life or my pride.
Even at a time like this,
you won't look at me.
That's the reason why I never fell for you.
Get him, Rouga!
Show that human what the
Commander of Zoo Dorado can do!
Go, go!
Don't let him beat you, Setsu!
Setsu-san! Good luck!
Arena din Regdom, capitala regală
Whoa, this turned into a whole thing...
We Beastmen do love festivals.
Go knock him out, future master!
Ow! What was that for?!
It's a Beastman's good luck salute.
I don't need that. This'll be an easy win!
The match ends when one fighter can
no longer fight, or surrenders!
Place pride in your fists!
Ready yourselves for battle!
Now, the battle for the right to
marry my daughter Roa Leonaire...
will begin!
Too slow!
You're faster than I expected.
Got you! Flying Claw!
There.
Come on, show me your full power already.
What's the point in dilly-dallying?
You will regret this!
Beast Transformation!
Setsu, don't let your guard down!
Rouga's transformed form makes him several
times stronger than his previous—
And... Bam!
Seriously?! He's destroying him!
Overwhelming Rouga so easily
after he transformed...
Wow...
Awesome! Setsu, you're the best!
I love you!
Even with a different look,
you're still the best!
Isn't that enough, Regulus?
Future master, you're awesome!
There's no point in going any further!
I'll buy you dinner later!
Marriage aside, just let
me borrow Roa for now!
So awesome! So great!
Enough of your nonsense!
This isn't over—
I don't want to hurt your
Beastman pride any more.
Know when to quit.
I'm not even worthy of being
defeated by you? Is that it?
Is it despair?
Is it jealousy of a superior being?
I... I'm...
Is it hatred of your powerless self?
Take this!
Good. You've got guts!
There!
This isn't over!
Come on, bring it!
I am... I am...
There's something wrong with his opponent!
This bad feeling...
I cannot... ever... allow myself to lose!
What is this power?!
That's Toma's curse!
Setsu! Watch out!
No! Evacuate the audience!
That's some incredible power.
But gaining so much strength
from a curse would surely...
Setsu! Use this!
Kill! Kill Setsu!
I need to settle him down!
Damn it! He can regenerate, too?!
Rouga! The duel is canceled! Stop it!
Die! Everyone die!
Watch out!
Don't be so careless!
That curse could transmit to you!
Then the least I can do is finish him myself,
as a proud Beastman warrior!
No, he's just temporarily being
controlled by the curse.
I don't want him to die!
You have a plan?
Yeah. But it's a big risk,
given the strength of the curse.
I'll be defenseless while I do it, so...
No problem. I'll protect you, no matter what.
Arise, Glutton!
Devour this curse!
Oh, no! I can't let this weakling bother Setsu.
Roa-san... Roa-san!
Long time no see, Setsu. I missed you.
Toma, you...
Are you mad?
I had to stop him. He was going to make
you waste your precious magic power.
I'm sorry. I should come see you in person,
but I can't go there right now.
I always believed you'd come back,
so I'm glad to see you again.
Was it you?! Did you trick
Rouga into doing this?!
Stop, Roa! Don't approach Toma,
even if he's an illusion!
Filthy female.
Don't interrupt my conversation with Setsu.
Stop, Toma!
Oh, so you'll do that?
You'll point your sword at me
for some lowly female Beastman?
Again, you'll protect
someone other than me, huh?
You promised! Yet it's always someone else!
Fine, then. Even so, I'll make you happy, Setsu!
I'm the only one who can make you happy!
All the unnecessary stuff—humans, demons,
Beastmen—I'll kill them all for you!
Once the whole world is tidied up,
Setsu and I will live a quiet life as gods!
Sounds wonderful, right?
Cut it out, you yandere idiot!
I don't care what you have planned.
If you're gonna hurt innocents...
I'll cut you down again.
You really are pointing your sword at me.
Yeah, I guess that's how
"Everyone's Hero" should behave.
Distinia's invasion of the
demonic continent has begun.
The world has been set in motion.
Can you make it here in time from there?
Can you protect everyone, "Hero" Setsu?
I'm glad you're well, Setsu.
I'll finally win you over this time.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have approved this duel...
It's not your fault.
But we can get sentimental later.
Now isn't the time to sulk.
Yes, you're right.
We'll head over to the demonic
continent right away to stop Toma.
Right. I'll arrange a ship for you right away.
Our Zoo Dorado army will make preparations
and follow as soon as possible.
Yeah. I'm counting on you!
Are you all right, Roa?
Who do you think you're asking? Of course I am.
We can get sentimental later.
We have things to take care of.
Yeah, you're right.
Watch me, Rouga.
Data viitoare
Invocat pentru prima oară într-o altă lume
Next time: "Summoned to Another
World for the First Time."