Please listen to today's confession.
My friend is a demon lord but is living a frugal life.
Studio rental, guitar maintenance, fliers...
I don't have enough money,
You have a long way to go.
Be-Belial-sama!
Welcome.
Uhm... what do you mean?
You don't have enough charm.
Very well, I will make an exception and teach you the special technique of the Byrnedale family.
Just for you.
You'd go so far for me? Thank you!
First is this.
Clothes?
Yes.
Look carefully.
This is the Byrnedale money saving technique!
The Flash!
You don't look very different then you usually do.
Exactly!
Yes?
You don't need anything more in summer.
This has beneficial effects for both your diet as well as romance.
The proud seraphs all dress like this.
Really?
It's a little embarrassing.
Coming!
Wait! You're going to answer like that?
I am.
I know!
Do the live show like this as well.
It's a perfect opportunity.
Two birds with one stone.
Yes, you should do that.
Like hell I can do this!