Please listen to today's confession.
My friends are actually really stupid.
Today is the day I beat you.
The battle is on.
This is not the season for a beach flag battle though.
This is an ancient battle tradition for the Byrnedale line.
The one who pulls the buried mandragora first
and makes it scream wins.
Do you understand?
On your mark!
Why are we doing this on slippery ice?!
Do you have a problem with that?
This is the way Byrnedale battle!
That's just stupid, and so are you!
You're the last one to say that!
What the hell are you doing?!
What have you done, you shameless fallen angel?
There's always a scene like this in cat fights, right?
Fine.
Bring it on!
This isn't the Byrendale way, but I shan't lose!
Wow!
The view counter is going higher and higher!
I might be able to use this for new subscribers.