Please listen to today's confession.
My friends are demon lords, but they play party games in their underwear.
Mamo-chi, Beli-chi, let's play a game!
The winner gets a reward.
Oh my, in that case I shall participate.
Then I shall as well.
As the leader of the Sins I must prove my worth.
Alright!
Asobimashou!
Mamo-chi, right hand red.
It's still pretty easy.
Beli-chi, left hand blue.
Here?
This might be difficult.
I can still do this...
Beli-chi, right foot green.
How could I, the ruler of Hell, the most beautiful, lose?
Mamo-chi wins!
Now you fight me!
Oh my, I hope the rewards doubles.
Right hand green.
Left hand yellow.
Left hand blue.
Right foot green.
That's not fair.