Please listen to today's confession.
My friends really hate to lose.
The fact that you are trying to become a deadly sin is laughable.
I'm going to teach you the power of a real deadly sin.
That's rich coming from a woman wearing a maebari.
Pathetic.
Don't blame me for what happens if I get serious.
This battle is amazing!
I can't take it anymore!
Then let the maebari decide this battle!
What the hell?!
Tug of war of hell.
You pull on the string attached to the maebari without using your hands.
The one who loses the maebari is the loser.
By the way, apparently when it comes off, you will feel hellish pain.
Go! Go! Onee-sama!
Do your best, Belial-sama!
Not bad, you arrogant woman.
You too, maebari woman!
I'm out...
Onee-sama!
Huh? What happened?