Hey, Master. I didn't think I'd get
to see you again in this life.
I didn't think you were still alive, Girart.
Well, yeah.
I don't know why I'm still kicking either.
We've got a lot to talk about,
but let's start with introductions.
Meet the current king of beasts, Wolfgang.
And his daughter, Cuore.
These two are my confidants.
My right hand, Van Ku,
and my left hand, Rajim Dolk.
I'm Shin. Maybe you've already heard,
but I'm a high human.
It's nice to meet you.
You can talk like you normally do, Master.
Then talk to me like you normally do!
You've never called me "Master" before.
We haven't seen each other in so long.
Let me have my fun.
Besides, it's the only way
to put them at ease.
What?
You know how crazy high humans are.
To the people of this world,
high humans are legendary beings
to be feared and revered.
Hey, are you still alive?
Couldn't be better.
How many did you kill?
A hundred? A thousand? Maybe more.
The moment of truth is still to come.
I'm raring to go.
Good.
Watch my back.
I thought we were dead men back then.
Right? I'm amazed we both came out all right.
How many did we end up slaying?
I don't remember.
Right?
Speaking of things that have happened
in the last five hundred years...
Schnee told me all about
how you founded a nation.
Hey! You went and spilled the beans?
I was going to brag about it.
Knowing you, I figured you would exaggerate,
so I provided an objective account
of my observations.
What?!
I believe it.
I'll go make some tea.
Sure. Thanks.
I guess the tales of my heroism
will have to wait.
Tell me about you instead.
Well, I've told Schnee, but the truth is...
I see. No wonder I couldn't find you
no matter how much I looked.
Sounds like you've gotten yourself
into some strange trouble.
You're telling me.
The silver lining is that it's not all bad.
Yeah... You're right.
At the very least,
this is a great thing for me.
Girart?
Let's get down to business.
Shin, there's something I have to tell you.
What is it?
I'm going to die soon.
What?
I don't have long to live.
I probably have less than a month left.
How do you know?
I've felt something was off
for a few weeks now,
but when Schnee told me about you,
I was certain.
It seems time has begun flowing for me again,
as though it were waiting for your return.
If there are gods in this world,
perhaps they heard my prayers.
Your prayers?
Duel me, Shin.
I want to fight you.
Girart, do you intend
to die in battle, as a warrior?
I can't help but wish for it, Shin.
I want to duel you, the strongest warrior.
How effective are my fangs
against someone so superhuman?
Very well. I accept.
Have you told Wolfgang and the others?
About my life expectancy, yes.
I haven't told them about the duel yet,
but I won't hide it.
I intend to tell them.
That said, I think Van and Rajim
have realized what I want.
Your brothers-in-arms?
Yeah.
Since you disappeared, we've fought together.
They're two of the longest-lived
types of beasts.
They've followed me this whole time.
But we're all getting old.
It's time this nation
was freed of our influence.
I heard Wolfgang is an exceptional ruler.
He is.
He listens to the people and can walk
shoulder-to-shoulder with them.
He's already a fine replacement for me.
Any regrets?
Only that I haven't dueled you.
I see.
There's something I must tell you.
I've found the place where I'll die.
What?
What do you mean by that?
I've told you how long I have left.
I've asked Shin to duel me
before my time's up.
The duel will take place one week from now.
I see.
So the time has finally come.
Yeah. My unfulfilled wish
is finally coming true.
Very well.
How... How are you all so calm?
You're going to...
I've lived a long life.
I've watched companions fall, their sons die,
and even cared for their grandchildren
on their deathbeds.
Why have I lived all this time?
In one week, you'll learn the reason.
I want you to see it happen.
Very well.
We'll fight in the Raluah Forest.
It will be the final
and greatest battle of my life.
I want all of you to witness it.
Yes, Your Majesty!
A duel, huh?
Just when I finally got to see you again...
Shin?
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I'm okay.
Shin, I admired you.
When you disappeared,
I was filled with regret.
A single, tremendous regret.
The world was bland without you.
I'd given up on my wish,
thinking it would never come true.
Thank you, Shin.
I've restored them to perfect condition.
Now you can fight your heart out.
Hey!
Feels like the clock's turned back!
Thank you, Shin.
Don't worry about it.
Tomorrow's finally the day.
Yeah.
Shin, I know I should
mind my own business, but...
What is it?
Is this about Schnee?
Yeah.
If you find a way to go home,
will you return to your world?
Will you leave Schnee behind?
I'm going home.
That's the reason I've kept fighting.
I see.
Sorry.
No, I should be the one apologizing.
I shouldn't have asked.
It's a difficult thing.
If only there were a way to solve
everything at once, for me and for Schnee.
You used to call yourself something
whenever you were in trouble...
An opportunist, was it?
Yeah. I wanted everything to go my way
and reach a happy end
where we lived happily ever after.
That's not something
we'll ever get to experience.
Seriously.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
Yeah.
It's the perfect day for a duel.
Right? How are you feeling?
I'm ready anytime.
My body and mind are raring to go!
We will wait here.
If any stray attacks go flying,
I'll need you to stop them.
I will. Don't worry about anything,
and fight to your heart's content.
Got it.
I will leave Girart in your hands.
Yeah.
Um...
We'll see you later.
Good luck, Shin!
I'll be back.
The rest is up to you.
Good luck.
I'll never forget your teachings
as the first king.
You can trust me
with the kingdom and its people.
Yeah.
I...
I'll also...
I'll also become a warrior worthy
of the first king's bloodline.
Good.
Shall we go?
Yeah.
I haven't seen the king smile
like that in a long time.
He's grinning like a child.
Let us witness the first king
realize his wish together.
Right.
Ready?
Anytime.
It's begun.
Shin!
Girart!
Your blows are as heavy as ever!
Don't act like you can't shrug them off!
Doesn't this remind you
of five hundred years ago?
It feels like just yesterday for me!
Of course!
Same for me!
Incredible.
I had no idea the first king was this strong.
They should be done warming up soon.
His warm-ups are always quite the spectacle.
That's our king.
You mean that's still not their full power?
Of course not.
Master, you're as strong as them, right?
Even I would struggle against Girart.
But that still means she's stronger...
This is a battle between
a high human and Girart.
We must sear this into our eyes.
Even the techniques I developed
to fight you are useless.
I'd expect no less from my master.
Don't play dumb.
I know you're stronger than this.
Yeah. I'm going to put everything
on the line now.
Hear me. Watch as I become...
a single fang!
Shin.
I know how you feel.
I'll fight as hard as I can tomorrow.
But I won't use the titles I acquired
from defeating the final boss.
Relying on such unfair abilities
wouldn't be cool.
If I were in Shin's position,
I would've done the same.
But even if this is over
in the blink of an eye,
I want to fight Shin at full power.
This is the only moment
my fangs can reach you!
Here I come!
Too slow!
You didn't think you could
beat me with this, did you?!
Of course not!
He's coming.
My ultimate technique...
Legendary Excellence!
That's a pretty tough one!
Eight Flower Palm!
Twin Flying Springs!
He's chaining different skills together.
He must've trained incredibly hard
to develop this strategy.
Pathetic. He's risking his life, while I...
I'm sorry, Girart.
I haven't been fighting at full strength.
That's the spirit!
Legendary...
Excellence!
Heavenly Haze!
It will be over soon.
Gotcha!
Girart?
Girart!
I hear you.
Looks like this is the end.
You got me at the end. I'm impressed, Girart.
I haven't lived five hundred
years for nothing.
This fang landed a blow on you.
My long-awaited wish has been fulfilled.
Shin, as a reward for landing a blow on you,
will you do something for me?
What is it?
I'm glad I got to fight you at full strength.
But there's more, isn't there?
I had no idea you were so powerful.
Farewell.
Girart...
See you later.
Yeah... That's my master, all right.
It's over.
Girart!
Raise your heads.
Your king scored a hit on me, a high human.
That means Girart ascended to our level.
Girart...
Behold the king's face.
He looks satisfied.
Not a single regret.
You're right.
Yeah. He'd laugh at us if he saw us crying.
Schnee?
You look like you're about
to disappear somewhere.
I'll do anything.
If there's anything I can
do for you, please tell me.
I know.
I know this is what Girart wanted.
Yes.
I accepted that and fought him.
But...
Yes.
It hurts to have a friend die.
You fulfilled your duty, Shin.
You can cry now.
It's okay to be sad now.
Next Time
Episode 9
The Queen of Bayrelicht