So... why are you dressed like that?
Since elves stand out, disguising
ourselves as beasts allow us to blend in.
These are amazing!
They act like the real thing once equipped.
You called them cosplay items, did you not?
They have the ability to conceal
the traits of one's species.
Er, yeah, that's right.
I never dreamed stuff I mostly made
for a laugh would come in so handy.
By the way, Shin, what do you think?
Of what?
Do they look good on me?
Oh, yeah. You look great.
W-We're going to see Schweid, aren't we?
Let us hurry.
I've never seen her like this before.
Me either.
That aside, I didn't think
I'd get to see him here.
Kilmont is an allied nation of Farnid.
And representing them at the funeral...
was my former support character
Schweid the high dragnir.
Representatives of the various
nations are staying here.
Is Schweid a monarch like Girart?
No. Though he was the first emperor
of the Dragon Empire, Kilmont,
he's cut ties with the imperial family.
Ever since Kilmont stabilized,
he has been living at his leisure.
I'm surprised the people accepted that.
The second and current emperor
was originally meant to be the first,
but he was injured during
the nation's founding.
So Schweid was just a stand-in, huh?
I shall fetch Lord Schweid. Please wait here.
I have a meeting to attend,
so I will be on my way.
Please let Cuore know if you need anything.
You are dismissed.
Uh, long time no see?
I am delighted that you have returned.
I shall serve you once more
and be the spear that pierces your foes.
Ah, right. He's that kind of guy.
Listen, I'll tell you what I told Schnee.
We finally get to see each other again.
Let's take it easy, okay?
However...
Schweid, if Shin says it's okay,
then it's okay.
Not "Master," but "Shin"?
That's different.
Yes.
Very well. If that is how things are,
I shall conduct myself at ease.
By the way, Schnee,
why are you dressed like that?
To suit Shin's tastes.
Could you not give him the wrong idea?
I see. So Girart passed on a satisfied man.
That sounds just like him.
A warrior until the very end.
So, Shin, what will you do now?
I've researched all I can
at the libraries here,
so I'll hit the sacred place next.
I will be returning to Kilmont.
Allow me to join you after that.
It's been a while since we partied up.
Indeed. We can use telepathy
to keep in contact.
Welp, we'd better get going.
Oh, that's right.
It can't be! Is that...
Yup. It's your personal weapon, Nagizuki.
It's been ages since I held it last,
but nothing could feel
more natural in my hands.
I took care of the maintenance for you.
See for yourself.
Impressive work.
Though it seems more powerful
than the Nagizuki I know.
You can tell?
My mana control has improved
since I repaired Girart's equipment.
Thanks to that,
she's now five times stronger!
Your abilities have grown
in such a short time?
That's incredible, even for you.
I'd like to get my adventurer
rank up to around C.
This will do.
Goblin slaying?
We can do this as a day trip.
Um, would it be all right if I joined you?
I don't mind, but are you sure?
Yes. I'll take care of my
remaining work once I return.
Work?
I'm investigating the Raluah Forest
where you held your duel the other day.
To make sure it's regrowing properly.
Mind if I tag along?
What? You could, but...
Since I was part of that duel,
I want to check it out.
In that case, I'd love to have you.
We'll each take one. Got it?
Roger!
And that's one job done.
Incredible. We made a mess of this place,
but it's already back to normal.
We're going to examine the regenerated trees
and look for anything unnatural in the area.
If you spot any unusual herbs growing,
please pick them.
Let's see...
We finished the job.
Mind confirming it for us?
Very well. Also, I have a message for you.
What is it?
It's from Barlux, guild master
of our Bayrelicht branch.
Barlux? Isn't that...
I've been summoned
by the palace in Bayrelicht.
It says to head there as soon as possible.
What does the palace want with you?
Don't ask me.
You don't have any ideas?
None.
Well, okay, maybe one.
I might have to take care of this
before working on my rank.
I'll join you.
So will I.
I wish I could go with you,
but I can't leave the country.
Don't make that face.
There's something I want to give Wolfgang.
Could you let me know when he's free?
You have something for my father?
Father, do you have a moment?
Shin wishes to speak with you.
Show him in.
Sorry to interrupt.
Don't be. This is also part
of my kingly duties.
Now, more importantly, what brings you here?
Sorry for the short notice, but I need
to leave for Bayrelicht right away.
I thought I'd give you these before I go.
Those are...
Girart's Death Moon.
I've already changed the owner.
You can transfer them to whoever you want.
I'd heard they were destroyed in your duel.
I'm the one who made Death Moon.
Repairing them was nothing.
Besides,
Girart asked me to give them to you
once the duel was over.
The first king wanted me to...
Mind making sure they're good to go?
Very well.
These are unbelievable!
It's up to you who inherits them next.
I accept that responsibility.
Okay, let's head back.
You intend to teleport?
Perhaps to where the Moon Sanctum was?
Yeah. A wagon would take too long,
and that area is safe.
Another crystal? How extravagant.
All right. Here we go.
Someone's watching.
I'm glad I used a stealth skill.
Perhaps they think the Moon Sanctum
will reappear in this spot.
People must have long forgotten
that it could be moved.
Y-You won't disappear, will you, Shin?
What?
I just... grew a bit nervous that
that day may come again.
Schnee.
It's unfounded, isn't it?
You're going to be left behind.
Oh, sorry.
Hey, wait. I'm the one Barlux summoned.
So why are you just standing there?
I couldn't imagine what it's like to wait
for someone who might never return.
I'm not sure I could do it.
You couldn't.
That was quick!
Elves and humans have totally
different perceptions of time.
If we wanted to wait, why wouldn't we?
Is that how it works?
Yes, it is.
For long-lived species like us, losing our
reason to live is the gateway to hell.
So thinking about it too hard
gets you into trouble...
That's right. If you're going to think,
put your mind to something more useful.
Besides, it throws me off
when you suddenly get serious.
Could you not make it sound like I'm cavalier
about everything all the time?
You do get serious
about the strangest things, Shin.
Shaddup.
Shin, it's good to see you again!
I received a summons from the guild master.
We'll let him know you're here.
One moment, please.
Cilica, could you go get him?
Sure thing!
Do you know what this is about?
No. We're not told that much.
But I did expect you'd be summoned soon.
What? Why?
Because you're hardly an ordinary adventurer.
Of course...
You're always traveling with beautiful women.
I-I have male acquaintances, too!
Oh? I've never seen you speaking to one before.
That can't be true. There's, uh...
Oh, right! Wilhelm!
We've worked together before.
What?
Is that true, Shin?
It wasn't an official job, but yeah.
Why did everyone go quiet?
He rarely forms parties.
They say his combat strength is S-rank,
but there are many rumors about him.
Folks find him difficult to approach.
Yeah, he's easily misunderstood.
Wilhelm himself is an
exceptional man, however.
Can say that again.
Shin!
We're ready for you. This way, please.
You're here sooner than expected.
I was already headed this way.
Sorry to rush you. This is Arahd the mage.
I am Arahd Royl. A pleasure.
He appraises gems for the guild.
He assessed the Skullface gem
you brought in as well.
My name is Shin. It's nice to meet you.
As I said in my message,
the palace has summoned you.
May I ask why?
Before that, I have a question.
Are you aware that a sword
flew into the palace?
I heard something flew into it...
About that...
It was a massive white sword.
On top of that, it crashed into the bedroom
of the second princess of Bayrelicht.
It caused quite the stir.
O-Oh?
Fortunately, no one was hurt.
The issue is the sword itself.
Its elemental enchantment
and base materials are quite impressive.
Apparently, it's comparable
to the kingdom's royal sword.
That's amazing.
The gem from the Skullface you defeated
also possessed powerful mana.
I heard it was a rather high level.
G-Guess so.
They definitely know who's responsible.
How did you manage to figure out
that I was involved?
Someone was trying to find out what happened.
They got wind of the gem, too.
As its appraiser, I was asked
to examine the sword as well.
There were traces of mana left on it
distinct from the sword's own.
It matched the mana from the gem.
So it's like fantasy DNA identification.
From there, they followed the trail.
When they discovered you were the one
who brought the gem, you were summoned.
Given the circumstances,
the guild couldn't keep your secret.
Considering what they knew,
you couldn't fool them anyway.
That's not on you.
Fortunately, because you had a letter
of introduction from the Moon Sanctum,
the situation isn't any worse.
Now, getting down to business...
The second princess, Her Highness Rionne
herself, is the one who summoned you.
What?
This incident piqued her interest in you.
Is she going to hold me responsible
for nearly injuring royalty?
No, you won't be punished for that.
The princess has slain Skullfaces before.
Based on her experience,
she's convinced everyone that
you'd have no choice
but to use full force against it.
I appreciate that, but then
what exactly does she want from me?
I don't know the answer to that either.
Politicians are nasty creatures, after all.
Anyway, that's what they told me.
I see.
You sent a sword flying into the palace?
Why would you do that?
It's not like I did it on purpose!
So Shin's just amazing?
In some ways, yes.
Perhaps they wish to press you
into their service
or have you marry an important noble.
M-Marry?!
Yes. They say a nation's power is proportional
to its high-ranking chosen ones.
I believe they'll aggressively
try to recruit you.
I suddenly don't feel like going anymore.
I doubt there's any problem with you
refusing to enter their service.
Really?
As your party members,
we'd suffer a great loss if you left.
That should be reason enough
to turn them down.
But on the other hand,
if they want to marry me off...
Refusing stuff like that without
a good reason only causes more trouble.
On that front, you could tell them
I am your fiancée.
Hey, yeah, I could say I'm already spoken for.
Depending on the circumstances,
you could even say you're betrothed to Tiera.
T-To me?
Oh, would you not like that?
As long as we're just pretending...
Then Yuzuha will be Shin's fiancée, too!
Wait, Yuzuha. We can't do that!
It'd destroy me socially!
We're just pretending.
It's only make-believe. It's not for real.
You're not going to mate with Schnee?
H-Hey! Don't say stuff like that in that form!
Mate...
Why don't we all calm down?
I've been summoned by the second princess.
My name is Shin.
I've been expecting you.
I'll retrieve your escort. One moment, please.
Understood.
I wonder what's going to show up...
Excuse me. You're Shin
the adventurer, aren't you?
Yes, that's me.
I am Gadras. Princess Rionne
asked me to fetch you.
I'll show you the way. Come with me.
Understood.
Dark Knight
Gadras Jarre
Level 188...
They sent one of the kingdom's
most powerful men to meet me.
We're here. Princess Rionne is just inside.
It's Gadras. I've brought Shin.
Enter.
Thank you for coming.
I am Rionne Sytrail Bayrelicht,
second princess of this kingdom.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Shin.
Thank you for inviting me today.
I care little for etiquette.
Feel free to call me Rionne.
Very well, Rionne.
Your Highness, that's hardly proper
for someone you've just met.
You've confused him.
We may fight side by side eventually.
It beats building walls
just because I'm royalty.
I beg your pardon, Shin,
but this is simply how she is.
No need for formality.
Uh, may I ask why I was summoned?
I'm sure Barlux gave you an overview,
but it's about the Skullface.
You recognize this, don't you?
That's the sword the Skullface was wielding.
I imagine it was quite strong.
Well, yes. My own weapon
was destroyed in the battle.
I see.
At least that much is true.
I knew you were different.
Different, you say?
Most adventurers like you who suddenly
distinguish themselves are chosen ones.
When we determine one to be rather powerful,
we typically summon you here.
Some have used the opportunity
to plot assassinations.
How frightening.
Some suspected you would as well,
but you seem safe.
I don't recall saying anything
that would clear such suspicions.
Of course you didn't.
I'm going off my instincts.
What?
You've shown your colors.
I mean, I doubt anyone would
accept that without more concrete proof.
That's not a problem.
I possess the skill "Intuition."
My hunches have never been wrong.
Is that how Intuition works?
Is the Intuition skill
enhancing her woman's intuition?
Well, the most decisive factor was that
you possess a letter of introduction
from the Moon Sanctum.
Schnee wouldn't grant one
to anyone who'd plot an assassination.
This was more like a final check.
I see. So, now we get down to business?
Yes. Allow me to be direct.
Is it marriage after all?!
Shin, I want you to fight me!
What?
Next Time
Episode 10
Demon