Wow. Are there always this many people here?
This is actually on the sparse side.
This crowd?
I've only ever heard about it from people
who came to the shop, but this is incredible!
She's like a child visiting
an amusement park for the first time.
Don't get lost because
you're having too much fun.
I-I'm not that excited!
Let's complete our errands first.
Then we can use our remaining time
however we want.
You're right. Okay, let's head to the guild.
I'd hardly believe she used
to be afraid to go outside.
By the way, do you know where the guild is?
Um...
It's this way.
Hey, wait!
Guild Card
Shin
Adventurer Rank
Guild Card
Shin
Adventurer Rank
You've ranked up.
As of today, you're rank E.
Guild Card
Shin
Adventurer Rank
What? But I still haven't
completed a single job.
You defeated a high-ranking Skullface
and a surprise horde of Skullfaces.
The guild has verified your reports,
so we've decided to promote you.
Oh, so that's the deal.
Personally, I think you could've
been promoted to rank A.
Other adventurers wouldn't look kindly
on such a big promotion.
By the way, how do you know this woman?
We're traveling together on mutual business.
Since we were stopping by anyway,
I thought she could register as
an adventurer and get a guild card.
Is she your girlfriend?
What?
N-N-No!
I heard you were holding hands like a couple.
H-How did you find out about that so quickly?
She's certainly beautiful.
Men just can't help themselves, can they?
Why do you sound so hostile?
Holding hands with a pretty woman
must feel like some kind of dream.
Even if you end up ogling her around town,
it's nothing to be ashamed of.
You can't help it, after all.
Uh-oh. We've triggered something weird.
Um, by the way, do you have
any information on sacred sites?
Sacred sites?
Yeah, the places said to have been destroyed
during the Dusk of Prosperity.
I'm sorry, but we can't disclose information
on those to anyone below rank B.
I see. I was mostly just curious.
I'll come back once I've ranked up.
I know. I'm going to Farnid.
Do you have any jobs
I could complete on the way?
In that case...
Let's see. In the direction of Farnid...
Someone is requesting a wagon escort
to Bayreun's staging post.
Job Description: Wagon escort to Bayreun
Client: Nakk
Open Positions: Up to five
Reward: Ten silver coins per person
That sounds good.
What do you think, Tiera?
It's certainly fine by me.
Very well.
They're departing this afternoon
when the bell rings thrice.
Two adventurers have already signed on,
so please meet up with them.
We've got some time
until my guild card is ready.
We're not getting together
for the job until the afternoon,
so let's wander through town
on our way to the church.
Really?
Lacia.
Hey there. Good morning.
Good morning, Shin.
And... who might this be?
My name is Tiera. It's nice to meet you.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Lacia, a nun at this church.
I work at the Moon Sanctum—
What? The Moon Sanctum?
Does that mean you know Schnee?
She's my master.
What?!
That's incredible! Just incredible!
How did you become her student?
Is Schnee a strict master?
In your opinion, what kind of person is she?
Good to see you, Yu!
You seem well, Millie.
Yeah. The orphanage
is here to stay 'cause of you.
Thanks, Shin!
Really? That's great.
Thanks to you, I'll be taking over
as the next head of the church.
The children are delighted.
We don't know how to repay you.
Don't worry about it.
Actually, where's Wilhelm?
He's investigating the other priest.
He said there's no way
that man would back down quietly.
That figures.
After all, we still don't know why
this guy wanted to take over the church.
I hope it's nothing serious.
Take this just in case.
You too, Millie.
What's this?
It's enchanted with all kinds of magic.
Think of it as a lucky charm.
A lucky charm!
Thank you so much for everything.
Thank you.
Not at all.
Sister, is it true that Shin is here?
There he is!
Hey, guys. You look full of energy.
We are, we are!
Play with us, Shin.
I've got treats for you later.
Really?
All right!
Shin...
Help!
I only left you for a second,
and they've taken right to you.
I'm sorry for the fuss the children caused.
Oh, it was nothing.
I was unsure at first since I've
never played with children before,
but they're so lively and cute.
Indeed. I swear I'll protect this pwace—
Ow.
This is your guild card, Tiera.
Please look it over.
Guild Card
Tiera
Adventurer Rank G
Now I'm an adventurer, too.
Let's go pick up the Moon Sanctum next.
I'd completely forgotten about it.
That's the last thing you should forget about.
Carrying your house around with you
is crazy in the first place!
Huh. Since I own the Moon Sanctum,
it just seems totally normal to me.
Is that a crystal?
I've never seen one so large
and beautifully refined before.
It's enchanted with the Teleport spell.
It's a consumable item that instantly
warps you to a saved location.
Let's use this to get to the Moon Sanctum.
I swear, everything you pull out
of your pocket is something extraordinary.
Don't tell me you can make these too.
What? How are crystals enchanted
with Teleport treated these days?
Teleportation is a lost spell.
As long as I have the materials,
I can make as many as I want.
Sorry, I guess?
Of course you can.
You're a legendary high human.
The coast is clear. Welp, all ready to warp?
Yes. Go right ahead.
Here we go.
Moon Sanctum
Wow. What a strange feeling.
Okay, let's do this.
What? Already?
Storage.
Look.
Is that it?
Yup. This is the Moon Sanctum
in transport mode.
I'm impressed.
Okay, we've finished all our errands.
Shall we head to the job?
Excuse me.
Is this Nakk's wagon?
That's right. Are you also
adventurers who took the job?
Yes. We'll be joining you.
I'm Shin. This is...
I'm Tiera. Nice to meet you.
I'm Gaien. I look forward
to traveling with you.
And this is...
Tsubaki. Nice to meet you.
Yeah. Nice to meet you too.
Nice to meet you indeed.
Okay, looks like everyone's here.
I'm Nakk the merchant.
I'm counting on you to get me to Bayreun.
Hello.
All aboard?
Then we're off!
The Moon Sanctum has disappeared?
You're absolutely certain?
Yes. The reports are correct, Your Majesty.
An immovable structure
that survived the Dusk of Prosperity...
Moon Sanctum
Not even the most powerful individuals
or high-level monsters could break into it.
A mystical shop made from lost technology...
If it has truly disappeared, this is more than
just a problem for the Bayrelicht Kingdom.
What about Schnee Raizar?
Do we know what happened to her?
We've been informed
she's headed to the castle.
If that intel is correct,
she should arrive sometime today.
Rionne still hasn't returned.
We don't have enough information to act.
Father, we should wait
for Ms. Raizar's arrival.
You're right.
Have you ever killed anyone?
What?
Sometimes you have to fight
people on escort jobs.
You're more likely to be attacked
by bandits than monsters.
Folks tend to underestimate me because
I'm small, but I beat them all up.
How dependable.
I know. Things will be easier if we
know what we're all capable of in a fight.
Why don't we briefly reintroduce ourselves?
Sure.
I am a samurai by trade.
My adventurer rank is A.
I'm useless with magic,
so don't expect me to cast any spells.
I'm a boxer. My rank is E.
I can cast support spells to boost speed.
I'm an alchemist,
but I can use a bow and sword as well.
I recently became an adventurer,
so I'm only rank G,
but I can cast simple healing spells.
Let me know if you need one.
Like Gaien, I'm a samurai. My rank is E.
I can cast a bit of fire and lightning magic.
This is Yuzuha. Believe it or not,
this little one's a monster.
We have a Tamer contract.
A samurai who uses magic?
You must've undergone some unusual training.
And it's rare for monsters
to take a liking to people.
Yuzuha is surprisingly strong, too.
Are you originally from Hinomoto?
No. What makes you think that?
Most samurai are from Hinomoto.
You're the first one I've met besides Gaien.
Oh? You don't say.
Most people are warriors,
knights, or specialists.
Those who become samurai
tend to be the eccentric kind.
Eccentric?! Don't be ridiculous.
It's a great profession that can do
it all, from tank to attack!
Like how knight and berserker
are prerequisites for the profession.
It makes no sense.
Oh, that's what you meant.
I get that, but to be blunt, we're strong.
I'll concede that much, but it's still weird.
Indeed. Hinomoto, where most samurai
hail from, is a unique island nation.
It was created by natural disaster
and is home to several samurai
and shinobi guild headquarters.
The nation was built around them.
Because of that, many who devote
themselves to battle in Hinomoto
hold a special admiration for samurai.
What are some of the guilds
founded in Hinomoto?
The most commonly known are
Kacho Fugetsu, Majin Keppuroku,
and Kuromiko Jinja.
Wow, really?
I can't believe there's a whole country
based around guilds from the game.
There are other smaller guilds,
but they aren't as famous.
Got it. Thanks for the information.
What's wrong, Nakk?
Are you bandits?
Sorry, Mister Merchant.
If you don't wanna die,
leave all your money and cargo.
Nakk, get inside the wagon.
Yuzuha, defend Nakk.
What should we do?
There aren't too many of them.
Should they attack us,
we'll turn the tables on them.
Have you ever killed anyone?
I have to do it.
Otherwise, the others
will be in greater danger.
C'mon, now. You think the three
of you can take us?
Why don't you leave the redhead, too?
We're gonna have some fun with her.
We'll make you scream and cry.
I can't get excited unless I hear screaming.
Poor thing. He won't let you die quick.
If anything, you'll be begging
for him to kill you.
Not that it'll change anything.
Shin?
He's not his usual self.
I don't like this bloodlust.
I don't like this Shin.
I'm scared to shoot someone,
but I have to do it.
I don't enjoy needless killing.
Retreat now, and you're free to go.
But if you refuse, I'll cut you down.
Come on. Don't you realize
the position you're in?
We know you've got a bunch
of E-rank and lower adventurers.
You may be rank A, but you can't fight
while protecting the others.
They know who we are?
Sounds like this was no chance encounter.
I'm curious where they got that information.
We'll beat it out of them.
What?
This is getting to be a pain.
Let's kill 'em all besides the girl.
They'll be quiet once they're corpses.
What?
How'd they spot our guys?
Get 'em, boys!
Just you? You underestimate me.
Don't fight back too hard.
I can't have any fun with you if you die!
You piss me off.
Flashing Vigor? E-ranks shouldn't
be able to use that technique!
Fly.
What?
Idiots! Don't take your eyes off them!
You'll die for this affront.
That katana...
Your swords seem to be magical,
but unfortunately, so is mine.
You're wasting your time.
Who the hell are you people?
Aside from the dragnir,
aren't you all rank E or lower?
We've got magic swords and should be
higher level than you, but...
What will you do now?
Let's get rid of that sword.
Once I immobilize you, you're finished.
What? No, wait...
I-Is it over?
You went wild on him.
I was actually holding back.
You can't be serious. You can't!
I'm gonna kill you!
You can't keep up that bravado for—
You're going to tell us
where you got your information.
Shin. Shin!
Uh, what are you doing?
Just give us a second.
Don't you move.
U-Um, Tiera?
Uh... What are you doing?
You're back to normal.
Good.
What was that?
Dunno.
What am I doing?!
Shin seemed so cold and dark earlier.
Did he realize it, or was it just me?
It always calmed me down when
my master did that for me,
so I did it to Shin on a whim, but...
How am I supposed to face him now?!
What's going on?
Dunno.
Next Time
Episode 7
Bayreun