Lady Rionne, what shall we do
about this sword?
Call an appraiser.
Determine its material composition at once.
Find out who launched it
into the castle as well.
Yes, milady!
Whoever sent this sword flying here...
must be powerful indeed.
What's going on?
Hey, what happened to them?
They were attacked in
the northern woods by a Skullface.
What?
Worse, of the twelve who
went into the woods, only four survived.
So the attack must have been
the cause of the wreckage.
Also, it's not clear if it's related,
but witnesses reported seeing a sword
go flying out of the northern woods.
Apparently, it crashed into the castle.
What?
Fortunately, nobody was hurt.
Know anything about it?
No. I was just out harvesting hilk grass.
Well, if anything comes to you, let me know.
The higher-ups have me on the case.
Sorry. That was because of me.
I'm glad no one was hurt.
Welcome back, Shin.
Celica! I stopped by to report in.
Is all this commotion about the Skullface?
Yes. Since it appeared near the kingdom,
a high-priority extermination
request has been issued.
Now then, what do you have to report?
I thought I'd let you know that
I defeated the Skullface Jack.
Here's the gem I recovered.
What?
It was an odd one wielding a massive sword.
Shattered my own blade to pieces.
Wait a minute! Such a monster
is not so easily slain!
Hey, Celica, personal space!
I-I'm so sorry!
I mean, since you're normally so composed,
seeing you lose your cool
is kinda, you know...
What?
Be that as it may, try not to tease
my colleague too much.
Els!
Um...
I'm Els. I work with Celica.
She's told me all about you.
Get this, Els!
Shin claims he defeated the Skullface Jack.
What?
That said, I've got no way to prove it.
The Skullface's gear was unimpressive,
so I didn't bring it back with me.
Getting your hands on Jack-level gear would
require either rank B or a small fortune.
You scarcely sound like an adventurer.
No matter. Let's examine that gem.
It should contain the Skullface Jack's mana.
Right. Shin, we'll be borrowing this.
Sure.
By the way, do Skullfaces frequently
appear in the northern woods?
Undead are born when mana fuses
with the lingering grudges of the fallen.
The northern woods
are full of savage monsters,
so no shortage of folks
have lost their lives there.
I see. So the conditions
are ripe for creating undead.
But the mana of the woods itself isn't strong.
We don't normally see Jack-level monsters.
So this one was an exception.
It was over level 300, even.
Level 300? Really?
Level 359, to be exact.
It was probably unique.
L-Level 359?
Celica, gems can be used to determine
a monster's strength, right?
Yes. I'll have this appraised right away.
Els, I'm sorry, but could you
man the reception desk?
You can do that?
You're rather nonchalant, aren't you?
If you're right about its level,
then you're at least as strong as
an A-rank party all by yourself.
Erm, could you keep that between us?
I don't want to attract attention.
Understood.
Excuse me!
Welcome!
Oh, Shin?
Wait, huh? Cilica?
Doesn't Celica work here, too?
We're twins, after all.
Now, right this way.
Shin, do you mind sharing a table?
Not at all. Sitting alone is awkward, anyway.
Thanks so much.
The magic spear, "Venom."
Said to be a legendary weapon,
its abilities rival those of mythic arms.
Sorry to impose.
Hey, I'm Shin. Nice to meet you.
I'm Wilhelm Avis.
Wilhelm Avis
Lăncier
You a new adventurer?
Oh, yeah. Today's my third day.
Your equipment says otherwise.
It's better than your average armor.
I guess so.
I'm from the sticks, so I don't know
what's normal around here.
No wonder my name didn't scare you.
Have you done something to frighten people?
They call me Wilhelm the Vampire
because I hunt so many undead.
Seriously? So it's not because
of that pale complexion?
What?
Is that guy stupid?
I don't believe it! Does he have a death wish?
You're a funny one.
This here is the real reason.
Venom has the Drain ability.
It consumes its victims' life force
and transfers it to the wielder.
I worry it might end up
consuming me before I know it.
So that's the story, huh?
Sorry for the wait!
This is for you, Shin.
Ooh, it's here!
And the usual for you, Wilhelm.
Good.
Take your time.
Thanks.
Well, shall we eat?
Sounds good.
I haven't been to a library in a while.
I hope I can learn something about this world.
Fondarea Regatului Bayrelicht
Here we go. The annals of the
Bayrelicht Kingdom.
So it was founded 511 years ago...
Tiera said the Dusk of Prosperity
occurred 500 years ago.
So that was around the same time.
You don't even know what that is?
It was a major historical event
when many people vanished.
Players disappear when they log out,
so I can see why that caused confusion.
I'd like to see more records, though.
Elf
Dragnir
Beast
Pitic
So these are the peoples of this world...
Zână
They're basically the same
as in the in-game races.
Om
Lord
Guess that's about all
I can gather from reading.
Now then, let's begin this special council.
The Skullface Jack that appeared
in the northern woods has been slain.
Its slayer returned only with its gem,
which is currently being examined.
They defeated a Jack-level monster
and didn't collect its sword or armor?
The alleged slayer didn't find them
particularly impressive.
He wasn't impressed?
There's always something strange
about those with letters of introduction.
Don't pay it too much mind.
Wait, hold on now. I'm not that weird.
That's hardly convincing coming from you.
What?
Anyway, the appraisal confirmed
the gem to be level 359.
So it's true.
It's good to have confirmation,
but the real question now is if
similar monsters are in the area.
Though this one was a Skullface Jack,
that level puts it on par with a King.
I've already dispatched investigators
to look into the matter.
We'll have answers tomorrow.
Skullfaces become active at night.
I'd like the knights to be on their guard.
Understood, but I have a question.
What is it?
I heard the Skullface
brandished unusual equipment.
I'd like to know more about that
and the person who defeated it.
I can tell you about the weapon,
but the slayer has asked
to keep their identity a secret.
Why do you want to know?
The day that sword flew into the castle
was the day this Skullface
with remarkable gear was taken down.
Some believe the two are related.
What kind of sword is it?
Please keep this between us.
The blade's roughly two mels long,
made of an alloy of magic steel and mithril.
It's even permanently enchanted
with the light element.
In other words...
Yes. It's comparable to, if not greater than,
our nation's royal sword.
What? But that would make it legendary.
So you can't blame me
for being curious about who
defeated a monster wielding such a blade.
Moreover, there's something of a problem...
What's that?
Man, gathering information sure is difficult.
What should I do now?
Stare...
Uh, you want some?
Is she a tiger-type beast girl?
She doesn't look like a beggar.
Is she lost?
Thanks for the meal.
You're very welcome.
I'm Millie. You're a nice guy.
Thanks. I'm Shin.
Shin!
I'm going home now. What about you?
Should I walk you?
He's here to pick me up!
Hey, I wasn't expecting to run into you again.
Right back at you.
Wil!
Is she your kid?
No way. She's one of the kids
from the church orphanage.
Millie's good at sneaking out,
so I always come to find her.
I see.
Anyway, I'm surprised she's
taken a liking to you.
She's actually pretty shy.
Is that right?
Now, let's go home, Millie.
Wait a second.
...in the northern woods.
Please save them.
What?
Bye-bye!
Why did Millie ask me to do that?
There's a fox in the northern woods.
Please save them.
They must be in danger if she
wants me to save them, but why me?
Guess I've got nothing better to do
until Schnee returns.
I'll check out the northern woods.
Wait, I know a way
to get in touch with her.
I'll give it a shot.
Moon Sanctum
Welcome!
Oh, Shin!
Hey. I forgot to leave a message the other day.
Oh, right. You mentioned that.
Anyway, could you tell her, "If you recognize
this, I'd like to meet and catch up"?
Is this an ancient weapon?
Huh? You can tell?
This is Schnee's sword, Blue Moon.
It belongs to my master?
Yeah.
It can only be used by its creators,
me and Schnee, or people we designate.
So its wielders are limited?
That's right.
Huh. I can tell that it's a powerful weapon.
But I wouldn't want to use it.
Why not?
I feel like it'd swallow me up.
Maybe that's coming from the base materials.
It's primarily made of a chimeradite alloy,
plus a Black Death Dragon fang,
Ocean Thrasher scale, and Elementail tear.
And then...
Wait, what's wrong, Tiera?
I'm okay. I'm fine.
Rattle off all the legendary monsters you
want. I won't be surprised anymore.
Y-You don't look okay at all.
Everything stops making sense
when you're around.
Sorry, I guess.
But Blue Moon will tell me
if Schnee remembers me or not.
Fine. I'll hold on to it.
Also, use these to let me know
if you hear from Schnee.
They're one-way, but they'll reach me
no matter where I am.
Just write the recipient's name and say "send."
What a convenient item.
But couldn't you send her a message yourself?
I wondered that myself
and tried last night, but...
Send! Send! Send!
It didn't work.
Do these actually work, then?
Good question.
Hold on.
I got it, Shin!
Huh. There's nothing wrong
with the cards, then,
but for some reason,
I can't send them to Schnee.
It's probably dependent on whether
or not you've met someone in this world.
Say, Shin, could I get a few of these letters?
Sure. I've got more than I need.
Thank you! I'm actually trying
to become a mage,
so I'd like to study this magic item.
Okay. That should cover the cost
of leaving a message, right?
Of course!
Well, I should get going.
Say hi to Schnee for me.
You can count on me.
Moon Sanctum
Now, what should I try first?
Wait, shouldn't I send
one of these to my master?
I'm here in the northern woods,
but I have no idea how to go about
saving this fox.
For now, I'll try heading deeper.
Leave... Leave... Leave...
Is this a barrier?
I've enhanced my resistance to mental
interference, so it has no effect on me,
but it's a strong sign that there's
something up ahead.
Leave... Leave... Leave... Leave...
A shrine?
The mental interference is gone.
So this is the heart of the barrier.
What was that?
I just heard something shatter.
I don't see any traps.
This must be the one Millie was talking about.
Otravă X
Blestem X
Analizează
What? It's poisoned and cursed? It's dying!
I'd better cure it.
What was that sound?
Must've been the barrier breaking.
That's a lot of enemies.
Sorry, but hang tight for a minute.
I'm gonna clear these guys out of the way.
After the incident with the unique monster,
I don't want any more casualties.
Sorry, but...
none of you are getting away!
Furrow Pierce!
Next, Flashing Blossom!
Done and dusted.
What should I do now?
They weren't here before.
What?
Seriously? I've never seen these before.
Monstru
Invaded Golem
Invaded Golem, level 674?
I see. So that black haze is a miasma.
Whoa!
The miasma's making them behave erratically.
I have no quarrel with them,
but I can't just leave them at large.
Hold on a little longer.
Shadow Bind!
A smokescreen? It can't be ordinary mist.
Not good... The miasma is hurting it.
I'd better finish this quickly.
My Shadow Bind wore off!
I can't pinpoint the enemy's
location in this darkness.
If I use my full strength,
I'll hurt this little one, too.
But at this rate...
What is it?
There's something over there?
The magic circle you were in.
The mist hasn't breached it.
I can see into the mist from here.
Thanks. We'll be fine now.
The enemy's caught on, too.
But it's too late.
Arc Bind!
This ends now!
Cataclysmic Strike!
What a mess.
But the miasma is gone now.
That just leaves...
Whoa, there. Looks like you're all better now.
Come to think of it,
you're a Little Fox, right?
Let's check and see.
Monstru
Elementail
What?
An Elementail?!
Monstru
Elementail
Even in THE NEW GATE,
they were top-tier monsters.
But you should look humanoid
or like a giant fox.
I've never heard of a kit version before.
Well, no point in thinking about it.
What are you going to do now?
You wanna come with me?
Ow, ow, ow! Calm down.
You definitely understand me, don't you?
Golems afflicted with miasma
and an Elementail kit...
Those never appeared in the game,
but they could be a hint
about how to get back to my world.
I should ask Millie about this little one.
I told you, that hurts!
A letter for me?
What's Tiera doing with this magic item?
Master!
Data viitoare
Episodul 3
O cerere stranie