Well, at least it's
not using its claws anymore.
But man, I sure wasn't expecting
that many Skullfaces.
I'd better report to the guild.
I guess I won't tell them about
the Elementail for now.
I've got a question for you.
Want to form a contract with me?
It's called taming.
A tamer and monster form a partnership.
It'll keep your level and species hidden,
and we can stick together all the time.
Okay, okay.
Welp, here goes.
It is my desire to walk with you.
Here's to working together!
Now that we've formed a contract,
there's something we should do.
You need a name.
C-Calm down. You're shaking my head.
Anyway, what do you think of the name Yuzuha?
Sounds like you like it.
You have a new message
Must be from Tiera.
Dear Shin,
I was able to send a message to my master. I don't know if she has
any message cards, but I'll let you know if I hear back from her.
P.S. Is it possible to attach items to cards and send them??
"Dear Shin, I was able to send
a message to my master."
I hadn't really considered that Tiera
might actually reach her.
"Say hello to Schnee for me."
Okay, let's head to the guild.
Excuse me. I have something to report.
Go ahead.
Um, who should I speak to?
I'll handle—
I'll take your report.
Cilica.
What?
Shin is standing in front of me.
I'll take his report.
What? Why can't I take it?
You just can't. I'll do it.
That's not like you.
Excuse me?
Fine, fine. I'll be quiet.
Uh, can I make my report now?
Yes. I'm sorry for the trouble.
Go right ahead.
I'm glad I got to report in.
While we're here, let's check out other jobs.
A skill successor?
Looking for Skill Successor
If interested, please come to the orphanage next to the church in the west ward
Is that a term for a skill holder?
It's an unranked job.
Must be something special to it.
It's from the church orphanage.
Please save the fox.
I'm curious about that power, too.
Looking for Skill Successor
If interested, please come to the orphanage next to the church in the west ward
I'm on my way to see Millie anyway.
May I help you?
Oh, pardon me. I've never been
to a place like this before.
I'm here because I have
business with the orphanage.
Did you see my job request?
I thought I'd at least see what it's about.
Also, is there a beast girl named Millie here?
What of her?
She asked me to do something for her.
This way.
It's Shin!
Millie!
Shin!
It would seem you're not a bad person.
Is that how you saw me?
Forgive me. It's been a while since Millie
took such a liking to someone.
I'm Shin, an adventurer.
My name is Tria. I'm a nun at this church.
Can I ask Millie about
what I mentioned earlier?
Yes.
Say, Millie, is this the fox
you were talking about yesterday?
Yeah, it is! Thanks!
You're welcome.
Yuzuha, say thank you.
I was able to rescue you because of Millie.
Now, could you tell me
more about your request?
Yes. If you came after seeing it,
then you must have a skill.
Well, yeah.
Skill holders were common in the game,
but I guess they're a lot more rare now.
In truth, I'm looking for someone
who inherited a certain skill
so they can teach it to me.
Given your profession,
is it something like Heal or Cure?
No, actually. There are
other circumstances at play.
I... need Purify.
Oh, Purify?
I know I'm asking for a lot.
Yeah, that's a really tough one.
I'm sure it is.
Wait, what did you just say?
Er, I said it's a tough ask.
Do you perchance know how
to teach it to someone?
Yeah, I do.
S-So you can fulfill the job?
That depends on you.
Regarding the reward...
I don't need any monetary compensation.
Instead, I'd like to know
about Millie's power.
I'd also like you to share whatever
information the church acquires.
Of course she's at a loss.
I'm a stranger who showed up out of nowhere.
There's so much I don't know
about this world.
I'd love to have the church
as an intel resource,
but what should I do?
He's okay.
Shin is okay.
Millie.
Very well. I accept your terms.
But we're not experts.
I'm not sure we'll be able to
gather information for you.
I just need to know if anyone comes
to the church saying anything of interest.
The nature of Millie's power is the more
important part to me anyway.
Millie possesses the title "Star Composer."
Star Composer?
She sometimes has unexpected visions.
And they've never been wrong before.
So she can predict the future.
Yes. Perhaps she asked you for a favor
because she saw something.
If people found out about Millie's power,
there are those who would use it
for nefarious purposes.
I've warned my associates
to be wary of who they mention it to.
There's an adventurer from here
who provides us with assistance.
You mean Wilhelm?
Yes.
Most people leave our children alone
for fear of him.
In that case, I'd formally
like to accept the job.
Tria, are you the one
who will be learning Purify?
No, I was thinking of asking
another of our sisters to learn it.
I figured it would be you...
Our former priest has a granddaughter.
Things would go more smoothly
if she were to inherit the church.
Sounds like a sticky situation.
It's a fox!
I wanna hold it!
Me first!
No, me.
Me too!
All alone...
Complet singur
Hang in there.
Why do I feel so defeated?
Well, I can't expect them to take
a shine to a total stranger.
Millie, don't you want to see Yuzuha too?
I'd lose.
You'd... lose?
Yeah.
She's right. Millie's a bit small
to force her way in there.
Come here, Yu.
Now I've got you all to myself.
Don't tell me you're a little schemer!
Easy win.
That's exactly what it sounds like!
Are you the one who's going to save us?
"Us"? Not the nun?
What do you mean?
The nun said they might
get rid of this place.
They're getting rid of the church?
No, just the orphanage.
Will you tell me more about that?
This church doesn't have a priest right now,
so a new one has to take over.
Can't Tria do that?
It has to be someone
who can use a special skill.
So that's why she needs Purify.
The new priest wants
to get rid of the orphanage.
But the nun says the old priest's
granddaughter, Lacia,
might have a superior claim to the church.
Our former priest has a granddaughter.
So that's why she wants
another nun to learn the skill.
But why would a priest of this church
want to do away with the orphanage?
We don't like him.
What's he like?
He's a pig who only cares about money.
Yeah, okay. That tells me
everything I need to know.
It's okay.
Shin will save us.
If you say so, Millie, maybe we'll be okay.
Does Millie tend to be right?
Yeah. She always knows which shops have
good deals and where the snacks are hidden.
Not exactly what I meant, but okay.
Sounds like Millie's careful
about who she shares things with.
Is that weird?
No, it's not weird. If anything, it's good.
As long as you're not straining yourself.
I like head pats.
Thank you for waiting, Shin.
Say hello, Lacia.
R-Right. I'm Sister Lacia.
Thank you for helping ush— I mean, us.
Um...
Are you all right?
She can be a bit careless,
but I promise she's hardworking.
I'm Shin. I'm going to teach you
how to use the Purify skill.
Just remember that whether or not
you can learn it depends on you.
Okay!
First, I have a question.
Do you know where large numbers
of high-level undead appear?
The Ghost Plains are rather famous.
The Ghost Plains?
So you're the adventurer who took the job.
Oh, Wil, you're back?
Hey. I'm just stopping by.
Wil.
What are you after? What did they tell you?
About Millie and the adventurer
from the orphanage
who helps them keep her secret.
You shouldn't be so trusting.
He doesn't seem like a bad person.
Besides, Millie said it would be okay.
Did you see something?
Yeah.
I see.
Is that all?
If Millie says so, then I trust you.
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone
or do anything underhanded.
You'd better not.
If you do, I'll use this to kill you.
No fighting. You're so fussy, Wil!
I'm sorry. He's always been short-tempered.
Wil is impatient.
Hey.
That's a harsh review.
Whatever. Tell us about Purify.
Don't tell anyone else.
Wouldn't dream of it.
To acquire Purify, you must
defeat 200 undead over level 150
while holding an item called
a holy prayer orb.
Landing the finishing blow counts as a kill,
so I'll weaken the monsters
and Lacia can polish them off.
Wait, are you serious?
Yes. Acquiring a holy prayer orb
is actually pretty difficult,
but I already have one, so we're good.
You're saying such remarkable
things so casually...
Lacia, are you gonna be okay?
Hey!
Yes!
Shin, I'm coming with you.
Sure. You're welcome to.
Lacia, good luck.
I-I'll do my best.
I'm counting on you.
Of course.
There's too much I don't know about him.
Millie likes him, so at the very least,
he's probably not dangerous.
But I don't buy that some no-name novice
can take on loads of monsters
over level 150, all while carrying Lacia.
The only conceivable explanation is...
We leave tomorrow morning.
When we get home, let's eat and retire early.
Wilhelm?
Come with me.
I want to confirm something.
Are you a chosen one?
A chosen one?
You don't know what those are?
Not a clue.
Chosen ones are people born with skills,
titles, and knowledge they shouldn't have.
Does that include memories of previous lives?
No, mostly information
about items and monsters.
I've never heard of anyone
remembering a past life.
I see.
People starting off
with multiple skills and titles?
Does that mean the reincarnation
system still works?
Sound familiar to you?
Not exactly...
I've reincarnated within the game before,
but I wasn't reborn
in this world as an infant.
High humans are apparently extinct, too.
No matter. I won't make you
tell me everything.
I appreciate it.
By the way, most people have
never heard of chosen ones.
Careful who you mention that to.
You're surprisingly caring, Wilhelm.
Are you sure people are afraid of you?
I can't help what others think of me.
You're a hero who protects an orphanage.
The kids are crying because some greedy
pig won't stop messing with them.
The sound grates on my ears.
So you're stopping this guy
to shut them up, huh?
That's right.
Crap! I always had a feeling,
but he's seriously a nice guy!
What?
Uh...
Nothing. It's nothing.
Sorry. One second.
Huh?
Ai un mesaj nou
Dear Shin, I received a response
from my master.
She'll return as soon as
she's finished with work.
Please keep us informed
if you leave Bayrelicht.
P.S. I'm scared of how many questions
my master asked about you.
P.S. I'm scared of how many questions my master asked about you.
What did you do to her??
What did you do to her?
How many questions
is a scary number of questions?
Important
Why is it flashing?
That's a letter of introduction
from the Moon Sanctum.
You know what this is?
I wouldn't have thought you had one, too.
Right back at you.
So these are the Ghost Plains, huh?
Lacia.
Y-Yes?!
Here's the holy prayer orb.
You've gotta make sure you're holding it.
Oh, shank— I mean, thank you.
They're already here.
Lacia, give it all you've got.
Okay.
Single Ablution!
Attack the Biohounds.
G-Got it!
Heal!
Good. Healing magic works
just like it does in the game.
The next group is coming!
Break their limbs
so they can't counterattack.
Don't tell me you can't pull that off.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Flashing Blossom!
Not bad.
What's this blue wall?
It's a seal created by the guild.
The undead beyond this point
are on another level.
Prepare yourselves.
O-Okay.
Rapt Raptors and Jumpkins.
Looks like five in all.
Wilhelm, you take the front.
I'll stop the ones to our left.
Makes sense.
There are no other enemies nearby.
Yuzuha, you handle things here.
Heal!
Good work. You've gained a lot of levels.
I know! I've leveled up so much it's scary!
It's because these monsters
outlevel you so much.
You'll advance rapidly.
By the time you learn Purify,
you should be about level 150.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Wil.
Here.
SPLATTER
No!
I heard unusually high-level Skullface Jacks
had appeared in the Ghost Plains,
so I came to defeat them,
but these are exceptionally strong.
Without this sword that came flying
into my room that day,
this battle would have been tough.
I'm worried about the other group.
So am I.
Allow me to handle it.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Go around! Aim for the core!
Its attacks are too powerful!
Anyone with strength left, lend us your aid!
Damn! What's wrong with this thing?
We won't last like this...
If we lose any more men,
we won't be able to stop it.
Schnee!
Data viitoare
Episodul 4
După o noapte lungă