The church?
Yes. The bandits attempted to raid this wagon
for goods connected to the church.
They weren't told what exactly
they were, however.
So they attacked us without knowing
what they should take?
They intended to kill the lot of us
and make off with all the cargo.
How awful.
To appoint the next head,
the nuns said they needed official
authorization from church HQ.
Was someone trying to prevent that?
Maybe it's coincidence, but it feels like
escorting this wagon was the right choice.
Good work, everyone!
I made it safely to Bayreun thanks to you!
Here are your certificates of job completion.
Take these to the guild.
I'm glad we all made it here.
Yeah. That's what matters most.
Absolutely!
I'll hire you again if I need anything.
Now that we've reported in to the guild,
what are you two going to do next?
We're headed straight to Kilmont.
What about you?
We're on our way to Farnid.
Is that so?
I'm sure we'll meet again if it's meant to be.
If you see us, say hi.
Sure.
Take care.
Well, how shall we continue
our journey? Another wagon?
Do you prefer to travel by wagon?
It was pretty comfortable.
If a bit painful on the posterior...
Farnid is a pretty long way away.
Thinking ahead, it wouldn't hurt to own one.
Okay, let's buy our own.
They're all pretty much the same.
We'll have to modify one.
Hold on. Did I just hear you
make a terrible suggestion?
Whatever do you mean?
You know what you said.
I just want to reduce the shaking
and improve the wheel movement.
It should make it nicer to ride in.
Really?
It won't move without horses
or fly through the sky?
I wouldn't do that!
In other words, you could.
Well, as long as it isn't too flashy...
That's the idea.
I'm still feeling all this out, you know.
I'd believe that coming from anyone else.
Aren't you being mean to me
for no reason?
So, which one should we get?
I'd like one large enough to sleep in.
So...
about that size?
You're right.
There's room for luggage, and we'll be
all set for when my master arrives.
You're right.
Excuse me! I'd like to buy this.
We'll pick it up on our way out of town.
Sure thing!
By the way, have you already acquired horses?
No, not yet.
Then I've got a little advice for you.
You'll want to get horses
with good legs to pull this wagon.
It's a bit too heavy for one horse, too.
I've heard rumors about people
using monsters to pull their wagons.
Some do. After all, they're way stronger.
You have to be able to tame one, though.
I see. Thanks. I'll take that
into consideration.
We can have Yuzuha transform
if we get desperate.
That's a telepathic call alert.
This is Shin. Is that you, Schnee?
Yes. I've concluded my business
in the kingdom.
Where are you now?
We just bought a wagon in Bayreun.
After this, we need to find horses
to set out for Farnid.
In that case, allow me to capture
a monster to pull the wagon.
I'll arrive in Bayreun within a day.
Could you wait for me there?
Sure. You don't need to rush.
Thank you. Also, regarding the Moon Sanctum...
The castle was quite concerned
over its sudden disappearance.
Seriously? They're that worried
just because I packed it up?
Everyone was rather pale.
This will do them good, though.
How so?
Honestly, I was getting fed up
with their incessant flattery
while trying to observe and recruit me.
Ah, yeah. That must be rough.
I'm sure any kingdom looking
to bolster its military
would want you in their ranks.
Yes. One kingdom even dared to claim
ownership of the Moon Sanctum.
I considered eradicating the entire nation.
That's no joke coming from you.
Maybe they thought they'd get you
if they acquired the Moon Sanctum.
Indeed, there have been people who tried.
And also those who proposed marriage.
Yeah, I bet.
I'm the one who made her that way,
but Schnee is a total knockout.
It's no wonder she's popular.
Are you jealous?
Well, yeah.
I see. You're jealous over me.
Where did that come from?
Figure it out.
Now then, let me know
once you've found an inn.
Sure, you got it. Talk to you then.
Aren't these pretty?
Yeah. It might be nice to wander and
take in the sights while we look for an inn.
Are you from out of town?
If you haven't found an inn yet,
I can tell you where's good!
This seems...
Expensive.
Welcome.
We're looking for a place to stay.
Will you be sharing a room?
S-Separate rooms, please!
Very well.
That was close.
I can't believe we spent
almost half our reward on an inn.
That woman recommended
one heck of a place to stay.
Maybe she thought adventurers could afford it.
It's apparently famous in Bayreun,
and it's not bad to indulge once in a while.
It's definitely a luxury inn.
Can I talk now?
Yeah. It should be fine here.
It's so fluffy!
Rolly, rolly! Rolly, rolly! Ack!
We have some time until dinner.
Guess I'll do maintenance on my weapons.
Shin, do you have a minute?
Sure. The door's open.
Did you tell my master
we're staying in this city?
Yeah.
I don't know exactly when, but she
said she'd arrive in Bayreun tomorrow.
I see. Then we should get some rest.
Yeah. Let's have dinner in the room.
I'm stuffed.
I'll take a quick bath,
then go straight to bed.
You'll turn into a fox for the night, right?
Perhaps I'll take a bath and go to bed, too.
I wanna take a bath together!
Sure. That's fine.
Yay! Bath time!
Bath, bath, bath!
Wait, Yuzuha! We should use the bath in my room...
Guess I'll keep working on my weapons.
Wow, Tiera! Amazing!
Hey, stop!
They're so soft!
Yuzuha, please!
Hey! I'm right here, you know!
Yuzuha, let go!
Boing, boing!
Don't do that!
The moon's lovely tonight...
Hey, Yuzuha! Come on!
Not bad.
No wonder I can't breathe.
I'm going to work on the wagon
until Schnee gets here.
What are you going to do?
I'm curious to see what modifications
you'll make, so maybe I'll watch.
Me too!
I should probably start by altering the axles.
If I do this and add some springs,
that should reduce the shaking.
Huh? What?
Okay, that should do it.
Now I just need to add the bearings.
What was that, Shin?
The metal went all bendy!
It's a creation skill for working metal.
Though I've adapted it a bit for this.
That was fast...
Huh?
That was way too fast!
It hasn't even been a minute!
Do modifications always take so little time?
Oh, right, we're avoiding attention.
I'll install the bearings
in a more conventional fashion.
Huh?
It's Schnee.
I've arrived. I'm in the woods
beyond the north gate.
Got it. We'll head there now.
What is it?
Schnee's here. Let's finish this up
and meet her as fast as we can.
Didn't you just say you'd do the rest normally?
Something's up ahead.
Yeah.
What is it?
Oh, um... you'll see once we get there.
We're close.
Shin, it's strong.
Huh? What is this?
Monster
Gruefazio Jade
A Gruefazio Jade.
It's a monster whose max level
is normally 650.
But since you don't usually see them with
horns like that, I'm guessing this one's unique.
I have returned.
As promised, I've brought you
a monster to pull the wagon.
This should be able to do the job
without issue.
Out of curiosity, where did you get it?
From the nearby sacred mountain.
Always going above and beyond, Schnee...
You honor me.
I mean, it wasn't really a compliment.
She loses all reason when it comes to you.
It's already taken a liking to you.
They're popular with kids,
so maybe it's the friendly type.
This isn't just my problem, you know...
Well, now that we've brought it here,
we're stuck with it.
Why did you choose this monster?
If it is to pull your wagon,
I knew it had to be a monster
in the sacred beast class.
Come on, now! It's way too big.
What kind of wagon were you
expecting me to get?
I anticipated you would say that, Shin.
What?
Go on. Do it.
It shrank?
So it has that ability, huh?
It can go even smaller.
It will be quite convenient
for staying at inns.
You're right. This size should be fine.
I'm strangely exhausted...
It was intimidating enough before
to make most people faint.
Yeah, you're right.
You're both crazy for carrying on
like it was no big deal.
Still, I never expected her
to bring something so high-level.
Did I do something wrong?
Master! Most people wouldn't even think
of making a sacred beast pull a wagon.
Do you not like it?
What?
Wait, wait! Why are you getting sad?
I don't have a problem with it.
I'm happy to have a cool
sacred beast pull my wagon.
He says, "You can count on me."
You two monsters
can communicate with each other?
He really is a sacred beast!
By the way, what's his name?
His name is Shimmer.
He can use illusion and thunder skills.
Shimmer, huh? Nice to meet you.
Mind your manners around my master.
Okay, Shimmer. Our first destination is Farnid.
We're going to see an old friend named Girart.
So let's go! Take us to him!
This is great! It feels amazing!
I guess we're still drawing attention,
despite my best efforts.
Well, there's nothing we can do about that.
It really is incredible, though.
The wagon doesn't shake at all,
and my rear doesn't hurt.
It outperforms even a royal carriage.
I've ridden in one before,
and it wasn't this comfortable.
What are you talking about?
Shimmer's childhood.
Shimmer and his mom used to rule
the sacred mountain together.
But an adventurer defeated his mom,
and only Shimmer survived.
An adventurer, huh?
I'm ashamed to admit
I did similar things in the game.
He ran as fast as he could
and was rescued by an elf girl.
Then he worked hard to get stronger
and return to the sacred mountain.
An elf, was it?
No wonder he wasn't
especially cautious around me.
He says he followed you
because you smelled familiar.
Familiar?
He says it was Tiera's smell.
Me?
Was Tiera the elf girl who rescued you?
Yeah!
Seriously?!
Come to think of it,
I did save an injured puppy when I was a child.
I thought they looked similar, but...
Could it really be?
He says you met over a century ago.
Then it is him! I see... So you're that puppy.
Then why don't I transfer ownership
of Shimmer to you, Tiera?
What?
Will that be okay at her level?
There should be no problem
if both parties accept.
I shall dissolve our contract
and have you form a new one with Tiera.
First, to dissolve the contract...
May there be light where you walk.
Okay, Tiera, you're next.
Right!
It's okay. I can do it.
It is my desire to walk with you.
Whoa, there.
Are you okay?
Sorry. I suddenly felt weak.
I'm fine. I just need to rest a little.
Hey, Schnee.
Did you let Tiera have Shimmer
so he could protect her?
Yes, precisely.
We can't always be by her side,
and I'd feel better knowing Shimmer is
with her when she chooses her own path.
Now that they've formed an ownership
contract, she can summon Shimmer anytime.
We can count on him.
I'd come running anytime you're in trouble.
Thanks.
Honestly, you're the one I turn
to when I'm really screwed.
I appreciate it.
Schnee?
You can count on me.
What?
You can count on me!
Thanks.
This forest goes on forever.
We're in southeastern Farnid.
It's right on the edge of Raluah Forest.
Someone's coming.
They're pretty high-level.
I just sent a message to Girart.
They must be here to meet us.
I thought you might come.
We came on orders of the First King.
Are they the ones?
Yes. Please take us to Girart.
Very well. We'll show you to the mansion.
Hey, do you know those two?
They're Girart's grandchildren.
Seriously?
We've brought Schnee's party.
Enter.
Hey, Master. I didn't think I'd get
to see you again in this life.
Next Time
Episode 8
Trusted and Entrusted