Some suspected you'd try to assassinate me,
but you seem safe.
I don't recall saying anything
that would clear such suspicions.
Of course you didn't.
I'm going off my instincts.
What?
You've shown your colors.
I mean, I doubt anyone would
accept that without more concrete proof.
That's not a problem.
I possess the skill "Intuition."
My hunches have never been wrong.
Is that how Intuition works?
Is the Intuition skill
enhancing her woman's intuition?
Well, the most decisive factor was that
you possess a letter of introduction
from the Moon Sanctum.
Schnee wouldn't grant one
to anyone who'd plot an assassination.
This was more like a final check.
I see. So, now we get down to business?
Yes. Allow me to be direct.
Is it marriage after all?!
Shin, I want you to fight me!
What?
Your Highness, we should discuss
him entering our service first!
What are you talking about?
Confirming his abilities comes first.
Even so, there must be a more
delicate way to go about this.
What kind of princess up and
demands that people fight them?
My sister is the ladylike one.
The ladylike one?
Now, then, let us be off.
What?
Y-Your Highness...
You must have it rough.
I appreciate your understanding.
Where are we teleporting?
Somewhere we can fight
to our hearts' content.
What is this place?
They say it was a training ground built
for battles between chosen ones.
"They say"?
In truth, we don't know what
other purposes it may have served.
Teleportation points are
pre-Dusk of Prosperity technology.
We still don't fully understand them.
I see.
I did think it was strange that they
have teleportation points
even though teleportation is lost magic.
Now, let us begin.
Choose whichever weapon you'd like.
I'll use this.
Then I...
shall go with this.
That looks so odd in real life.
This battle is to test your abilities.
I expect you to put in a bit of sweat.
Go easy on me.
Now, then...
Begin!
She let go of her sword.
I thought I'd be able
to surprise you a little.
Oh, I'm plenty surprised.
You say as if you didn't readily dodge me.
The next one won't be so easy.
To fight a primarily melee-ranged
chosen one on even terms,
I'll adjust my stats like so.
Now it's my turn to attack.
You'd challenge me to a contest of strength?
I'm actually pretty confident
in my physical strength.
You may use skills as well. No holding back.
If you insist.
Flashing Vigor!
They both used the same skill.
There's hardly any difference
in the degree of enhancement.
All that separates them now
is simple difference in ability.
She's fast!
Hey, you dodged it.
If I hadn't, I think you'd be looking
at a dead man right now.
It appears we're fighters of a similar type.
Our reaction speeds are roughly the same, too.
You're right.
Settling this match won't be easy.
Why don't we stop here?
You think? I'd rather keep
fighting a little longer.
Your sword seems to be at its limit.
I knew it couldn't withstand it...
Your skills rival Her Highness's.
On top of that,
your reaction time is impressive.
This was an adequate assessment.
I suppose I shouldn't force you to continue.
Very well. We shall conclude our duel.
Thank goodness!
This room is off-limits. Please turn back.
Shin, would you be interested in joining us?
I'd feel better with you serving our kingdom.
My apologies, but I'll have to pass.
You wouldn't be a general,
but I can promise you decent status.
With all sorts of strings attached, no?
I prefer the free life of an adventurer.
I see. Let me know
if you ever change your mind.
Thank you.
By the way, why do you
have the Skullface's sword?
You didn't use it when you tested me.
Oh, this?
In our kingdom, it's customary for a man
to give a woman a sword
when proposing marriage.
She'd use it to cut him down
if he were unfaithful.
Well, that's unsettling.
These days, it's just a formality.
Anyway, I'd like to consider this sword that
crashed into my bedchamber a gift from you.
Wouldn't that imply I'd proposed to you?
Yes, I suppose it would.
It was only an accident
that the sword went flying...
I know. I won't force the matter.
However, there are those plotting to leverage
this incident to arrest you as a criminal
and have you gradually repay
the kingdom through service.
Well, even if it wasn't on purpose,
it easily could have killed someone.
So I suggest we treat it as tribute.
I see. We can treat it as tribute
instead of a marriage proposal.
That way, you're officially presented
with a powerful weapon.
And you can get the kingdom off your back.
It does sound a bit forced, though.
Naturally, I shall compensate him
for the blade from my own coffers.
I understand that we stand to gain
more from this arrangement,
but please, allow me to keep this sword!
Sure.
What?
All I want is to keep working
as an adventurer as I have been.
Oh, and I don't need any money.
Instead, could you allow me access to the
restricted zones of the magical library?
That's all you want?
This sword is worth enough for you to live
as you please for the rest of your days!
What I want right now is information.
It's just that valuable to me.
I see.
So, do we have a deal?
Of course. To tell you the truth,
I've already used it a few times.
It's starting to feel good in my hand.
She totally intended to make
the sword hers from the get-go.
Cardinal Greril, what are you doing over there?
Charm IV    Confusion III
Priest        Greril Dalles
This is bad! He's afflicted
with Charm and Confusion.
Stop!
Are we being teleported?
But I feel sick...
Your Highness!
Seriously? Where are we?
Are you all right?
What in the world happened?
Seems we've been teleported somewhere.
Somewhere this dilapidated, reachable
from that teleportation point...
We must be in the Holy Land, Calkia.
This is the holy land?
Were we the only ones teleported?
Looks like it. At the very least,
there's nobody nearby.
For a priest as powerful
as Cardinal Greril to lose his mind...
What's the meaning of this?
For now, let's get out of here.
Right.
Can you use telepathy?
No. Unfortunately,
I'm not in a party with anyone.
Then I'll get in touch with mine.
I'd like to tell my companions
where to meet us.
Do you know any nearby cities?
There's the walled city of Valmer.
You'd pass through it whether
coming or going from Bayrelicht.
Got it.
Well, speak of the devil.
Hey, Schnee.
Shin! Where are you?
Are you all right?! Please respond!
I-I'm okay, so calm down.
I'll explain the situation.
B-But...
I'll say it again. I'm fine.
V-Very well. I'm sorry.
You disappeared so suddenly,
I thought you'd left again.
So, what happened?
Well, actually...
Charm and Confusion?
Yeah. It's safe to assume someone
was controlling Cardinal Greril.
Mind-affecting skills are taboo.
Even royals are subject to execution
if caught with them.
Then we have someone lurking in the shadows.
Yes, without a doubt.
I could just teleport out of here,
but if I use supposedly lost magic,
I doubt the princess and her people
will let me go.
I hate to ask, but could you
handle things over there?
That's no problem at all.
I'll tell them the princess is safe as well.
Where shall we meet up?
Let's meet in Valmer.
It's apparently a good place for that.
Understood.
Thanks, Schnee.
You can count on me.
Master...
Shin is all right.
I'm so glad!
Also...
I have urgent business.
You'll be coming with me.
Urgent business?
Yes. We're going to the palace.
Shin has gotten caught up
in some kind of trouble.
Apparently one of those is behind it.
One of what?
A demon.
A demon?
I don't like those!
They're monsters born from miasma, right?
Yes. They're enemies who make people suffer.
The chief difference between them
and other monsters
is that they're empowered inside miasma.
They can also disguise themselves
as other monsters.
Monsters afflicted with miasma
indiscriminately attack creatures around them.
The more humanoid a demon is,
the more powerful and intelligent.
Grand Duke Class
Duke Class
Marquis Class
Count Class
Knight Class
Baron Class
Viscount Class
They are ranked accordingly.
Because this one used skills to control a man,
it's likely a relatively intelligent
demon of the count class.
And what level would that make it?
Let's see... 300 at the lowest,
400 at the highest.
And it's still only a mid-rank class, huh?
M-Master, I'm still not even half
the lowest level it could be...
That won't be a problem.
We're just going to observe today.
We're... observing?
Around here should do.
Hiding.
A concealment spell?
Don't tell me we're going to sneak in!
That's exactly what we're doing.
What?
We're going to take a brief flight.
Hold on tight.
What?
What?!
Now, let's sneak into the castle.
Come to think of it,
Master is pretty extreme...
I know we're using Hiding,
but we're walking in so brazenly.
Master, where are we headed?
To the dungeon.
Th-The dungeon?
The demon has already been captured.
What?
Sleep.
You're incredible, Master.
Who's there?
It's good to see you again, Cardinal Greril.
Lady Raizar?
What are you doing here?
I heard you had Charm
and Confusion cast on you.
You know about that?
I remember nothing of them being cast on me.
No matter how hard I try to recall,
all I can conjure are fragments of memories.
Probably an effect of having
two mind-affecting conditions.
Don't worry. The two individuals
who were teleported are safe.
What? Can that truly be?
Yes, I'm certain. It won't be long
before they return.
Please accept my deepest gratitude.
Now that there's nothing to worry about,
why don't we dispel the status effects on you?
Please do.
Here we go.
You've finally revealed yourself.
Th-This...
is the demon?
Count-class Demon
Magnumuk
You have a name?
I see. No wonder you're intelligent.
A silver-haired, blue-eyed high elf...
You're Schnee Raizar.
It's been five hundred years
since I've encountered one of you.
I haven't seen a demon since the cataclysm,
but you're as unsightly as ever.
How vexing. You're always getting in our way!
Of course we are.
You're mine!
A trifle.
Why do you protect the human?
Because it'd be a shame to let him die
over these false charges.
Besides, allowing you to run amok
would disgrace the Moon Sanctum.
The Moon Sanctum...
That's where the high human used to be.
The likes of him defeated many of my kind.
But that's all in the past now.
You think so?
Many warriors forsook this world and left.
The people are still divided,
and corruption is spreading.
The age of man is ending.
Schnee Raizar, join us.
I was wondering what your angle was.
That will never happen.
Why are you so determined to scorn us?
You were abandoned by your master.
What?
What did you just say?
Your master left you behind.
Much time has elapsed
in the high humans' absence.
They will never return.
Do you not resent those who abandoned you?
Do those who now depend
on your power not irritate you?
Ah, so you don't know after all.
What are you talking about?
I probably would have been angry before.
Perhaps I fought based on my emotions.
But you chose the most unfortunate timing.
That's Blue Moon! Could it be...
The high humans have returned?
I doubt I'd even lose
to an Elementail right now.
Wow! So that's the famed...
She's beautiful.
But what is she doing in the castle?
Everyone's staring at my master!
Excuse me.
Lady Raizar? What are you doing here?
Your Majesty, I came to speak with you.
I thought Cardinal Greril
had been thrown into the dungeon.
Yes. I have something to report regarding that.
A demon?
So the enemies of humanity
written about in history books are active...
And using taboo mind-affecting skills, too?
That's a serious problem.
I hope my magic can be used to resist them.
I have good news as well.
The two who were teleported are safe.
Is that true?
What a relief.
I had faith that Her Highness
and Shin wouldn't go down so easily!
This is great news indeed!
I'm terribly sorry for the trouble I caused.
If you were under the effects
of compulsion, it is not your fault.
I hope you'll continue to act
as our liaison with the church.
Certainly, sire! I vow to work
even harder from now on.
Your Majesty, word of disarray in the castle
would unnerve the general populace.
Information control is your top priority.
Very well. What will you do now, Lady Raizar?
There's somewhere I must go.
Excuse me.
E-Excuse us!
Master, what are we going to do now?
We're heading to the walled city of Valmer.
We'll meet Shin there.
But Shin has our wagon. Will we get a new one?
That won't be necessary. We'll run there.
Run?
I'm going to increase my speed. Try to keep up.
W-Wait, Master—
Master, you're too fast!
Next Time
Episode 11
The Closed Holy Land