The Black Blacksmith, huh?
I didn't think there were any
high humans left in the world.
That's true, so there's no way to be certain.
At the very least,
we know we're dealing with someone
insane enough to treat
a weapon like this as disposable.
Gadras, didn't the Black Blacksmith
own the Moon Sanctum?
Yes.
Let's pay a visit when we return.
If the high humans really are back,
what will you do then?
I'll challenge him to a duel.
He'd make a fine spouse, too.
Just so you're aware,
please don't suddenly attack him
and claim you're testing his skills.
I have more common sense than that.
All right, it's high time you spilled the beans.
Why are you acting so hostile out of nowhere?
Schnee Raizar doesn't bow to anyone,
but you got her to follow you?
It's good to see you again, Wilhelm.
What in the world happened?
In short, Schnee defeated the Lord, and—
Whoa! Hey, watch it!
Why give her the credit when you're the one
who unleashed that torrent of mana?
I know it was you!
How'd you find out?!
Because it's obvious.
You popped off that flashy spell
and caught up to us like it was nothing.
The hell's your deal, anyway?!
Wait, wait. Calm down.
No Venom, okay?
Quit screwing around and fess up.
So you're a high human...
He's also my master.
I mean, something like that.
The hell does that mean?
Either way, I guess this
explains all that mana of yours.
Sorry. I was actually holding back there.
Is that right, Mr. Schnee Raizar's Master?!
Are there any remaining records
of us high humans?
Some, sure.
All about how stupidly strong and skilled
with your specialties you are.
There're folks who revere you
as gods to this day.
The others left various
anecdotes behind as well.
That sounds like it's
going to be a headache...
Welp, at least I'm pretty confident
in my blacksmithing.
What? You're a blacksmith?
Yeah. Want me to fix up Venom for you?
Don't be ridiculous.
Let me know if it ever loses its spark.
I'll give you a discount.
You expect me to trust you when you
look like some unscrupulous merchant?
It just gets my inner
blacksmith excited, y'know?
Huh? Shin?
Hey.
Hello.
W-W-Wait! What are you doing here?
You're all right?
Apparently, they made it out somehow.
"Somehow"?
Oh, and who is this?
Nice to meet you. I am Schnee Raizar.
It's a pleasure.
Wait, what did you just say?
Schnee Raizar.
You know, the Schnee Raizar.
Her?
Yeah, her.
Wait, what?!
It's really you!
URP
I'm going to be sick...
Must be because we were running at several
times the speed of a horse. Sorry, Lacia.
It's fine.
You're sure you're okay
parting ways at the gate?
It's fine. Your job was over
when she learned the skill.
If anything happens at the
church, it's our problem.
You're still far more sincere
than your tone suggests.
Whatever.
Here. Take this.
That item that allows you send messages, huh?
Let me know if things go south.
If things got bad enough that I'd use this,
I'd be in a pretty desperate state.
You'd be getting dragged into
a serious situation.
So he doesn't want to involve outsiders?
I understand in principle, but...
Then drag me into it.
After coming this far,
I wouldn't sleep well knowing
I'd abandoned you.
But...
Besides...
I can't abandon the first friend I made here
and the kids he's trying to protect.
What did you just say?
I'm telling you to not worry about it
and just contact me!
I'm getting embarrassed now,
so take it already!
I won't show any restraint, you hear?
That's fine. You can count on me.
You haven't changed, Shin.
You think?
You've always been this way.
You've never boasted
about your almighty strength
while protecting the weak equally.
Let's get a move on, Schnee.
Right.
Moon Sanctum
Something smells nice.
Uh-oh. My stomach is growling.
Hungry!
It's time for dinner, anyway.
Why don't we eat first?
Master, welcome back!
Like I wrote in that message card,
someone claiming to know you
showed up, and...
First, calm down. You've lost your cool.
Wait, huh?
How are you two together?
Hi again.
Well, uh, we've been through a lot.
How about dinner first?
Indeed, it will be a rather lengthy story.
Very well. But is Shin going to eat with us?
Naturally.
What do you mean by that?
Come to think of it, I haven't told you yet.
This is Shin, owner of the Moon Sanctum.
That's me.
You're the owner? Oh, the owner, of course...
Y-You're the owner?!
Aren't you a bit too surprised?
It'd be weirder if I weren't!
The owner of the Moon Sanctum
is a legendary high human.
I identified myself when we met, didn't I?
Obviously, I didn't take you seriously!
But there's no way my master could be mistaken.
Which means...
F-Forgive me for not realizing
you were the owner!
What?
Oh, right. It's like she just
found out someone
she's been talking casually
with is actually her boss.
Don't worry about it. I know how you feel.
What? Um, okay, but...
Seriously, don't sweat it.
I'd honestly prefer to skip the formalities.
You won't throw me out?
I wouldn't do that.
Moon Sanctum
And there we have it!
Also, I'm a little late on the introduction,
but since you're already in shock,
this is my Elementail partner, Yuzuha.
Moon Sanctum
Yuzuha hungry!
An Eleme— Wait, it talks?
Nice work, Schnee. This all looks good.
I've never seen any of these dishes before.
You went all-out, Master.
Of course I did.
Giving you those ingredients was
totally worth it for food like this!
Pray tell, what ingredients did you
give her, exactly?
There's some kind of aura around the food.
An aura? I don't see anything.
But let me think...
The meat was cuts of
Thermal Lion and Orc King.
The vegetables were
blood radish and karima onion.
The fruits were ideah and topaz pear.
The rest was whatever looked good.
And you added what you had on hand, right?
Yes. Since it's a special occasion,
I chose the best of the best.
But...
That said, I didn't have time
to make anything elaborate.
So you're saying you can do even better?
I'm looking forward to that.
As you should.
Wait a minute.
Are you serious?!
You're talking about high-end ingredients
that are impossible to get!
And no one would ever think to cook with them!
What? Really?
Anyway, Schnee, what's with the aura?
"Anyway"?!
It's the remnants of the mana
or life force in the ingredients.
You often see it with powerful
monsters and rare plants.
Huh, you don't say.
Are you even listening to me?
Calm down, Tiera.
Let's eat before the food gets cold.
O-Okay...
Right.
Well, thanks for the meal!
Thanks for the meal.
Thanks!
Tiera, you give thanks for meals, too?
My master does,
so I figured I should as well.
I started doing it because you did, Shin.
I see. That's kind of funny.
Moon Sanctum
So the other support characters
are living their own lives now, huh?
It was wishful thinking to hope
that you were still out there somewhere.
I think we all understood
it was best not to fret for you.
Personally, I appreciate that.
I wouldn't want you guys looking
for someone who may not even be around.
Even if we'd done so,
it would've been of our own free will.
It's nothing you should worry about.
You think so?
Are you sad, Shin?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Honestly. You worry too much
about everything, Shin.
Tiera, you're drunk, aren't you?
Hey, I see two Masters!
She sounds pretty far gone.
Is she a lightweight?
I've never seen her like this before.
I'll put her to bed.
Sure. Good luck.
Come on, Tiera. Can you stand?
I'm totally fine!
This place hasn't changed.
I feel the most relaxed here.
Yuzuha?
Already asleep, huh?
Guess I'll hit the hay too.
Something feels heavy...
Yuzuha?
Nope, you're over there...
It's kind of fluffy.
It's soft and warm and smells nice...
What?! Seriously? What's going on here?!
I can't believe this is actually happening!
Th-This is really, really bad...
Schnee?
...ter.
Master.
I don't know what these tears mean,
but I'm sorry, Schnee.
It's so bright...
Schnee?
She's up already.
What's this silver hair?
Yuzuha
Elementail
Yuzuha?
Wait, what?!
So loud...
Good morning, Shin!
That is not the right response!
Put something on!
Why?
Please, just do it!
Shin warm!
If anyone sees this, I'm done for.
Put this on.
What's this?
I just made it for fun,
but it's what Elementails typically wore
in human form in the game.
It'll adjust to your size. Let me know
if you prefer a different color, too.
I like this!
Don't stand up!
Shin...
You should've said
you don't know how to put it on.
Good morning.
Oh, Yuzuha can transform into a person, too?
What beautiful red hakama.
G-Good morning.
And good morning to you, too.
I'll prepare another table setting.
Thanks for the meal!
You're welcome.
Moon Sanctum
By the way, Yuzuha, I have questions for you.
What?
First, why were you at that shrine?
I was there because it was
the least uncomfortable inside.
Do you know what that symbol
written on the floor was?
I dunno.
I thought it might slow
or alleviate symptoms, but...
Okay, second question.
Do you know anything about lots of people
disappearing five hundred years ago?
I dunno.
People didn't come by often.
So, what were you doing there?
Let's see. I was napping in the sun.
Then the ground suddenly went blam,
and the wind went whoosh,
and the mountain went kaboom!
It startled me awake.
Then I made sure the ground
wouldn't get messed up.
In other words, there was a natural
disaster, and you tried to stop it?
That sounds correct.
Elementails can use
all the elements, after all.
I suspect they intervened with the natural
disaster in some special way.
All that effort made me hurt,
so I was resting in the shrine.
And just when I thought I might die,
you showed up!
So I barely made it in time.
It's because of Millie
that I was able to save you.
I'm gonna thank Millie later!
Good idea. We should bring her a gift.
In that case, how about cafalle?
Cafalle?
It's a type of elven baked treat Tiera makes.
I sold some on a whim, and now they're
one of our top products!
The Moon Sanctum doesn't
primarily sell food, though.
Even if we wanted to replenish our stock,
you're the only one who can unlock the armory.
Oh, right. Sorry.
I'll make a few swords later
to replenish the store's inventory.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, but there's something else
we should discuss.
What is it?
There's someone I'd like you
to meet as soon as possible.
Who?
It's... Girart.
Girart, huh?
Wait, do you really mean Girart?
Moon Sanctum
He's alive?
It's been 500 years
since the Dusk of Prosperity.
High beasts like Girart only live 150 at most.
A few days won't make a difference, but he
probably doesn't have much longer to live.
He's been waiting for you as well.
He has?
You're aware he united
the various beast tribes
and formed the
Farnid Beast Alliance, aren't you?
Yeah. They called him
the first beast king, right?
The current king is the eighth.
He has all the military might
and abilities of a leader,
which has allowed Girart
to wait for you in peace.
Then I gotta go see him.
He's not in any immediate danger, right?
No.
Then I'll travel normally.
I'd like to check on a few things first.
Will you two be ready to leave tomorrow?
Sure.
I'll watch the shop like usual.
You'll be coming with us this time, Tiera.
I'm going too?
Now that Shin is back, we don't need to be
so particular about this location.
But what about the shop?
Oh, it'll be fine. We'll bring it with us.
B-Bring it with us?
In any case, don't worry about the shop.
You can finally leave this place now.
I think it would be good
for you to travel with us.
What will you do?
If you two will be traveling together,
I'd like to go with you.
Then it's decided.
Everyone together!
Well, let's start getting ready.
I guess all we have to do
is buy food and equipment...
I'll report on the Skullfaces to the kingdom.
May I act independently for a while?
Sure thing.
I'll head to the guild
after I make a few swords.
While we're split up,
I'll look for a job in the direction
of Farnid so I can try to rank up.
Where shall we meet back up?
I'll let you know by message card.
Then let's form a party.
That way, we'll be able to use voice chat.
For real?
These days it's known as telepathy.
Player Guide
Settings
System
Party
That should do it.
Perhaps you should take this opportunity
to register as an adventurer, Tiera.
Very well.
Wanna go to the guild together?
In that case, I should find something
appropriate to wear.
I'll wait for you at the forge.
I'll come with you!
Then I shall be taking my leave now.
See you later, Master.
Wow! This is the forge?
You can look, but don't touch.
Some of these weapons are cursed.
Everything still looks usable.
What are you going to do?
Make some swords.
I intuitively know where to strike.
Must be the benefit of my skill.
That's one blade done.
I tried too hard.
I unintentionally imbued it with magic, too.
It's way beyond the level of anything
available in this nation's shops.
Failure?
Not a failure. Just not something we can sell.
I've gotten the hang of it now, so I should
get it right in the next couple of tries.
That should be enough
to last the store a while.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Shin!
I didn't think it would take so long.
It's been ages, so I wasn't sure what to wear.
You haven't been out in a century, after all.
Moon Sanctum
It's so nice outside!
The weather is lovely, too.
Yeah, it sure... is?!
It feels great!
Well, shall we get going?
Yup. Uh-huh.
What do you think of my chest?
It's a real sight for sore—
Sheesh. Let's go.
You're paying, Shin.
Seriously?
Of course. That's what you get
for staring at a young woman's chest.
I'm so sorry.
Next Time
Episode 6
Escort Mission