Wide Heal.
Thank you for saving us, Lady Schnee.
We were just thinking
we'd be forced to retreat.
Please.
I was only able to defeat it
because you and your men fought.
You honor us with such praise.
For the past month,
undead that shouldn't be able to leave the
Ghost Plains have been showing up.
We've dispatched elite units
to take care of them.
I can't believe she took down a monster alone
that we've failed to defeat in groups.
I should have expected as much from someone
who once earned a high human's favor.
That was the last of the irregular monsters
mentioned in your report, correct?
Yes. I hope that's the end of things.
I'll continue searching the area.
If anything happens,
launch that magic item I gave you.
Will do.
Farewell.
Master!
I finally get to see him again.
Wil!
Don't just stand there. Finish it off.
R-Right!
Heal.
Wh-What's happening?
Lacia!
Don't worry.
This effect occurs when you meet
the conditions to learn a new skill.
Hey, Lacia!
Huh?
You look lost in thought. Are you okay?
I-I'm fine.
My mind was suddenly flooded with
images of how to use the skill.
Well, in any event,
you've successfully learned Purify.
Congratulations.
Nice work.
Thank you.
Now we'll be able to save the orphanage.
After a short break, let's leave
the sealed area and return to Bayrelicht.
Yeah. No reason to stick around.
What was that sound?
What is that?
Hey, what are... you...
The hell's going on?
It's pretty...
That's the magic matter
that animates undead.
Magic matter?
Yeah. Drain it from monsters until they
can't maintain their form, and they vanish.
Skullface Lord
Monster
Level 804?
What an unbelievable monster.
Oh, no...
A creature of that level could
destroy an entire nation.
We have the seal. W-We'll be okay, right?
Yeah, I don't know about that.
So much for the seal, right?
Yeah. That blow would've shattered it.
This can't be...
Hey, it's looking our way.
Yup.
Run for it!
Not gonna let us escape, huh?
No, that's not it.
Wil, what should we do? Hey, Wil!
Keep it together.
Shouting won't help anything.
C'mon, Shin! Let's break
through them and flee.
No. I'm staying here.
What? What're you talking about?
You got a death wish?
Limit Off.
Now that the seal is gone,
I can't allow these monsters to roam free.
I'll stop them here and now
before they cause more damage.
You two make a break for the kingdom.
This power...
Just who are you?
Take care of Yuzuha and Lacia for me.
You've got some explaining
to do once we're back.
Sure.
I'll cast a physical enhancement buff on you.
You'll run faster than normal, so don't trip.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Hey. The fox won't let go of you.
Ow, ow, ow! Come on, Yuzuha.
Fine. You'd better not leave my side.
Looks like you reached an agreement.
Yeah. I'll clear the way for you.
Lightning Banker!
Go!
They're off.
Let's get started, too.
Fox Fire, huh? Nice one, Yuzuha.
If this happens every time it roars,
we'll be here forever.
Yuzuha, this is gonna get a little wild.
Hold on tight.
Flying Sparrow Thunder Strike!
That took out a decent number of them.
Ugh, the map is solid red.
If only Schnee were here,
I'd have more options for fighting them.
A blue marker?
Blue is for allies.
But wait. If it's getting closer, then...
Yuzuha, we're gonna make a quick detour.
H-How have you been?
Read the room, guys.
Yuzuha?
A barrier, huh? Thanks, Yuzuha.
Schnee—
S-Schnee?
Don't you have something to say?
Um, sorry for abandoning you all this time?
Not that.
Th-Thanks for watching over the shop?
She doesn't want an apology or thanks.
What does that leave?
Moon Sanctum
What haven't I said yet?
What should I be saying?
Oh, right.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
I thought you'd never return.
I bet.
Ending the death game
should have wiped my save data,
including the Moon Sanctum, Schnee,
and my other followers.
Yuzuha?
The barrier wore off.
We've got a lot to discuss,
but why don't we deal with this first?
Right.
I figured we can fire off one huge attack.
A good idea.
We've got just the thing for it.
Here we go.
It's been a while
since we last worked together.
It has.
That which is pure, reveal yourself.
That which is eternal, reveal yourself.
Sanctuary!
Master!
Wait.
Give... that power... to me...
Did this thing... just talk?
Master, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. All good here.
In the end, I didn't learn anything.
Feels like I should have been able to, though.
Guess that's that.
It certainly seems that way.
This place will return
to how it once was eventually.
Since we're here, we don't we chat a little?
Very well.
Do you remember sending me off
when I went to defeat Origin?
Yes.
Well, I slew him, which should've
put an end to everything.
Destroy
Create
Collect
System
Player Guide
Settings
Log Out
But there were these huge doors
in the dungeon boss room.
And when I beat the boss, they opened.
Doors, you say?
Yeah. Then I lost consciousness
and woke up in a field.
So it's not like I just
wandered off for 500 years.
I see. So that's what happened.
Schnee?
It's nothing.
The dungeon disappeared without a trace.
When other players' support characters
started saying their masters had vanished,
I knew you'd cleared the dungeon.
But we found it strange that we remained
when we should've disappeared with you,
so we decided to look for you.
However, seismic shifts
threw the continent into chaos,
so we split up to work separately.
I returned to the Moon Sanctum,
which brings us to the present.
That more or less lines up with my research.
Master, is there something on your mind?
No. It's nothing.
By the way, Schnee...
Could you stop calling me "Master"?
What's wrong with calling my master "Master"?
It would cause a fuss if someone overheard
a legend like you addressing me that way.
I see. Then how shall I address you?
Huh? Can't you just call me by my name?
I-I daren't...
What's wrong, Schnee?
W-Well, in that case...
Shin.
Y-Yeah.
I thought my heart would give out!
What?
Oh, nothing. Really, it's nothing.
Anyway, call me Shin from now on.
Very well, Shin.
Good!
Shin, what are you going to do now?
Well, first I'm thinking of visiting
the sacred site I read about
in my research at the kingdom's library.
Ever been there?
Yes. Only for a cursory
investigation, however.
I don't know what it's like on the inside.
I see.
Then I'll have to go check it out myself.
If you find a way to leave this place,
will you return home?
Yeah.
I see...
Of course you will.
Sorry.
It's all right. I figured you'd say that.
Say, Schnee...
How much do you remember from the game?
Everything.
Everything?
Everything from the day
we descended to this land together.
I remember it all.
Don't bother telling me to forget it.
I wouldn't do that.
I became more aware during the period
you and the others called the death game.
Until then, it was like I'd been
watching a video
or observing the situation from above.
I see.
In other words, they knew
they'd disappear after we logged out.
When I think about what you guys
must've been going through then...
If we'd said anything,
it only would have troubled you.
It was the right choice at the time.
I see.
We weren't completely autonomous then,
so either way, we couldn't have done anything.
Even so, you can't expect me not to second
guess it now that I know you were self-aware.
You're as difficult as ever, Shin.
Shut up. Leave me alone.
But even if you'd known,
you still would have gone to fight.
Well, yeah.
Besides, we made a promise.
Yeah.
Now, then...
That's enough solemn talk.
Let's not spoil our reunion.
Right? Let's party once we're back
at the Moon Sanctum.
Yes, let's.
But first, I'd like to ask you something else.
Who is this?
Oh, right.
It's a long story, but we're partners now.
Meet Yuzuha.
Between you and me, Yuzuha's an Elementail.
An Elementail?
I knew it was no ordinary spirit
when I saw those tails, but...
You could tell by the tail?
Have you not noticed?
There are three...
Good morning, Shin.
What?! Wait a minute, Yuzuha.
You can talk now?
My head cleared up
when that black stuff disappeared.
Black stuff?
Come to think of it, the shrine
was surrounded by Skullfaces, too.
That Lord must've been their leader.
In any case, no speaking in front of people.
Aw.
Normal spirit foxes don't speak.
Then can I speak inside your head?
You mean telepathy? That's fine.
But Shin, now that it has more tails,
you can't pass it off as a Little Fox.
Yuzuha, can you merge your tails into one?
Piece of cake!
Impressive.
Can you do this when we're around people?
Sure thing.
Well, that was an easy solution.
Was I good?
Yes, very good.
How cute.
N-Nothing.
Wanna pet it?
Yes, please.
You always find ways to surprise me, Shin.
No one has ever successfully
tamed an Elementail before.
You seem pretty calm in spite of that.
I was surprised, but I figured
you of all people could pull it off.
Unlike the one we fought previously,
this one isn't high-level.
Pulling your punches to weaken one
would would be no easy feat.
Normally, you can't let your
guard down around their kind.
We should get going.
All right.
Oh, right. I sent my companions
back without me.
Then we should hurry.
We may be able to catch up to them.
You're right. We'll go as quick as we can.
Don't want anyone reporting this to the guild.
If you'd told me that sooner,
we could have saved our talk for later.
I couldn't wait after seeing your face.
This and that are entirely separate matters.
Okay, let's go.
All right.
Hey, Wil. Shin will be okay, right?
Don't worry. You know how strong he is.
But...
Something's coming. At a crazy-fast speed, too.
Wil...
Stay back!
Did that monster follow us?
It's coming in hot.
We'll engage it here.
Hey, Wilhelm.
Looks like we caught up.
Is something wrong?
Don't confuse me like that!
Look at the ground here.
What happened?
Have you learned anything?
No. I'm sorry, Lady Rionne.
I see.
After we heard that mysterious voice,
a horde of Skullfaces suddenly appeared.
Then that light filled the sky.
The Skullfaces turned to dust,
and we were all healed.
Who could've been responsible?
Forgive me for interrupting you,
but could you take a look at this?
What is it?
It was on the ground
at the far end of the fissure.
It was jammed at the starting point,
so I believe this sword was the origin.
I don't know what kind of skill
did it, though.
I see.
The thing is...
What do you see on this sword here?
Some kind of bird?
Yes. I believe it's what's known as a falcon.
I know a blacksmith
who carves these on their swords.
Watch this.
Well, well.
Not only did it not break,
but it's still this powerful, even nicked.
As far as I'm aware,
there's only one smith
who forges swords this fine
and engraves their work with falcons.
Who?
A high human.
The Black Blacksmith, the most
skilled smithy of his kind.
Next Time
Episode 5
A Momentary Break