Rionne, do you know anything
about the holy land?
Well...
Holy lands are cities that fell
during the Dusk of Prosperity.
This is my first time entering one,
but I heard it takes several chosen ones
to take down the monsters that appear within.
Then we'll need weapons.
Fortunately, I was teleported with this.
The Skullface's sword!
Good. That'll do nicely.
I'm all set, but what about you?
Do you have any weapons?
Don't worry about me.
I can't let the princess find out
how strong I really am.
If she learns I can use dozens of skills,
she'll never let me leave.
However...
Getting out of here without using my
full strength will be next to impossible.
The Holy Land, Calkia, has gates
in the four cardinal directions.
When our people inspected the city,
they entered through the south.
There's a small door not far from it.
Behind it should be a device
for opening and closing the gate.
There's no need for us
to wander through the city.
I'd like to take a shortcut to the gate.
What do you think of climbing the wall?
What?
What was that?
Sorry. Let me try again.
Sure.
Rionne, how did that look to you just now?
You definitely jumped,
but you vanished once you were above
the wall and reappeared on the ground.
I see.
Am I being teleported?
Shin?
What's going on?
You're moving strangely.
I know why now. Come with me.
Found you.
This is it.
A ball of light?
It functions just like in the game.
If one of these is here,
this entire city must be a dungeon.
What?
I've never heard of a city
becoming a dungeon before.
It does seem to work a bit differently
from your standard dungeon.
We can only reach the exit of this
dungeon by following a set route.
So you couldn't reach the rooftops
or pass through the hole because...
Yup.
Straying from the route sends you
back to where you were before.
We'll have to follow those
spheres in order to escape.
I don't see any traps, so we just need
to follow the spheres
and defeat any monsters,
and we should be able to get out.
I see.
Forgive me for saying so,
but I'm glad you got teleported with me.
You saved me from having
to crack the mystery myself.
The pleasure is all mine, Your Highness.
Yeah, right.
Now, let us find these spheres
and advance through the dungeon.
Let me know if anything seems off.
This is a holy land.
There's no telling what could happen here.
Got it.
That sphere should teleport us
to the next location.
I'll go first.
I'll come right back if it's all clear.
Wait here.
It takes you to a place not far from here.
The vicinity is safe.
Let's go.
Sorry for saddling you with a dangerous role.
It's fine.
I couldn't allow a princess to teleport first.
Besides, even if it drops me
into a horde of monsters,
escaping would be a piece of cake for me.
And even if they're dangerous,
I can instantly slaughter them
if I'm not being watched.
I promise I'll repay the favor.
Now, let's both get out of here alive together.
Of course. Now, then...
There's a monster around the corner.
Got it.
What is that?
It's a ghost-type monster
known as a Ghillie Waiz.
It uses earth and wind magic.
Monster           Ghillie Waiz
It moves irregularly, so be careful.
It opened with an unbelievable spell!
So this is a monster of a holy land...
I'll handle this.
Rionne, try to land a blow on him.
Understood.
I'm counting on you.
Good timing.
You're mine!
Flame Edge!
Fiery Ashes!
That should do it.
That was surprisingly easy.
The Skullface's sword is enchanted with light.
That's the Ghillie Waiz's weakness.
I see.
By the way, Shin, what is that sword?
It's called Kakura.
It's a mid-tier mythic arm.
Wow.
You were hiding
quite an impressive weapon.
Well, yeah. Everyone should keep
a card or two up their sleeve.
Of course, I've got more than one or two.
Huh.
I'm suddenly very interested in you.
How many monsters can you sense within range?
More than twenty.
Monsters typically don't leave
their territory within a dungeon,
but we can't let our guard down.
It'd be great if we could reach
the gate without issue.
We should avoid as much danger
as possible as we go.
Right.
It's annoying that I can't
flex my skills right now.
Why do I have to play with restrictions
when I'm not in the game world?
A ball of light?
I'll check it out first.
What is that?
Monster                     Gillslai
A Gillslai. We've run into
a troublesome monster.
What are you talking about?
A large slime should pose
no problem whatsoever!
Hey! Don't go charging in!
What is this feeling?
I told you so.
Dust Explosion!
I'm sorry. That was careless of me.
I should know better in a holy land.
Gillslai are nasty foes immune to
bludgeoning, slashing, and weak attacks.
They're also quite intelligent
and will give chase.
So let's defeat it here.
Can you fight?
Yeah. My life is in your hands.
Flare Burst!
Now!
You destroyed its core
with precision. Nice going.
You did far better than I.
Anyway, you're getting
far more casual with me.
It doesn't bother me.
It'd be weirder if you were too polite,
given the circumstances.
Neither of us needs to hold back.
Still, it's better to be proper.
So this is just until we get out of here.
Very well.
By the way, Shin,
why do you keep looking away?
Well, uh... I can almost see a few things.
What do you mean?
Put that on.
Did you see?
Nope.
Liar.
Thank you.
Are you always so thoroughly prepared?
Where I'm from, we have a saying:
"Forewarned is forearmed."
Wise words.
But I wasn't expecting you
to have so many items.
Well, you know. A friend gave them to me.
Huh.
So, I hate to ask when
you've graciously lent this to me,
but don't you have anything baggier?
I mean, this is a little tight.
It is?
Oh, right...
Hey! What are you looking at?
Uh, nothing.
Say, can you not use any magic skills?
I can cast a few beginner-level spells.
But surely they'd be useless
against holy land monsters.
I guess so. Hold on.
Schnee, do you have a minute?
Yes. What is it?
An imitation enchantment?
Yeah. It's not as powerful
since it doesn't use the regular method,
but it'll work as a stopgap measure.
I just wanted to make sure it'd be okay
to teach the princess how to use it.
Normally, I would stop you,
but this is an emergency.
You have no choice but to teach her
as a method of self-defense.
You're right.
Okay.
I'm going to teach you some forgery.
Forgery?
Will that really be good enough?
Yeah. You'll see.
In that case...
Fire!
Here!
It was burned?
That's an imitation enchantment.
In other words, a forgery
of a real fire enchantment.
It'll quickly destroy any weapon
that's not at least legendary,
but it's pretty useful even
if you can't use specialized skills.
Are you sure you should be teaching me
something so valuable?
If such a skill were more widespread,
fewer people would fall to monsters.
I appreciate it, but still...
You gave me this sword and refused a reward.
I've done nothing but take.
As royalty, it's humiliating.
Don't scowl at me like that.
You've acquired useful information.
Shouldn't that make you happy?
Nevertheless, I dislike taking without giving.
Then in exchange, I have a request.
As royalty, please protect
your kingdom and your people.
Everything you want to protect.
Shin...
That's all I ask.
Very well.
I hear you.
I managed to fool her,
but imitation enchantments
were actually an exploit in the game!
But when she looks at me
like that, what can I say?
We're almost there.
Yeah.
Hey, what's wrong?
I suddenly felt like I was being sucked in.
I can't say I felt anything.
Really?
Something inside the holy land's
drawing me in?
What could it be?
Are you curious?
No. We can't head back
into the heart of the city.
Let's keep going.
Is that a monster egg?
No.
Normally, when monsters are born,
the environment is warped
by the concentration of mana,
and the monster breaks out
from the proverbial "shell."
I've never seen anything like this.
Which means it's no ordinary monster.
Between this and that feeling earlier,
it's like something doesn't want us to leave.
Shin, it's emerging.
A griffin?
Is that... ice?
Not good.
Let's jump!
It froze? Seriously?
It instantly tried to mow
us down with its breath.
Talk about ridiculous.
U-Uh, Shin?
Could you put me down now?
Oh, sorry. It was an emergency.
I swear, you're unbelievable.
So, what should we do?
Just getting close to it will be difficult.
I'll act as a decoy.
You strike it from behind.
Will you be all right?
You can count on me.
I doubt it'll hit me,
and even if it does, I can take it.
Got it.
Hey, you frozen chicken! Over here!
What are you aiming for?!
If I draw its attention,
Rionne can try to catch it off guard.
Trick Throw!
Where is he tossing those?
Now's my chance!
Tyrant Beat!
All right!
It only hit me with its wing,
and yet it's still so powerful...
Nice one, Rionne!
If it's primarily ice, then how about this?
Flare Burst!
Did you get it?
Yeah.
The opening you made let me
nail it with one powerful blow.
Now we can leave the...
Seriously? It can heal itself?
I'm positive we defeated it.
It didn't just heal itself.
It completely regenerated.
It's back to perfect health.
How are we supposed to slay it?
Well...
Rionne, could you do me a favor?
You want me to find the device
to open the gate by myself?
Yeah.
I'll attack from the front
and draw its attention again.
In the meantime, you examine
the opening mechanism.
And look for what?
Judging by its unusual regeneration,
it's probably a monster made by magic.
There's a spell somewhere
regenerating the monster.
And that spell has been applied
to the opening mechanism?
It's just a possibility.
Very well.
If I can open the gate,
we could also temporarily
immobilize the griffin and escape.
It's an unknown monster.
It might keep chasing us
even if we leave the dungeon.
But we'll roll with the punches!
Still, will you be all right on your own?
I can handle it.
It's not my first time
fighting something like this.
I'm counting on you!
Sorry, Rionne. Honestly, it doesn't
really matter if there's a spell or not.
No more restrictions.
It's time to go all out.
Limit Off.
I don't know how much of
my power I can safely unleash,
but you'll make a good test subject.
Let's see who can hold out longer!
Found it!
I've defeated it thirty times,
but it keeps coming back.
Since it recovers from physical and magical
damage, I'll have to try sealing it.
What is that white sphere?
This is what I felt before...
Take this!
It absorbed my attack?
It's chancy to charge in
without knowing what it is.
But it's a chance I'll have to take.
I'm being enveloped in golden light...
The sucking feeling is gone.
I'll give it a shot.
It stopped regenerating?
I don't get it, but you're mine!
Flame Strike!
See you.
Just what was that?
Shin!
What was that explosion? Where's the griffin?
As you can see,
I obliterated it without a trace.
How'd you do?
Thanks. Now we can say goodbye
to this dungeon.
Let's hurry out of here.
We're supposed to meet my companions in Valmer.
Valmer is east of the Melt Mountains.
If we head toward the mountains,
we shouldn't get lost.
So you safely escaped the holy land?
I'm glad.
And you'll be camping out tonight
with the princess?
Indeed, there's not much else you can do.
What? I'm not mad.
Goodbye.
Master, what's the matter?
Let's get moving.
What? Already?
Shimmer, can you go even faster?
Then let us be off.
Huh?
I'll keep watch first. Get some rest.
Thanks.
Want some tea?
A tent, clothes, and food...
Don't you think you're a bit too prepared?
I was already all set to hit the road.
And with an item box,
it's easy to travel light.
An item box, huh?
I wish my kingdom had someone like you.
Please ask someone else.
You really won't do it?
No.
No matter what?
No matter what.
Can't you make an exception?
No! Stop rubbing up against me!
Am I attractive enough to fluster you?
You mean you didn't do that on purpose?
You really don't hold back, do you?
But I prefer that.
Doesn't that just mean I'm rude?
As royalty, I'm used to everyone
treating me with respect.
So I like talking to people like you.
Honestly, it suits me much better.
What about your family?
It's been a long time since we
enjoyed each other's company.
Maybe some part of me is
looking for something to replace that.
Well, I don't mind talking to you whenever.
Hey, wait. Why are you snuggling up to me?
Just while we're talking.
Not bothered, are you?
We couldn't let anyone at the castle see this.
No. It's been a while since I haven't
had eyes on me outside of battle.
It's been a really long time...
Sheesh. Just for now, okay?
You're warm.
Are you cold?
That's not what I meant.
Shin?
Smoke?
It's monsters.
An absurd number of them have formed a horde.
Not only that,
but they're headed toward Valmer.
What?!
Next Time
Episode 12
Major Flood