A massive horde
of monsters heading for Valmer?
Don't tell me... Could this be a flood?
A flood?
Yeah.
When the magic matter overflowing from
a holy land coalesces enough,
it transforms, released as monsters.
We call that a flood.
Looks like most of them are low-level.
Why have they set their sights on Valmer?
The area around the holy land
is protected by Mist Garuda.
The only path to avoid
it is the road to Valmer.
Which is why Valmer is fortified.
It serves as a bulwark against such floods.
I see. So they're equipped
to fend these things off, huh?
No.
There are strong soldiers
and chosen ones in Valmer, yes,
but the city always suffers
significant casualties.
And up against a major flood like this...
I should have Schnee hurry, just in case.
There's still time before the
monsters reach Valmer.
We'll hurry there and join the guard.
Shin?
I can't just say "so long, nice knowin' ya"
given the circumstances.
Got it.
So this is Valmer, huh?
Shin, how long until the monsters arrive?
Probably a few days, I'd say.
I see. I'm going to meet with the local lord.
You make your report to the adventurer's guild.
What about after that?
The guild and the army will be essential
to counter a large-scale invasion.
The chosen ones will gather first thing.
Okay, got it.
Welcome to the adventurer's guild.
I'm the guildmaster, Baron Lakt.
My name's Shin.
Shin, eh?
I heard you have information about the flood.
Yes. A flood of primarily humanoid monsters
like goblins and orcs has appeared
in the vicinity of the Holy Land Calkia.
At the speed they're going,
they should reach Valmer in a few days.
That soon?
You sound like you've seen it for yourself.
I saw a large number of monsters
heading towards Valmer near the holy land.
I see.
If that's true, we can begin
preparing right away, but...
Will this make you believe me?
Is that from the Moon Sanctum?
Yes. If you still don't
believe me, ask your lord.
My companion is currently
getting in touch with them.
No, I see now that you aren't lying.
I'm declaring a state of emergency.
If your companion has an audience with
the lord, then the army will act posthaste.
As soon as we get word,
we'll begin evacuating the citizens.
Eliza, get in touch with
the representatives of every guild.
Understood.
What will you do now?
Let me lend you my aid.
That'd be a huge boon.
We're short on chosen ones
to defend the city right now.
Much obliged for the help.
Sure thing.
I should meet back up with Rionne.
I feel like I've seen that before...
"Meow Land"?
Wait, don't tell me this store is...
No, hang on.
Shin, I will be arriving in Valmer shortly.
Got it. Once you're here,
let the lord and guildmaster
know you'll be joining the defense.
Understood.
Also, I found a curious store in Valmer.
It's called Meow Land.
Have you heard of it?
No. I haven't the faintest idea.
I see.
Thanks for handling the rest.
Y-You...
Is that you, Berett?
Well, well! It's good to see you again, Shin.
I was hoping we'd run
into each other someday.
Y-Yeah.
I wasn't expecting to run into a friend's
support character from the game.
But Schnee exists, so I guess it makes sense.
So you'll be helping us turn back the flood?
Yeah. I just finished talking
to the guildmaster.
I see. But if it's just a flood, couldn't
you have wiped it out when you found it?
I was with the second princess
of Bayrelicht at the time.
I can't exactly use my full strength
with her watching.
I see. High humans these days
are practically revered like gods.
I could see a princess proposing to you.
She's actually interested in me, so I'm trying
to deal with the flood
without revealing my true strength.
I see. Well, you're an old friend
of my master's.
If there's any way I can help,
just let me know.
I appreciate it.
Oh, right. I just happened upon
a shop called Meow Land.
That's your friend Hibineko's shop.
Hibineko?!
Hibineko's here in this world?
You didn't know?
Shadow and Holly are here in Valmer too.
They are?
Yes. They're currently out of the city
on business, but they're doing well.
I see.
I thought all three of them
died in the death game.
What are they doing in this world?
I didn't expect you to be so surprised.
I have a list of players in this world.
Would you like to see it?
You do? Show me.
This is the whole list?
Yes, though of course
it's not comprehensive.
Just learning there are other
former players is a shock.
But all the players living here
were involved with me in some way.
Also...
Take a look at this.
What is it?
A running list of known individuals
identified as player killers.
PKs?!
They took out lots of my friends
and other people during the death game.
They're deviants who kill for fun.
When players were first
discovered in this world,
Schnee was the one who insisted
that we look for PKs right away.
She was?
Sounds like she didn't tell you about that.
No. This is the first I've heard
of other players, too.
I see. If I may say so,
as your friend's follower,
that's a clear act of betrayal.
We mustn't deliberately withhold
important information from our masters.
She may be your follower,
but she must be punished.
No way. Schnee would never betray me.
Although, earlier...
It's called Meow Land.
Have you heard of it?
No. I haven't the faintest idea.
I'm just kidding.
Don't worry.
Given Schnee's personality, I can't imagine
she'd try to hurt you by hiding information.
Come on, don't go yanking my chain.
But you're right. Schnee would never
do something like that.
Well, that's enough reminiscing.
I need to get ready for the flood as well.
You do? Will you be fighting too?
Oh, no. Valmer's safe with you around.
I'll be preparing to stock up.
There are plenty of materials
to go around after a flood!
Come to think of it, this guy's
backstory is that he loves money.
I did some research on floods,
and apparently a powerful individual
has appeared amid
low-level hordes a few times.
The larger the flood,
the more likely they are to show.
So maybe, with this flood...
Oh, Shin.
That you, Tiera?
Shin!
Whoa.
I finally got to see you again.
Good timing.
Where's Schnee?
Didn't she finish reporting to the lord?
My master's very popular.
They wouldn't let her leave so easily.
I see. She's got it rough, too.
Master, where are you going now?
To meet with the chosen ones
at the lord's castle.
We'll be working together in battle.
Schnee returned in the middle of the night,
so I never got to ask her about that.
That's a clear act of betrayal.
Is something the matter?
Nope. Let's get a move on.
Schnee, thank you for coming.
Allow me to introduce you.
This is Shin, and this is Tiera.
I am Tauro Yaxfair, lord of Valmer.
A pleasure to meet you.
We don't have much time
before the flood arrives.
The chosen ones will stand outside
of Valmer with knights behind them.
Once they are in firing range,
our second squad, led by Schnee, will
attack with magical area-of-effect skills.
Our first squad and the knights
will handle any monsters that get past you.
I see. Then I shall instruct
the knights personally.
That'd be wonderful. We really appreciate it.
Very well.
They'll be training with my master?
What's wrong, Tiera?
Training with my master is hell.
I feel sorry for them.
Tiera, you'll be participating
in the training as well.
After all, teamwork is important.
I-I'll do my best.
Try not to die, Tiera.
What's this?
No sign of monsters?
No. Monsters normally do appear that far out,
but they've vanished completely.
Probably an effect of the flood.
As far as I know, there's no record
of this happening in the past.
I've experienced it.
The monsters in the area all but disappeared,
then came surging forth like a black wave.
Of course there are no records of that.
It was an in-game event.
I'm glad Schnee played it off.
Do take care.
It's possible there will be a powerful
individual leading such a major flood.
In other words, the event boss.
I'm exhausted.
Good job with your training.
And thank you, Schnee.
I appreciate you handling
that conversation for me.
But of course.
By the way, Schnee, after I disappeared,
did you ever use large-scale
spells in guild battles?
No. After all, I can handle most things
with standard area-of-effect spells.
So I should be careful
about slinging mine around.
Could you try using one
during the opening strike?
Yes. I'm sure that will be
my only opportunity to use them.
What are you up to next, Shin?
Well, since I have the chance,
I guess I'll update my disguises!
I don't like the look on your face...
Moon Sanctum
All done.
Scouts have confirmed
the presence of the monsters.
Should a princess really be
taking part in a fight like this?
A bit late for that old line, don't you think?
It's a good opportunity
to test the sword you gave me.
I see. Then watch the rear.
You got it.
Shin.
Schnee.
There's something I'd like to discuss
once this battle is over.
They're here. Schnee.
Yes.
Blue Judge.
Begin the offensive!
Yeah!
My master's incredible!
But it's not over yet.
Even after all that, they're still coming.
This is no ordinary flood.
Schnee, can you fire off another?
No. It seems I can't repeatedly
use large-scale spells.
Just like in the game.
It's not exactly what we planned,
but I'll kite the second wave of monsters.
Understood.
Say hello to this.
Amber Wave!
Phoenix Sage!
That should do for now.
I'd like to save my best abilities
for later, so the rest is up to you.
Get them!
Don't let your guard down
until they've stopped breathing!
Yeah!
Wow, Tiera!
Shin said he made some
adjustments so I could use it,
but he didn't tell me it'd be this powerful!
Not bad.
Follow Rionne's lead!
Yeah!
Looks like they're not all small fry.
I need to help her!
Tiera?
I think I spent too much mana.
Don't strain yourself.
But at this rate...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You...
You have a letter of introduction.
The name's Wilhelm.
I'm here to save you, princess.
It's that man!
It's good to see you again.
Lacia!
Allow me to restore your mana.
Let's go!
Flashing Blossom!
Full Moon Edge!
Thank you.
But what are you doing in Valmer?
The guild received a request for assistance.
Besides, after what she said...
There are lots of monsters! They're in danger!
Go help Shin!
I doubt he's struggling, though.
What's that?
I'm finally up.
Are you okay?
Wh-Who are you?
Who, me? Well...
Call me Red.
O-Okay.
Sorry, but I need you to clear out.
I can't use my abilities properly
with you guys around.
B-But...
I might end up killing you, too.
That's how this weapon works.
Retreat!
Just who is that guy?
Shin...
That's a cursed weapon, isn't it?
Wh-What is that?
A weapon that instantly slays—
no, consumes everything.
He's a monster.
Kill, kill!
Kill, kill! Kill more!
More, more, more!
Oh, shut up. Cursed weapons are so noisy.
This scythe is perfect for floods
since it attracts enemy aggro, but...
Found it.
A demon.
That's the event boss leading the flood.
A mind-affecting attack, huh? Too bad...
Limit Off.
That won't work against a high human like me.
Shin, the monsters have been exterminated.
We suffered zero casualties.
Roger.
I want to go home.
Same.
I heard they wanted to reward those
who fought admirably against the flood,
but I didn't think they'd hold a ceremony.
If that's the custom in Valmer,
we must endure it.
Sorry to keep you waiting. Let's go.
R-Right...
Stuff like this isn't my thing.
Wilhelm and Lacia said they weren't
interested and left already.
Kindly take my arms, ladies!
How did that sound?
That was so out of character!
You should be glad you have
a lovely lady on each arm today.
I appreciate the escort.
Everyone's looking at us.
Yeah, I'll bet they are.
Shall we move to the edge of the room?
Yeah.
Shin! You finally showed.
Rionne.
Shin, I've been wondering...
Did something happen
between you and the princess?
N-Nothing happened.
She's just interested
in my equipment and spells.
I see. I thought she'd made advances on you.
Oh, uh...
Shin, don't act so distant
after making eye contact with me.
People will stare if I'm with you.
I don't mind at all.
Very funny.
Why are you acting so aloof?
You've already proposed to me and everything.
Hey! That wasn't...
I'm joking. Forgive me for teasing you.
I'm going to get some food.
Don't let me get in your way.
Schnee?
Rionne, could you regale me with tales
of your heroism during the flood?
Of course.
Shin, could you go get a drink for Rionne?
What?
Oh, sure.
It's a nice view.
I'm sorry for stepping away.
Were you jealous?
Well, yes. After all,
I'm not actually your fiancée.
Schnee?
Did Berett tell you?
There are players besides me
in this world, right?
Player killers, too.
Is that what you wanted to talk about?
Yes. I'm sorry for hiding it from you.
But I couldn't tell you.
If you learned of the player killers,
I thought you'd become that Shin again.
The cold Shin who keeps everyone
at arm's length.
If I had as little sense of self as I did
in the game, I could endure it.
But now... Now, I don't think I could.
I can't stop you.
I can't replace her!
Despite knowing that, there's a part
of me that's glad she's gone.
That thought maybe I could replace her.
Maybe I could be your rock.
So I... I...
Sorry.
Please don't apologize.
Don't blame yourself too much.
If I were in your shoes,
I'd probably do the same.
Shin...
Listen. I'm really glad I found you, too.
I thought it was finally all over when I beat
the boss, but then I found myself here again.
I didn't know anyone.
My home felt like a stranger's house.
So when you welcomed me back,
I felt so relieved.
You remembered me.
Of course I did.
Berett called it an act of betrayal,
but I won't hold it against you or punish you.
But I...
I can't hear you. I've already made up my mind.
I've made my decision.
I'll hear no objections.
No more secrets between us.
Okay.
Sorry, Schnee. This all started because I...
Um, Shin, may I ask you something?
What is it?
Do you still love Marino?
Yeah. My feelings haven't changed.
I see. I understand.
I won't give up. I love you.
I know you'll return to your world someday,
but my feelings for you are real.
W-We should head back inside.
I wasn't expecting this...
I still don't know how to return to my world.
I'm worried about the player killers
I crossed in the game, too.
And if the friends I thought were dead
are actually alive, then maybe...
Let's go.
On to the next town!
Thank you for watching