Quratar Labyrinth
Seventh Floor
Fireball!
Impressive as always, Master.
Rabbit Pelt
We've gathered quite a few of those.
Yeah, thanks to you.
Imperial City
Rabbit pelts?
Yes.
I doubt the guild will pay us much for them,
but I've heard the clothing stores
here will buy them for a high price.
But why? It's a low level item.
Coats made from rabbit pelts make
exceptional cold weather clothes.
They're very popular among noble women.
I see.
So there's demand for them.
Thank you for waiting, Master.
What'd they say?
They'll buy them from us if
we have at least one hundred.
There's one.
Slow Rabbit: Lv 7
It pains my conscience.
This pains my conscience, but...
Fireball!
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
This way.
Seems like we'll have plenty
in no time, thanks to you.
I'm glad to be useful.
It was worth coming so early
in the morning, Master.
It's a treasure chest.
This is a treasure chest?
The ground here isn't made of dirt.
Quratar Labyrinth, Seventh Floor
Boss Waiting Room
Rapid Rabbit: Lv 7
The only thing different about
this one is that it's red.
It's still pretty cute.
I take it back.
It's fast.
Quit scurrying around.
Roxanne never ceases to amaze me.
It thinks it can hit me, huh?
But that's what you call overconfidence.
Overwhelming!
I've got my own way of doing things.
Impressive, Master.
It was so quick, even I
nearly lost sight of it.
Thanks, Roxanne.
Rabbit Meat
Did it have to drop it on the ground?
I'll have to wash that
thoroughly when we get home.
Rabbit meat...
Perfect. We can have it for lunch.
In that case, how do you
feel about a schema roast?
Schema roast?
Quratar, Michio's House
First, sprinkle salt and
pepper on the rabbit meat.
Then wrap them in schema leaves
from the yard and skewer them.
Finally, drizzle olive oil over
the meat so it chars nicely,
and your schema roast is ready to eat.
This really is good.
Maybe we should gather some more rabbit
meat while we're collecting pelts.
I see you've developed
a taste for rabbit meat.
Quratar Labyrinth, Seventh Floor
Master, the Boss Room is up ahead.
Boss Waiting Room
He's alone, huh?
Looks like there's a little bit of a wait.
Are you a two-person party?
Yeah. You're alone, huh?
That must be tough.
I'm trying to save up money
to gather party members,
but I can't help but spend money.
In other words, he wants to buy slaves.
He's like how I used to be.
It's been more than two years since I
started coming to the seventh floor.
My Explorer level has risen,
so I thought I'd take this
opportunity to go higher.
I see. Well, good luck.
Thank you.
If I beat the next boss,
I'll finally be able to acquire
my first party member.
Looks like luck is finally turning my way.
If you'll excuse me.
Two years on the seventh floor?
Then he's a veteran of labyrinths.
There are limits to what
you can accomplish alone.
I was once in the same boat,
so I understand that very well.
Master, it's our turn.
Okay. Let's go.
The boss is already waiting for us?
We haven't seen this before.
There might be something
special about this encounter.
I'll use Overwhelming off
the bat and finish it off.
Let me handle this, Roxanne.
Overwhelming!
Nothing unusual happened.
What's going on?
What's that?
Huh. Sometimes there's
equipment in Boss Rooms, huh?
I believe that equipment belonged
to the party that entered before us.
Really?
Yes, since the boss was already
in the room when we entered.
It was already waiting in
the room for the next party
since it had beaten the previous group.
That's a black Magic Crystal.
If you press your own Magic Crystal
against it, they should merge easily.
If I beat the next boss, I'll finally be
able to acquire my first party member.
Looks like luck is finally turning my way.
If you'll excuse me.
That friendly guy was beaten by that boss.
Is this all our lives are worth?
Is something wrong, Master?
No.
Let's go home.
Quratar, Michio's House
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Master...
You're so rough today.
I knew the labyrinths were a dangerous place.
That people lost their lives there.
But it was just a fact I knew.
That Explorer in line ahead of us challenged the boss
and disappeared.
There's no guarantee that
won't be me tomorrow.
It wouldn't be surprising if my own
position suddenly changed in the future.
Labyrinths are like rickety bridges.
Depending on which plank you step on,
the floor could fall out from beneath you.
Why am I crossing that kind of bridge?
No, I shouldn't think that way.
When the night is so quiet,
I can't stop thinking about it.
Master?
You can't sleep?
I'll fall asleep eventually.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Come here.
Roxanne?
If there's anything I can
do to help, I'll do it.
After all, you're my master.
I don't know if she knew what I was thinking,
but she's warm.
Thank you, Roxanne.
Not at all.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
I'm happy, too.
Quratar, Michio's House
Good morning, Roxanne.
Good morning, Master.
Have you calmed down?
Quratar Labyrinth
The Explorer we met yesterday is dead.
Spy Spider
Escape Goat
It's still true that
could be me tomorrow, but...
Right now, all I can do is get stronger
so I won't be weak anymore.
Even if I step on the wrong plank,
I just need to become
strong enough to hang on.
Master.
All right. I'm not having trouble fighting.
Item Box.
Item Box
We've saved up 300 of them, huh?
Roxanne, let's head to the Imperial City.
Yes, Master.
Welcome.
I'd like to sell 300 rabbit pelts.
Thank you. This way, please.
We gathered this many?
I'm sorry, but given how many there
are, this will take some time.
Is that all right?
I'm not surprised.
In that case, we'll pass
the time in the shop.
Thank you.
The display room is in the back.
They've got camisoles. They're made of silk.
It's not transparent,
but it's still pretty sheer.
If Roxanne wore this...
That product is very popular
among noble women as sleepwear.
What do you think, Roxanne? It's not bad.
Um, I...
How much?
Eight hundred nars.
Then, I'll take two.
Are you sure?
Don't worry about it.
This is to thank you for yesterday.
Thank you.
Let's get one of these light pink ones.
I agree. For the other...
Thank you for waiting.
You can choose the other one.
Yes, Master.
I counted exactly 300 pelts.
Each one is worth 10 nars,
but since you brought so many,
I'd like to give you a bonus.
Sure, thanks.
I have a feeling that was just my 30%
bonus coming into effect, but whatever.
Quratar, Michio's House
Thank you for buying sleepwear for me.
Um, I'll wear one of these when
you take care of me tonight.
Could you choose one?
Of course, but first...
Let's take a bath.
This part still sucks.
Roxanne.
Yes, Master.
I'm heading to the Quratar labyrinth.
Could you give me a hand?
I ran out of MP to make hot water with.
Understood. I'll get ready right away.
Quratar Labyrinth
Seventh Floor
Monsters ahead.
Same old, same old.
Let's get this over with.
Cheep Sheep: Lv 7
Paunch: Lv 7
Collagen Coral: Lv 7
And once this is over,
I've got a camisole waiting for—
Master!
Are you all right?
Let me heal you.
I'm fine. It's just a scratch.
I wish I could go back in time a few seconds
and tell myself overconfidence
is my greatest enemy.
My finger still feels swollen.
I'm pretty sure I recovered using Durandal.
Are you all right, Master?
It might heal quicker if you sucked on it.
What?
Um, I've heard a little spit is enough
to heal scratches, but I've never...
It's worth a shot.
This is my first time doing this,
so let me know if it hurts.
It's so wet and warm.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It feels good more than not.
Keep going.
How was that?
The pain's completely gone. Thank you.
That wasn't difficult for you, was it?
It was surprisingly long, so I wasn't
sure I'd be able to fit it in my mouth,
but it was fine since you stayed still.
This makes me want to go further.
I really want to go further.
I was actually hit somewhere else, too.
Could you suck this, too?
Yes, Master.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
It does look a little swollen.
Allow me.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Did that hurt?
No, quite the contrary.
She's covering her teeth with her tongue so they don't scrape me.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
All her attentiveness is paying off.
Maybe it's because she's gotten the hang of it, but
she's way better now than when she was sucking my finger.
I had a painful experience
today, but this evens it out.
No, this is better than even.
This is what you call a fortunate error.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
What an incredible way to be healed.
That was amazing.
Thanks to you, the pain is completely gone.
I-I see. Was that useful?
More than useful.
I thought you'd cast a spell on me.
I'm not sure my mouth can do that.
Oh, it certainly can.
Roxanne, you worked hard for me.
It's the same as healing magic.
Master...
What do you think?
That looks great on you.
Thank you.
The light pink adds a touch
of color to her skin
as it elegantly and gently
envelops Roxanne's body.
These two mountains are the exception.
They jut upwards sharply,
and tiny little delicacies
can be found on their peaks.
Her clothes are trim,
but what's beneath is out of control.
Roxanne, could you spin around for me?
Yes, Master.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Roxanne, you're not wearing
anything underneath?
Well, it'd be visible
beneath these clothes,
and I thought you'd prefer this.
Oh, I love it.
You look incredible.
Thank you.
I'm glad I bought these.
Between the smoothness of the
silk and Roxanne's skin,
I can't wait any longer.
Although in that regard,
this wasn't such a good purchase.
Quratar Labyrinth
Firestorm!
In that case, one more.
Master.
I can't cast it in time.
Fireball!
This jerk.
It took all that to kill three?
It'll be tough for our
current party to handle
the groups of up to four we've started
encountering on the eighth floor.
I need to seriously consider
expanding our party.
Huh? We only got two even
though we defeated three?
Great news, Master.
Look at this.
This is a Skill Crystal.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem