This is the story of a possible future.
It's been ten years, huh?
Master?
What is it, Roxanne?
What are we doing here?
This place seems perfectly ordinary.
The kind of rural farming
village you'd find anywhere.
Is it perhaps a health resort?
Are we here on vacation?
No, this place is an
ordinary village. I just...
I came here once, a long time ago.
What? Here?
Yeah.
Back before I met you, Roxanne.
It's a stable.
Is there something special about this place?
Yeah.
Just remembering what it was like.
I do feel nostalgic for this place,
but I don't remember it very well anymore.
Durandal
Offensive Power x5
HP Absorption
MP Absorption
Incantation Interruption
Hey. Do you remember me?
Or are you a different horse?
If so, the thief who stole those
sandals has nothing to worry about.
Is something the matter?
I was just thinking his
hair is an unusual color.
You mean his black hair?
You don't often see that around here.
It's like yours.
Yeah, you're right.
Identify
Mio
<Male 9 Years Old>
Lv 1
Mio and Michio, huh?
He's exactly the right age, too.
Well...
That must be what happened.
What are you planting?
Kyupiko.
Kyupiko, huh?
That's this village's specialty, isn't it?
Are your parents doing well?
My mom is.
But my dad died before I was born.
I see. Do you listen to your mom?
Yeah.
Good.
Item Box
Identify
Scimitar of Rage
Offensive Power x5
HP Absorption
Give this sword to your mother.
If she allows it, then it's yours.
What?
Use this sword to protect your mother.
But...
Don't be shy.
Now, listen here.
Picking up that sword
doesn't make you stronger.
It's the sword that's strong.
Don't forget that.
Okay.
Thanks, mister.
Mister, huh?
Sorry, Roxanne. I let someone else have
the sword I originally gave to you.
I don't mind.
Who was that boy?
I've never met him before.
But I probably know that child's father.
Let's go.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
Vale
Vale Restaurant
Thirty-three gold coins
are worth 330,000 nars.
I'll use my silver coins to
pay the leftover amount,
which means I need 70,000 more.
If that slave trader is to be believed,
there are two ways for
me to quickly make money.
A labyrinth?
Yes. It was discovered in the
woods to the west the other day.
Is that not why you came to this town?
I didn't come here on purpose.
Is exploring labyrinths
something adventurers do?
Yes. After all, they can sell the items
they acquire by defeating demons.
For those confident in their abilities,
labyrinths are a guaranteed income source.
However, it's difficult to make a large
amount of money over a short period of time.
So collecting bounties would be quicker.
It certainly is good money,
but I wouldn't recommend it.
Why not?
Because bandits would rather
get rid of bounty hunters.
If you attract too much attention...
You'll find yourself the target instead.
Indeed.
Furthermore, while it's more efficient
than exploring labyrinths,
not many bounties are worth the risk.
I see.
I still have five more days to buy Roxanne.
I'll try the reliable method first.
I'll head to the labyrinth.
But first, I've gotta deal with this.
Fighting those bandits made one thing clear.
This weapon is amazing,
to an excessive degree.
People are likely to come after me for it,
Sandals
like how I stole those sandals.
If this gets stolen, I'm screwed.
After all, I put 63 bonus
points into this thing.
Reset Character.
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
Weapon
●●●●●●
Accessories
○○○○○○
That should do it.
And now...
To acquire a suitable weapon
to replace Durandal.
Identify
Scimitar
No Skill
Identify
Scimitar
No Skill
Identify
Scimitar
Skill Slot
●Empty
Identify
Scimitar
Skill Slot
●Empty
Empty, huh? Does that mean I
can add skills to it later?
Sir, is there something you're interested in?
Are all these scimitars the same price?
Yes.
Sounds like he doesn't know
about the empty skill slots.
Then, I'll buy this one.
Identify
Scimitar
Skill Slot
●Empty
Thank you.
I'm looking for some
protective equipment, too.
In that case, how about these?
Vale
Western Woods
I think he said the entrance was around here.
Adventurer
Explorer
Mage
If there are Mages,
Adventurer
Explorer
Knight
Warrior
Mage
then he must be using teleportation magic.
That's the entrance to the labyrinth?
I should head inside, too.
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
30% Sell Price Increase
Bonus Weapons
I'll remove my discount
skill and re-equip Durandal.
And then...
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
30% Sell Price Increase
Bonus Weapons
Incantation Reduction
Critical Strike Rate
Okay. That should do it.
Whoa. It doesn't even feel
like I'm touching anything.
Come on, buck up.
Whoops.
So this is a labyrinth.
Vale Labyrinth
First Floor
Visibility's not very good, but it
doesn't seem like I'll need a light.
And it's surprisingly tidy.
But a labyrinth is a labyrinth.
I need to be prepared for monsters.
Job Settings.
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Equipped Jobs
Jobs
Villager: Lv 2
Thief: Lv 2
Hero: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Huh? I've got more jobs.
Explorer?
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Explorer: Lv 1
Effects: Minor Endurance Increase
Skills: Item Box Operation
Party Organization
Dungeon Walk
Come to think of it,
Status
Kaga Michio
<Male 17 Years Old>
Villager: Lv 1
Thief: Lv 1
Equipment: Sandals
didn't I gain the Thief job
after stealing those sandals?
Villager: Lv 1
Thief: Lv 1
Equipment: Sandals
Which means I acquired the Explorer
job by entering the labyrinth.
Explorer: Lv 1
Effects: Minor Endurance Increase
Skills: Item Box Operation
Party Organization
Dungeon Walk
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Equipped Jobs
Jobs
Villager: Lv 2
Thief: Lv 2
Hero: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
What's this?
Hero: Lv 1
Effects: Moderate HP Increase Moderate MP Increase
Moderate Strength Increase Moderate Endurance Increase
Moderate Intelligence Increase Moderate Spirit Increase
Moderate Dexterity Increase Moderate Agility Increase
Skills: Overwhelming
Hero? When did I get this?
It seems pretty useful.
I'll select this as my second job
Equipped Jobs
Jobs
Villager: Lv 2
Thief: Lv 2
Hero: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
and Explorer as my third.
Explorer: Lv 1
Effects: Minor Endurance Increase
Skills: Item Box Operation
Party Organization
Dungeon Walk
One of the Explorer's skills is Item Box...
Item Box
So this is the effect of the
Incantation Reduction skill.
Item Box
I don't know how it works,
but it seems convenient.
What else?
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Explorer: Lv 1
Effects: Minor Endurance Increase
Skills: Item Box Operation
Party Organization
Dungeon Walk
Dungeon Walk?
Destination
Destination?
That room I was in earlier, then.
Huh... This is convenient, too.
Dungeon Walk.
I'll head back outside next.
It's not called Dungeon Walk for nothing.
I can only choose destinations
inside labyrinths.
Which means that was some
other kind of spell.
Adventurer
Explorer
Mage
Then, I'll head back to that hall—
Destinations are limited
even within labyrinths, too?
There's so much I don't know.
This sucks.
Identify.
Needle Wood: Lv 1
Is that an enemy?
Time to see how far I can go.
One hit, huh?
This must be because of Durandal.
Branch
The needle wood dropped an item, huh?
I'm not sure what it is, but I'll take it.
Needle Wood: Lv 1
Hey, there's another one.
Come to think of it, the
Hero job had a skill, too.
I think it was...
Overwhelming.
The needle wood's movements slowed down?
No, am I moving faster?
Not that it matters either way.
Once I swing my sword up
through it, it'll be over.
But what good would that do?
Why am I even doing this?
I'd rather wrap myself up in a futon and...
Dazed
What was that?
I suddenly lost the will to do anything.
Wait a minute. I felt the same thing
after I used Dungeon Walk earlier.
This sucks.
I know! It's my MP!
Expending MP by casting spells dampens
my mood and makes me pessimistic.
I returned to normal immediately afterwards
because of Durandal's MP Absorption.
I may be able to recover my MP,
but repeatedly falling into a
depression isn't a fun time.
I shouldn't use too many
spells until I have more MP.
Is this where I sell items?
Yes.
In that case...
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
30% Sell Price Increase
Bonus Weapons
Incantation Reduction
Critical Strike Rate
I'd like to sell these, please.
One moment, please.
Your total is 273 nars.
I see.
Vale
Vale Restaurant
Two hundred seventy-three nars
for 21 branches.
Without the 30% increase,
that would've been ten nars per branch.
Supposing I kill ten in
an hour, that's 100 nars.
In ten hours, I'd earn 1,000 nars.
That's nowhere near close
enough to buy Roxanne.
I'll try staying in the
labyrinth longer tomorrow.
I guess I got up too early.
I can't even see where I'm standing.
Maybe I'll head back and get a lantern.
No, wait.
Come to think of it, in
my Bonus Incantations...
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
Teleport
This is it.
Teleport.
Vale Labyrinth
First Floor
All right, it worked.
Crap, it worked. Why did I
come to this dangerous place?
I didn't even want to come here.
Crap.
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
30% Sell Price Increase
Bonus Weapons
Incantation Reduction
Critical Strike Rate
I'm thinking negatively again.
I need to defeat an enemy
quickly so I can recover my MP.
I can't keep going.
I'd forgotten I don't have infinite health.
Anyway, it would take 700 hours to earn
70,000 nars at a rate of 100 nars per hour.
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Equipped Jobs
Jobs
Villager: Lv 5
Explorer: Lv 3
Thief: Lv 3
Hero: Lv 2
1st Villager: Lv 5
2nd Explorer: Lv 3
3rd Hero: Lv 2
At least I've gained levels
thanks to my efforts.
Maybe I should go to a deeper
level of the dungeon after all.
A secret room?
What's that?
Could it be a treasure?
A broken sword?
No.
This isn't a secret treasure room.
It's a monster den.
Crap.
If I keep taking blows like that, I'll die.
I should leave for now.
Dungeon Walk.
I had a feeling it wouldn't
work during encounters.
If I can't run, I'll have to fight.
All right.
I can make up for the health loss
with Durandal's HP Absorption.
Overwhelming.
Crap, I'm low on MP.
I can't let them get behind me.
Overwhelming presumably consumes
a large amount of MP.
It'll take more than a couple
of monsters to recover it.
That said, if I'm too stingy with
my MP, then I'll slowly bleed out.
Overwhelming.
All right. I'm in the corner.
I can't get attacked from behind here.
This may be another world,
but it's still my reality.
Being defeated here would
certainly mean my death.
But I'll fight, even if it could kill me.
I thought I was gonna die.
No,
without Durandal's HP Absorption,
I definitely would've bit it.
That's enough for today.
What's that?
Vale
West Castle Gate
Did something happen?
Yeah, it's a bandit corpse.
Probably one of the bandits who
used to hang out in this town.
Used to?
You mean you don't know?
Recently a group of bandits left this town.
Nobody knows if they
moved their headquarters
because the knights started
cracking down on them
or they lost a dispute
with a rival organization.
The bandits who left were robbing
travelers and attacking nearby villages.
Oh, I know all about that.
Looks like they're back for revenge.
Revenge?
Hey, wait.
If they're the survivors of the bandit
gang that attacked that village,
then shouldn't they be getting revenge on me?
No, it's hard to imagine that's the case.
They'd be seeking revenge on whoever
made them leave town in the first place.
In other words, the knights
or their rival organization.
Either way, he's one unlucky bastard.
No doubt.
How do you know that's a dead bandit?
Take a look.
His left hand's been cut off.
His Intelligence Card didn't
appear right away when he died,
so they took his whole hand instead.
Ugh. Who's so desperate for a bounty
that they'd chop off a corpse's arm?
The bounty...
Bounties, huh?
Something the matter?
Nothing.
That's right.
Even if I keep going back into that labyrinth,
it's unlikely I'll make much money.
If I'm going to risk my life,
I should choose whatever method
gets me closer to Roxanne.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
I have no other options.
I'll have to hunt bandits.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem