There aren't any monsters, but there's
something about this room that feels off.
It's a waiting room.
A waiting room?
The first floor boss is beyond this door.
So the path to the second floor will open
if we defeat the boss on the
other side of this door?
Yes.
Additionally, only one party can
enter the boss room at a time.
What happens if two or more parties enter?
The boss doesn't appear,
and the door to the next
floor can't be opened.
When there's more than one party,
they must wait their turn in this room.
I see. That's why they call
this the waiting room.
Are you ready?
She's always so eager to fight, but...
Since it's called a boss,
it must be strong, right?
We'll be fine.
A lowly first floor boss doesn't
stand a chance against you, Master.
Don't you think you're a little too excited?
Huh?
Looks like no one got here before us.
So it opens automatically.
Shall we go?
Yeah.
If we're lucky, we might get some equipment.
Equipment?
Sometimes there's equipment left behind
if the previous party was wiped out.
What? Should you be calling that lucky?
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
It looks like an ordinary small room.
It's coming.
So this is the first floor boss.
Ood Wood: Lv 1
Here I go.
It's not flinching under our attacks.
How should we attack this thing?
Nice assist.
How was that?
It may only be the first floor,
but it's still a boss.
It didn't go down in a single blow.
Ood Wood: Lv 1
In that case...
How about this?
Rush!
It's still standing?
Ood Wood: Lv 1
One more time.
Rush!
Master, you're not hurt, are you?
Nah. How about you?
I'm fine.
Those attacks can be dodged easily
if you're watching closely.
Isn't that actually pretty impressive?
Humans can't move like that.
Is it a skill unique to beast warriors?
Oh, it's a leaf.
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Equipped Jobs
1st Beast Warrior: Lv 6
Effects: Moderate Agility Increase
Minor Stamina Increase
Minor Dexterity Increase
Skill: Beast Attack
Jobs
Warrior: Lv 1
Monk: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Farmer: Lv 1
Herbalist: Lv 1
Beast Attack?
It doesn't seem related
to how quickly she moves.
Wait, what? She has a new job.
Herbalist?
That's right. Herbalists use
these to make medicines.
Huh...
Leaf
So it's like a medicinal herb, then.
More importantly...
Roxanne, what kind of skill is Beast Attack?
It's a skill beast warriors have.
I've heard it's a technique that does
a large amount of damage to monsters.
I'm sorry, though. I can't use it.
What? You can't?
Party Job Settings
Item Box
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Warrior: Lv 6
Effects: Moderate Agility Increase
Minor Stamina Increase
Minor Dexterity Increase
Skill: Beast Attack
Using skills requires you to say
the appropriate incantation.
You don't know the incantation?
No, I can imagine the incantation itself.
But unless you get the pronunciation,
accent, and minor nuances all perfect,
the incantation doesn't work.
Is that right?
In my case, all my incantations are
either shortened or abbreviated.
You're always vulnerable
while speaking incantations,
so it's considered better for a beginner
like me not to rely on my skills.
I see.
Roxanne doesn't seem like a beginner to me.
So the second floor is beyond this portal.
That's right.
Vale Labyrinth, Second Floor
Huh. It doesn't look any
different from the first floor.
Roxanne, can we head back to the first
floor and fight that boss again?
Of course.
Roxanne acquired the herbalist job
by picking up that leaf earlier.
Jobs
Warrior: Lv 1
Monk: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Farmer: Lv 1
Herbalist: Lv 1
Which means if I pick a leaf, too...
Huh?
What?
I'm outside.
So you can't return to the
boss room from the next floor.
Of course. There was even a waiting room.
Um...
Crap. She'll lose respect
for me as her master.
I see.
What?
So it can't be done that way.
My experiment yielded intriguing results.
Oh, that was an experiment.
All right. She bought it.
Vale Labyrinth, First Floor
Boss Waiting Room
Let's go.
Yes, Master.
I feel more relaxed the second time around.
That said, I won't let my guard down.
Safety first.
Crap. Is that a spell?
What?
Now!
We managed to beat it somehow.
Yes, Master. Um...
What is it?
The magic circle seemed to
disappear as it was being cast.
Oh, that's...
because of this sword.
Durandal
Offensive Power x5
HP Absorption
MP Absorption
Incantation Interruption
What an impressive sword you have, Master.
Equipped Jobs
1st Explorer: Lv 13
2nd Hero: Lv 7
3rd Monk: Lv 3
4th Swordsman: Lv 8
Jobs
Swordsman: Lv 10
Villager: Lv 5
Monk: Lv 3
Thief: Lv 3
Herbalist: Lv 1
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
There it is.
Herbalist: Lv 1
Skill: Create Herbal Medicine
She said herbalists could make medicines.
Create Herbal Medicine.
I did it.
What? Master, that's amazing.
Don't tell anyone.
Antidote Pill
Antidote?
Do some monsters use poison attacks?
Yes. I've heard quite a few of them do.
I wish someone had told me that sooner.
Thank you for waiting.
Strengthening Pill
Nourishment Pill
Petrification Cure
Paralysis Cure
That's 640 nars for all of them.
Yes, sir.
Anyway, I never get a discount here.
Character Settings
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantation
Bonus Skills
30% Sale Price Increase
Bonus Weapon
Incantation Reduction
Critical Hit Chance
The slave merchant and innkeeper
both offered me a 30% discount.
Come to think of it, the merchant job
had a skill that helps with math.
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Merchant: Lv 1
Skill: Calc
That's right, it's called Calc.
Skills related to haggling might
rely directly on the Calc skill.
Calc
30% Discount
That must be how I performed complex
calculations in an instant.
That explains why my 30%
discount doesn't work here.
It looks like it's all here.
Thank you for your business.
I got some medicine.
There's still plenty of daylight left.
Shall we head back into the labyrinth?
Yes, Master.
Vale Labyrinth, Second Floor
This way. They're very close.
Needle Wood: Lv 2
Lv 2? It must be because
we're on the second floor.
Huh? There's something behind it.
Identify.
Green Caterpillar: Lv 2
Gross! This must be a monster that
starts appearing on the second floor.
I'll handle the needle wood.
Then I'll draw the green caterpillar to me.
Let's see how strong Lv 2 monsters are.
A one-shot?
Well, I guess I've leveled up, too.
As usual, they're not even
close to hitting her.
Unlike the needle woods,
it's easy to differentiate between the
front and back of these creatures.
I can safely attack from behind.
Another one-shot.
Thread
Did two monsters appear just now
because we're on the second floor?
That's right.
Does that mean three will
show up on the third floor?
No.
Monsters start appearing in groups of
three starting on the fourth floor
and in groups of four starting
on the eighth floor.
Then it's probably five on the 16th
floor and six on the 32nd floor.
There they are.
This time it's two caterpillars.
They haven't noticed us yet. In that case...
He who strikes first, wins.
Yes, Master.
I'll attract the attention
of the one in front.
All you.
Master, something's coming.
Huh?
It's aiming for me?
Master!
Crap! Roxanne won't make it in time.
Then I'll take the blow.
Thanks for coming all the way over to me.
Now let me return the favor!
I'm sorry.
It circled around into a position that
allowed it to attack both of us at once.
Don't worry about it.
More importantly, those threads are a pain.
Let's prioritize taking out those
green caterpillars first from now on.
You're right.
Vale, Vale Plaza
The question is what we'll do if we
encounter a large number of those enemies.
Since we can't use multi-target spells,
we either have to take them out one at a
time or devise another way to handle them.
If that labyrinth is too dangerous for us,
then we could always travel
to a different, safer one.
But I shouldn't take the easy way out
and get in the habit of running away.
Roxanne.
Master?
Don't stare.
What? Yes, Master.
You see the man standing behind
that building up ahead?
Yes.
What's he looking at?
Um...
The trading house I came from.
What is he doing?
He doesn't look like a customer.
He's not a customer,
and he's not here to make a deal.
Identify.
Bandit: Lv 3
Listen to me, Roxanne. That guy...
is a bandit.
Vale
Alan's Mansion
Someone's watching this trading house?
Yeah. He was a shady-looking guy,
so I thought I'd let you know.
I appreciate you taking the time to do that.
Sometimes my business earns
me the ire of others,
so it's not unusual, but I'll be careful.
He's not taking my warning very seriously.
U-Um, the person keeping watch
out front is a bandit.
A bandit, you say?
That's right.
How do you know that?
Of course he wants to know.
Normally you can't identify someone
as a bandit just by looking at them.
I may have learned a thing or two while
trying to raise the money to buy Roxanne.
I see. It's not as though I
have no idea who he might be.
This issue is actually related to you, sir.
It's about the young man you sold to me.
The one who committed theft in his village.
Him, huh?
What about him?
He was sold yesterday.
Oh?
He was purchased by a man
accompanied by two others.
He said he needed time to prepare
and would be back tomorrow.
Is that unusual?
It's not as though it never happens,
but now that I think about it,
it did seem a little strange.
The customer had two others with him.
While one of them was asking me questions,
the other was saying something to that man.
Ordinary people have no interest in
the Thief's Bandanna that man stole.
You're saying he had connections
to bandits beforehand?
It's a natural assumption to make.
What's he doing now?
He's in a room in the back.
Can he come and go freely?
Since he's already been paid
for, I no longer own him.
At the buyer's request,
he's in a room without a lock.
Then could he slip out after
everyone's gone to sleep,
open the front door, and let the bandits in?
It's both possible and likely.
How can you be so calm
when you know all that?
Even in the middle of the night,
it's hard to imagine all those bandits
raiding a trading house in the middle of town,
and I have my combat slaves, as well.
I don't intend to be beaten
by a bunch of bandits.
I see.
Let's go, Roxanne.
We warned him. It's their problem now.
Though I was sold here as a slave,
I did receive a lot of care, as well.
There was one old woman, in particular,
who was very kind to me.
You're worried about her?
Yes.
Well, Mr. Alan?
Why not hire me as a bodyguard?
Hire you?
That's right.
It'd leave a bad taste in my mouth if
the slave I sold you did you dirty.
And besides,
there's something I want to test.
Master.
Thank you.
It's okay.
In that case, I'd like to hire you.
Regarding your pay...
How does 1,000 nars sound?
Naturally, any equipment or intelligence cards
dropped by the bandits you defeat are yours.
We have a deal.
You won't be spotted by the
lookout out front from here.
Then I'll use this door to enter tonight.
I'll be waiting for you.
Um...
I'm sorry for being selfish.
I'm the one who suggested
he hire me as a bodyguard.
But I told him the lookout was a bandit.
Oh, that.
I was able to smooth things over,
and I didn't tell her
beforehand not to tell him.
Well, you know.
It's fine. Just be careful in the future.
Your concerns are my concerns, too.
Yes, Master.
Thank you.
Vale, Vale Restaurant
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Master.
Master, good morning.
It's nearly time.
Good morning, Roxanne.
I'll be back.
What are you doing?
I'm going with you.
What?
I'm going, too.
Fine, but stay in the
back as much as possible.
Yes, Master.
Vale
Alan's Mansion, Rear Entrance
I've been waiting for you.
Don't be alarmed.
These are my combat slaves.
I see.
Mr. Michio, please wait with
us here until they act.
Got it.
Now, then...
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem