Ugh, din nimeni nu sare atât de mult sânge...
Da, jocul ăsta e varză.
Harem într-un labirint dintr-o alta lume
Ce?
Unde mă aflu?
Parcă încercam să mă joc un joc online foarte ciudat.
Lumea antică
Lumea avansată tehnologic
Lumea săbiilor și magiei
Lumea piraților
Dar nu-mi amintesc nimic după aceea.
Uaa! Asta m-a luat prin surprindere!
Cal
„Un cal?”
Da, acela e un cal.
Identificare
Asta e cumva?
Bun, „identificare”.
Kaga Michio
Status
Știam eu. Asta înseamnă că sunt în joc
Kaga Michio
<Sex: M, 17 ani>
Sătean: Nivel 1
Asta e incredibil.
Parcă ar fi corpul meu real.
Even my track suit's been recreated.
I wish the game had given me some kind of
footwear instead of perfectly recreating me.
What are those?
Sandale
This works much better in games
where you can swap out equipment
with a single click
and not so well in VR.
Status
Kaga Michio
<Sex: M, 17 ani>
Sătean: Nivel 1
Hoț: Nivel 1
Echipament: Sandale
În regulă.
Sătean: Nivel 1
Hoț: Nivel 1
Echipament: Sandale
Yeah, sorry for stealing someone's stuff.
Come to think of it,
didn't I select bonus equipment?
Post
Unde e?
Gard
Mite
Furnică
Iarbă
Cal
Post
Ring of Determination
Fence
Straw
Ant
Durandal
Straw
Ah, how convenient.
This must be it.
Identificare
Durandal
Durandal, nu? Nu e rea deloc.
Offensive Power x5
HP Absorption
MP Absorption
Incantation Interruption
And this must be the accessory I selected.
Identificare
Inelul Determinării
Increases Offensive Power
Personal Strengthening
Nici abilitățile sale nu sunt rele.
E un nume potrivit pentru începutul unui joc.
Nu am idee cum au făcut acest VR realist,
dar mă aflu în interiorul jocului.
Iar acum că știu asta...
It's time to venture forth into savage lands!
Se pare că încep într-un loc destul de pașnic.
Oh!
Fir-ar!
Un sătean și un fermier, nu?
Identificare
Sătean fără nume
<Sex: M, 47 de ani>
Fermier: Nivel 15
Identificare
Sătean fără nume
<Sex: M, 17 ani>
Sătean: Nivel 5
I wonder how they're different.
Ce se petrece?
Se apropie!
Identificare.
Bandit
Jocul începe cu un atac al bandiților?
Plănuiesc cumva să li se opună?
They're roughly the same level,
but will they be okay?
Identificare
Hugo
<Male 38 Years Old>
Thief: Lv 41
Equipment: Iron Sword
Thief's Bandanna
Iron Armor
Leather Boots
One of them is higher level.
El trebuie să fie liderul.
<Male 38 Years Old>
Thief: Lv 41
Equipment: Iron Sword
Thief's Bandanna
Iron Armor
Leather Boots
"Thief's Bandanna?"
He's got some fancy equipment.
I knew it. They're totally outmatched.
Ce?
This could be my opportunity to sneak up
on him unnoticed and stab him from behind.
It's all right. This is the
first event of the game.
Even a level 1 character like
me should be able to beat him.
I've gotta try!
Din nimeni nu sare atât de mult sânge...
Da, jocul ăsta chiar e varză.
His armor prevents me from striking his body.
În acest caz, voi face asta și apoi asta!
Pfiu, mă bucur că iau lecții de kendo.
They race to get away as soon as
the situation turns against them.
They're just bandits, after all.
No need for me to hold back.
They'll all become experience points for me.
Man, I'm exhausted.
Identify.
Kaga Michio
Status
Villager: Lv 2
Thief: Lv 2
Hero: Lv 2
Hey, my level went up.
But I only gained one for
defeating all those bandits?
Thank you for saving our village.
I am Somara, the village chief.
Please visit me at my home.
I'd like to thank you in whatever way I can.
Really? In that case, don't mind if I do.
What're these?
The spoils of battle.
You must be exhausted, but I'd like
you to look through them, as well.
Me?
Yes. The villagers defeated
two of the bandits,
so we'll be taking our share.
But the rest belongs to you, Mr. Michio.
I see, so that's how it works. That said...
Identify.
Identificare
Bandană
Abilitate: Niciuna
There's no point in carrying
around all of these.
Huh?
What is it?
This isn't it.
<Male 38 Years Old>
Thief: Lv 41
Equipment: Iron Sword
Thief's Bandanna
Iron Armor
Leather Boots
That man was wearing a Thief's Bandanna,
not an ordinary bandanna.
What? B-But...
I'll look into it right away.
I'll prepare a room for you.
You can rest there.
All right, I will.
That's enough for today.
Huh?
How do I log out?
"Log out."
"Log off. Quit game.
Terminate session. End."
"Save."
"Menu. Open menu. Open window."
"Close window. Shutdown options."
Salvează ca
"Save as. Save and Quit."
Salvează și închide
Închide fără să salvezi
"Quit without saving. Close."
Închide
End the game!
Închide jocul
Let it end!
Nu te mai poți întoarce în realitate
Hold on. Am I really inside the game?
It's so real. Maybe this is reality.
No, that's not possible.
Identify.
Status
Kaga Michio
Villager: Lv 2
Thief: Lv 2
Hero: Lv 2
See? This isn't possible in reality.
This must be a game.
Technologically
Advanced World
World of
Swords and Sorcery
Pirate World
Ancient World
Da
Nu
Final Warning!
You will not be able to return
once you begin playing.
Are you sure you want to continue?
You mean that was real?
We've brought you some hot water.
You can wipe down your body with this.
We've also brought you a change of clothes.
What?
The clothes you're currently
wearing are dirty.
We'll wash them for you.
Even if I'm inside the game,
if I can't log out,
then it's practically reality.
And if this is reality,
Blood
You will not be able to return once you begin playing.
then I didn't just defeat game characters.
I killed people.
Mr. Michio, is something the matter?
No, it's nothing.
I see.
In that case, please let me know
once you've finished changing.
I took people's lives.
That's definitely true.
But it's a matter of perspective.
In this world, it's normal for
bandits to attack villages.
It's likely the same thing will happen again.
And when it does, if I lose my nerve, I won't
even be able to watch what's happening.
I'm glad I got to experience this early on.
That's how I feel.
That's right. This is the real world.
And I have to live in it.
I am sorry, Mr. Michio.
This man swapped out the bandannas.
Is he from this village?
Embarrassingly, yes.
This is the article he was hiding.
Thief's Bandanna
This is definitely it.
How shall we punish this man?
I'm sure your village has its own rules.
I don't intend to dispute them.
I-Is that so?
Huh? Why's he making that face?
Will of the swiftly flowing spirits,
steady breath of wisdom.
Open Intelligence Card.
Something appeared.
What are you doing?
I've written on this man's
Intelligence Card that he is a slave.
I see.
That card displays a person's social status.
Did you say slave?
Yes. In this village, those who
steal are sold off as slaves.
Half the profit from the sale
is given to their victim.
What about the remaining half?
It's given to their family,
who has lost a worker.
I see.
He was hoping I'd go easy on
him so this wouldn't happen.
Then he should've said so!
It's a tough world.
They've got slaves here, huh?
Ah, I nearly forgot.
These are the bandits' Intelligence Cards.
Oh.
If any of them had a price on their heads,
those are yours, as well.
In other words, bounties, huh?
There is a knight's station
in the town of Vale.
You can redeem your bounties there.
Vale?
It's the biggest town around here.
Market day is tomorrow.
It'd be the perfect place
to sell your spoils.
I see. I could sell all this stuff.
If necessary, I'll prepare
a carriage for you.
Will you be departing tomorrow morning?
Yes, please.
The Next Morning
On the Road to Vale
They ended up providing me
with everything I needed.
They not only fed me,
but paid me a reward, too.
I feel sorry for the village
chief and that man,
but this was pretty good for my first job.
It's coming into view now.
That is the town of Vale.
What a lively place.
Market day is held only once every five days.
People gather from nearby villages.
Vale
Knight's Station
The men you defeated belong to a bandit
gang that hangs around this town.
There were bounties on two of them.
You'll be paid accordingly, but first...
Huh?
Mr. Michio, they'd like to
see your Intelligence Card.
Oh, right.
Won't they find me extremely
suspicious if it doesn't appear now?
Will of the swiftly flowing spirits,
steady breath of wisdom.
Open Intelligence Card.
I'm safe.
All good.
Take this.
Now get out of here.
No "thank you?"
That's just how knights are.
I feel like the town's
atmosphere has changed.
Mr. Michio, try not to look around too much.
There are some unsafe areas around here.
There are brothels, as well,
but I wouldn't recommend going inside them.
Brothels?
Brothels
Brothels? As in a building for prostitutes?
In other words, a whorehouse?
A place for making love to sexy ladies?
For squishing and squeezing,
dazzling and satiating!
Mr. Michio. Mr. Michio!
Huh? What?
We're here.
This is the slave trader's mansion.
Vale
Alan's Mansion
Thank you for waiting.
I am Alan, master of the house.
Identify
Alan
<Male 51 Years Old>
Slave Trader
Forgive me. I have many guests today.
Did something happen?
You haven't heard?
Two days ago, a labyrinth was
discovered near the town.
They even have labyrinths here, huh?
So, I was told you had a slave to sell.
I understand the situation.
Anyway, I'm impressed you defeated
most of the bandits yourself.
You're giving me too much credit.
They were just weak.
Oh?
Anyway, about the price...
He's healthy and in his prime.
I believe the market price is 30,000 nars.
This is the village's share.
Looks good. Take care, Mr. Michio.
You, too. Thanks for everything.
Now there's nobody who knows who I am.
I don't know the language they speak.
I don't know what's common knowledge here.
I'm in a different world,
and I'm still an outsider.
Will I be able to make it all on my own?
Mr. Michio.
Come to think of it, there is one person.
What is it?
If you're not in a hurry,
may I have some more of your time?
That's fine.
We're in a different room this time.
The rug and furniture look expensive.
There are even paintings on the walls.
What's he up to?
Forgive me, but you're an
adventurer, aren't you?
Yeah, something like that.
In that case, why not purchase some slaves?
What? Slaves?
Do adventurers buy slaves?
Many do.
Buy a slave?
I did just sell one.
It makes sense that I'd be able to buy one.
The thought hadn't even occurred to me.
My trading company also sells female slaves.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
He sells female slaves?
Can I really buy a female slave?
Does that mean
I can get freaky with a female slave?
No, I can't. Calm down.
I should take a moment to cool my head.
Excuse me.
Huh?
They jiggled! They just jiggled!
Does she really move?
Here you are.
Identify
Roxanne
<Female 16 Years Old>
Beast Warrior Lv 6
Uh, thanks.
Have some tea.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
They jiggled again.
Those fleshy masses jiggled again.
She's definitely the most beautiful woman
I've met today—no, in this whole world.
And...
She had the biggest titties, too.
You seem pleased.
The tea's not bad.
I was talking about her, of course.
I knew it!
She's currently my most
highly-recommended slave.
So she is a slave.
Which means I could buy her.
Do slaves ever betray their masters?
No. Without someone to inherit them,
or a will promising them their freedom,
a slave that loses their master
follows them to the grave.
You mean they die?
Yes.
If they can't kill their master,
then what about running away?
Runaway slaves are demoted to bandits.
Bandits can't complain about being killed,
and their possessions can be stolen legally.
Even if they stole money from
their master before escaping,
it's unlikely they'd live a better life.
I see.
Also, the girl who was here earlier
is a wolfkin and a beast warrior.
She'd be useful in a labyrinth.
On top of that, she's intelligent
and has good character.
She's perfect for someone's first slave.
And there's another advantage
to her being a wolfkin.
What is it?
Humans and non-humans cannot produce offspring.
You mean...
There's one more important thing to consider.
She is a virgin.
Therefore, you needn't worry about diseases.
Additionally...
There's more?
She has consented to sleeping with her master.
I believe that would be meaningful to you.
Why?
Because some of my customers feel
conflicted about laying hands on a slave,
especially the younger ones.
But if she accepts such a relationship...
What do you think?
I see.
Those are the reasons I'd
recommend her to you.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
Can I really buy Roxanne?
To do as I please with
such a beautiful slave?
Can I even buy a slave?
No, that's how this world works.
Even I don't buy her, eventually she'll
become someone else's sex slave.
And I can't allow that, which means...
How much?
600,000 nars is what I'd like to say,
but after recommending her so aggressively,
including the outfit she was just wearing,
she's yours for 422,800 nars.
I can't afford that.
I see. Well, then it can't be helped.
She's so cute.
I can wait five days for you.
Huh?
Gather the funds you need by then.
But...
The customer has taken a liking to you.
Thank you.
Now I can't say no.
Excuse me...
Huh?
Nice to meet you.
Um, sure.
I'll see you in five days.
Yeah.
I don't know how I'll make that much money,
but I know one thing for sure.
Roxanne will be mine.
Harem în labirintul dintr-o altă lume