Băiete...
Tu ești al IV-lea Străbun despre care ne-a spus locotenet Okiyama?
Uua!
Citirea viitorului a
unui Șaman Spadasin?!
La naiba, fie ce-o fi! Trageți!
Yuiri!
Mă ocup!
Sunt puternice...
God, my God, grant me
the power to exact revenge.
Yukki, stai în spate!
Din nou?!
If you wish to restrain me,
you need only follow the proper procedure.
Dar eu sunt comandantul aici.
Attack Mage Hikawa,
if you resist, you will all be restrained.
Hmph. A mere human
thinks he can restrain me?
Ce glumă bună.
Ăsta e ultimul avertisment.
Aruncați armele și predați-vă.
There is no need for that, Hikawa Shio,
because that order is void.
Major Azama, you
are hereby relieved of duty,
along with the rest of the Holy War Faction.
Controlling all these people
at once through spirit threads...
Kuraki Shirona?
Perhaps you thought you were using us,
the Lion King Organization,
but we were doing the same.
One of our goals in this mission was to smoke
the Holy War Faction members out of the JSDF.
Înțeleg.
But regardless of the goal,
using a real dragon as a decoy
was a blunder on your part.
Incoming! Everyone, get down!
Lieutenant First Class Okiyama?!
Don't tell me you were also...
Two wyverns, eh?
This is going to be quite fun indeed.
Iblis!
We found out where the dragon is!
Gajou-san, Kojou's there, too!
Is that so? Thanks, Asagi-chan.
We're going after it. Lead the way, Asagi.
Off we go!
Yuiri...
Don't worry. Let's just
trust them to handle the rest.
Akatsuki Gajou...
You did great, Shio-chan.
Schneesturm Wolfin!
Come, Al-Nasl Minium!
Who the hell are these guys?
The Holy War Faction.
Most of these are crude
replicas or mere junk,
but they are a terrorist group that uses
magic tools that were relics of the holy war.
Magic tools?
So that's what was rendering
our magic powers useless.
I will not fall at the hands of a demon!
Kojou-kun!
Major Azama!
Good work keeping them here,
First Lieutenant Ueyanagi.
Yes, sir!
This is as far as you can go
with your imperfect magic tool.
I will put you out of your misery.
No... But...
Stop it!
Silence!
Yuiri!
Take it easy!
S-Senpai!
No! Glenda, you idiot!
Senpai! What are you looking at?!
N-Nothing!
Hold on tight!
Y-Yeah...
But, uh... th-they're
right up against my face...
Whoa, hey! I'm gonna fall! I'm gonna fall!
It's what you get for saying
something so perverted!
Seriously?!
I fell and...
You're awake now, um... Yuiri-san?
Kojou-kun? Where are we?
And where's Glenda?
Um...
This is a cabin built
for mountain climbers, apparently.
More importantly, um...
If you could cover up, that'd be great.
What are you doing to Yuiri-san, Senpai?
I can't take my eyes off you
for a second, can I?
You're the one who took her clothes off!
Can you move, Yuiri-san?
I gave you first aid,
but that was all I could do.
You did? Thanks, Yukki.
Yuiri, Yuiri... Does it hurt?
I'm fine. Thanks, Glenda.
There were some emergency
rations in the kitchen.
I'm heating them up.
Let's all eat.
Yuiri-san, would you like some more?
Yes, thank you.
Sorry to put you through so much trouble.
Not at all.
You've done so much
to help Sayaka-san all these years.
Yeah, Kirasaka-san was
always fighting with Shio-chan.
Oh, so you two have known each other
since you were kids, huh?
That's right.
Although we were in different grades at
school, so we didn't often talk in person.
Actually, you never really talked
to anyone at all, Yukki.
Huh?
You were kind of aloof,
always serious and methodical,
and you had excellent grades.
You were a little scary
during mock battles, honestly.
A-Aloof? Scary?
But I guess that's also why...
when I heard you had
received a Schneewalzer
and had been assigned to
observe the Fourth Progenitor,
it made total sense to me.
I knew it'd be you.
Wow...
So since you're a Sword Shaman, too,
you might have moved in next
to me instead of Himeragi, huh?
Huh?!
Yukki, you live next door to Kojou-kun?!
Yes... It's part of the job.
I... I see...
Senpai, that's bad manners!
I can't help it!
I can barely move my right hand, remember?
Oh, fine... Just give it to me.
Here.
Hey, this is good.
It does look a little weird.
Tastes better than it looks, though.
I think you'd like this flavor, Himeragi.
You're right! It's good!
Right?
Uh...
Here.
Oh, thanks.
What are you, married?!
What the hell?!
Yuiri-san?
Oh... I'm sorry! It's nothing!
I just kind of felt
like shouting a little...
O-Okay...
Yuiri.
You like Kojou?
Huh?! Wha... Where did that...
I was just thinking
that I could be the one
living next to Kojou-kun
and sitting where Yukki is right now.
But that's all, really.
Yukki, Kojou-kun...
They're coming.
Yes, and much sooner than I thought.
Major Azama, was it? You're alone?
I wanted to speak with you,
Akatsuki Kojou... no, Fourth Progenitor.
How do you feel about the state of this world?
What do you mean?
I refer to a world in which
a single vampire like you
can become a threat
that strikes fear in the people.
And you people think that's not right?
Correct.
The holy war fought by the Devas
and the Sinful God Cain
resulted in the laws
of this world becoming warped.
You're free to believe that if you want,
but what good is it going to do now?
Or do you think you can take over as
God and change this world's laws?
Certainly not. No human can become a god.
But we do have the ability
to resurrect a fallen god,
whom we can then bend to our will.
Glenda was left behind by Cain
to protect the relic.
She is a vessel containing the god's data.
We need her in order to fight
the Manmade Island Management Corporation.
Corporația de Management al Insulei
What does this have to do
with Itogami Island?
We only want to eradicate all demon races
and return the world to its intended state.
This should also prove to be good news
for you, Fourth Progenitor.
Huh?
If we can rewrite the laws of the world,
you will be freed
from the curse of immortality
and gain the ability to die
as Akatsuki Kojou, the human.
Appealing, is it not?
As it is now, you face
a future of eternal solitude.
Senpai...
What?!
It's...
a cargo plane?
It's the JSDF Special Attack
Mage Regiment's trump card,
the AC-2 gunship.
It currently belongs to us, however.
You mean... you used that to make a golem?!
This discussion is over.
Leave Glenda and vacate this area.
What you said did appeal to me a little bit.
But all I see is a man who killed
his comrades without a second thought
and injured a lot of other people.
I'll never give Glenda
to a bastard like that!
That's unfortunate, Fourth Progenitor.
In that case, die here as a lowly demon!
Come, first Familiar,
Mesarthim Adamas!
Rosen Chevalier Plus, boot up!
Yuiri-san!
I'm sorry, but I don't think
hiding will save us from that.
Yeah!
Leave this to me!
Schneesturm Wolfin!
Yuiri-san!
A Schneewalzer
of the Lion King Organization...
It can even sever the encroachment of Nod?
A troublesome weapon, indeed.
Nod?
The realm into which
the Sinful God Cain was banished.
It is an empty world, void of all magic,
whose god lost his omnipotence in the holy war.
Now I get it.
That's why our magic
attacks haven't been working.
Correct.
This armor is a magic tool that allows
me to control Nod's encroachment.
As such, it will also allow me
to purge you and any other demons!
Senpai!
Kojou-kun!
It's no use!
Himeragi, Yuiri-san...
Take Glenda and get out of—
No...
G-Glenda?!
The vessel leaped
into Nod of her own accord?!
Impossible!
Where am I?
This is...
Schneesturm Wolfin's divine vibrations?
Paper Noise was most
likely trying to seal you,
using divine vibrations.
She knew this would happen...
and tried to protect me?
Hey!
Kojou!
G-Glenda?
I take you back.
Make Yuiri happy.
How can we get out of here?
Do you know, Glenda?
Yes. I know.
I am a vessel of information.
Must take... to the priestess.
Priestess?
I take you back.
Make everyone happy.
Kanase? Why...
Yuuma?
La Folia?
Kirasaka?
Glenda, are you...
going back through my memories?
Himeragi...
Please take my blood.
Wait... you're...
By sucking blood, you gain
the memories of that blood.
The information within me
will give you power...
The power to fight the emptiness of Nod.
Senpai...
Himeragi...
It's all right.
Don't be afraid to touch the information.
Feel me.
Of course! You're...
Ko...jou...
I will attempt to retrieve Glenda.
Do it, Lieutenant First Class Okiyama.
Senpai...
It's working!
Give 'em one more!
Reinforcing the guns truly paid off!
You think your ugly fireworks
are going to be of any help
against the encroachment of Nod?
Iblisveil Aziz!
Impossible! How could any demon
break out of Nod's barrier unassisted?!
What are you so surprised about?
There has already been one
who successfully returned from Nod.
Just one, a very long time ago.
You don't mean...
he consumed Cain's memories?!
That can't be—
Senpai!
Glenda!
Fourth Progenitor.. Akatsuki Kojou!
Fourth Progenitor?!
Why?! Why did the
Sinful God's vessel choose you?!
You, a traitor whose very soul has fallen
to the level of a demon?!
Shut the hell up, old man.
Maybe you're right,
and this world really is twisted.
But if determining that to be fact
makes you so righteous and just,
then why'd you become a terrorist?
It's not the world that's warped.
It's you!
But if you still want to go after Glenda
in the name of what you call justice,
I will stop you!
From now on, this is my fight!
Akatsuki Kojou!
No, Senpai.
This is our fight!
Shit!
He's letting his magic tool
be consumed by another one!
I won't allow it!
Fourth Progenitor!
You know, I pity you.
You don't hesitate to sacrifice others,
and even abandon your own comrades,
to achieve your goals.
Were you actually counting
yourself among those sacrifices?
You're way too twisted.
I'm not gonna let you die.
I'm gonna make you think long
and hard about where you went wrong!
Come, second Familiar,
Cor Tauri Sucinum!
Pulsation!
Himeragi!
I, Sword Shaman of the High God, as a priestess of the Lion, beseech thee...
Dawn light of exorcism, spirit wolf of snowy mist...
Grant me the divine might of thy steel,
that I may smite a hundred evil spirits!
It's over, old man!
Kojou!
Well, anyway, I guess it's over now.
Yes, Senpai.
Nope, not yet.
Glad to see you're okay, Kojou.
So... what's all this
"Fourth Progenitor" business?
Asagi?!
Wh-What a coincidence!
It's over?!
What are you saying?!
I was just released from my suspension
and finally got a break to come here!
I finally got here!
Hey... Teacher?!
No fair running away...
Yo. Might wanna give
the psycho behavior a rest.
You're...
Akatsuki Kojou's friend, um...
Yaze Motoki.
I followed that disaster-prone
childhood friend of mine here, too,
but it looks like we were both too late.
I... I didn't exactly...
Seriously, just listen, Kojou-kun!
They keep telling Grandma she should
be admitted to the hospital for tests,
but she won't listen!
And Gajou-kun's no better.
The moment he heard they were taking him
to Imori-chan's hospital, he tried to bolt.
Don't you think they should be more willing
to listen to their kids and grandkids?!
Well, at any rate, I see you're okay now.
Yeah! I'll be able to go home with you.
Cool.
Glad she's doing so well.
Yeah.
So, Kojou...
When we get back to the island,
you're going to tell me
everything that's happened here,
and everything you've been hiding
from me! Every last detail!
Oh, uh...
By the way, Asagi... you know...
What?
Why are you wearing a swimsuit?
I-I have my reasons...
And... how long are you gonna
keep ogling me, pervert?!
I'm not ogling! You're the one
walking around in a swimsuit!
Speaking of perverts, Senpai...
That new Familiar came to you
because you sucked
Glenda-san's blood, didn't it?
That wasn't exactly Glenda!
She traced the memories in my
blood and... took your form...
My form?
So you took blood from Glenda-san
while she looked like me?
Well... yeah.
But... wasn't Glenda-san naked at the time?
Senpai, you didn't...
Wait, no! It was still Glenda inside!
But still... you saw, didn't you?
Well...
Yes.
You really are an indecent person, Senpai!
No, hang on! That was beyond
my control... or something...
I mean, it's not like I wanted to look!
Oh, I see! You didn't want to!
Why would you want to see me naked, right?
Well, I mean...
Gimme a break!
Itogami - Magazinul tău pentru tăieței
You were here, as well, Lord Ardeal?
Well, well.
The princess herself makes an appearance.
Do you seek the magic tool
of the Knight of the Sinful God?
You are welcome to take it,
in commemoration of our reunion.
Thank you, Dimitrie Vatler.
A magic tool of Nod...
So it was a replica after all.
It has already ceased to function.
Or might it still prove useful
if one were to analyze it?
Yes, perhaps.
There's one other thing I'm curious about.
The Priestess of Cain?
The Knight of the Sinful God seemed
to show no interest in her.
There are two possible reasons.
One is that they didn't know,
which would make them a rather
sad excuse for a Holy War Faction.
I'm sure we can safely say
that is not the case.
And the other possibility?
Mai există o preoteasă a lui Cain.
Nu se poate...
Nu este minunat? Lucrurile
devin tot mai interesante!
Haosul iubește cu adevărat acea insulă!