We will arrive at Lake Kannawa momentarily.
Please be patient just
a bit longer, Empress.
Got it.
It's bad for your health to hold it
when you need to pee, Empress.
It's not that!
I mean, yeah, I'm kinda cold
in this weird pilot suit,
Asagi
but there's something
making it even more... Huh?
Why is the outside air temperature so low?!
What the heck is going on?
What now?!
Unknown. I believe this signal is...
Magical beasts!
What?!
To strike first assures victory!
Time to launch our attack!
Wait a second, Tank!
Don't shoot that way!
Empress?
Look in front of us!
There's a kid standing there!
Knowing what is right and not doing it is...
Forgive me, Empress!
Wait, what are you—
Boy, we have this area covered!
Retreat now, while you can!
Got 'em!
Good grief.
You leap in front of me in a piece
of junk like that, only to embarrass yourself?
Still, I acknowledge your willingness
to risk your own life to save me,
injudicious though it was.
That power... Are you...
from the Dynasty
of Destruction in the Caucasus...
Oh?
So there's someone out here
in this backwater who knows me?
I am a direct descendant
of the Second Progenitor, Foregazer,
and ruler of the Eight Northern Provinces
of the Dynasty of Destruction...
Iblisveil Aziz.
Be honored.
Hisano-sama!
I'm glad you're all right, Haba Yuiri.
Yuiri! Yuiri! Yuiri!
I'm sorry. I lost sight of Nagisa-san.
Yuiri! Yuiri! Yuiri! Yuiri!
I know.
You did very well.
And... who is this girl?
Yuiri!
Um... I don't know.
I just found her and brought her with me.
She seems quite attached to you.
Well... yes, for some reason...
Haba Yuiri, I would like you
to guard the wounded JSDF members.
Take the girl and retreat to Gotemba.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Listen to me. Do not take
your eyes off of this girl.
I'm counting on you.
Baia femeilor
Baia bărbaților
Asagi is close to here?
Yeah, though she's kind
of lost at the moment...
What?! Is she okay?!
She's with that tank girl,
so I don't think we need to worry.
That "Didier" girl?
But why is Asagi on the mainland, too?
Oh, she probably wants to show you
that she can be helpful, too.
And she thought she'd show me that way?!
Oh, my.
I see you're as popular
with the ladies as ever, Akatsuki Kojou.
K-Kisaki?! Wha— Why—
And why are you in a towel?!
Don't worry.
I'll remove it before I get in the water.
Peek?
That's rather embarrassing to actually do...
Then get out of here already!
I was just pretending! Ta-da!
Ta... Ta-da?! You—
A-A swimsuit?!
Are you disappointed? Are you disappointed?
I'm not disappointed!
Wait, why are you getting in?!
Hey, quit staring!
It looked like you still haven't
regained feeling in your right hand.
The spell to generate
the barrier, Paper Noise,
was most likely intended to seal you
using divine vibrations.
Seal me, huh?
That makes sense.
Isn't there any way to get rid of it?
Who knows?
Would you like to try sucking
my blood, for starters?
I won't tell Himeragi Yukina.
That's such a lie. You have
every intention of telling her.
Oh, what a surprise. However did you know?
Jeez...
If you just wanted to tease me,
haven't you done that enough?
Just get out of here.
No, I haven't come to the real point yet.
I came to say goodbye.
Huh?
I've been summoned by the Taishi Bureau.
They've ordered me to clean up a swarm of
magical beasts that appeared at Lake Kannawa.
Magical beasts... at Lake Kannawa?
It seems the Lion King Organization's
plans ran awry.
Or perhaps this is how
they wanted it to end...
So long as we both live,
I'm sure we'll meet again.
When we do, I hope we can
truly bare all to one another.
Wait, Kisaki! What's going on?
What happened at Lake Kannawa?!
Kisaki-san! What are you
doing in the men's bath?
What happened to that warding barrier...
H-Himeragi?
Senpai, you...
Wait, wait...
You jerk!
Why?!
Gosh, to think you blew away all
those magical beasts in a mere instant.
That Familiar was incredible, was it not?
For real. That was unbelievable.
A little stunt like that was nothing.
More importantly...
Do you eat this directly from the container?
Yeah. What, you've never had it before?
It's good.
Right?
The boiling point is lower
at high altitudes,
so the key is to wait
a little longer for it.
Lydianne, and...
you said your name was Asagi?
You two are quite strange.
Huh? We are?
Is that so?
I haven't encountered many people who didn't
adopt a servile attitude upon meeting me.
We know you don't mean us any harm.
Why would we be scared of you?
Besides, I grew up
on Itogami Island, you know.
I see.
I visited there before coming here.
So you live on that island?
That explains it.
Exactly.
Iblis, since you stopped by
Itogami Island before coming here,
will you stop by again on your way home?
Perhaps. Why do you ask?
If you do, you might want to check out
Toushouken at the International Terminal!
Oh, but Noodle Shop Itogami's rich
pork back fat ramen is great, too...
No, wait... There's also Tsukemen Pacific...
You really are a strange one!
Wait... is that an exasperated reaction?
So... what was that back there?
Dragons exist to protect.
Maybe these ruins were a bullseye.
Bullseye?
Whatever the case,
slaying monsters isn't our domain.
With the JSDF in that state,
we can't count on them, either.
Actually, those guys...
I mean, the Special Attack Mage Regiment...
seemed to go down awfully easily.
Now that you mention it...
Hisano-sama?!
Hey, old hag. Did you kill all these guys?
You really believe that's possible?
I only stumbled upon them a moment ago.
It looked as if they were fighting
to protect something.
Gajou?
Shio-chan, you can use physical
enchantment spells, right?
Take Nagisa and get as far away
from here as you can.
A w-wyvern?!
That must be who wiped out all these beasts.
If so, then his objective must be...
The calamity of Lake Kannawa itself!
What's going on?!
Old hag!
Go now, Shio-chan!
No way...
Run, Shio...
You two... have to...
Sagara!
Iblis-dono, that magic was—
I know.
Hurry!
Who are you?
Kira, Tobias... You can handle that one.
Show him your finest hospitality.
We are a bit ahead of schedule,
but this makes the third.
Vatler-san?! What are you doing here?
So that's Akatsuki Nagisa...
The Fourth Progenitor's younger sister?
Well, well, if it isn't
His Highness Iblisveil Aziz.
And of all things, you've brought
the Priestess of Cain with you.
The Priestess of Cain?
Well, no matter.
More importantly, Vatler, is that...
Yes.
An armed agent of the Holy Massacre Faction.
The Knight of the Sinful God... I see.
So that's why you've come here.
Asagi, take those humans and leave here.
Take Akatsuki Nagisa, as well.
You have no complaint
with that, do you, Vatler?
Of course not.
Kira Voltisloa and the other one are losing?
Interesting.
You dare point a blade at me?
Know your place!
Rip out their entrails, Meretseger!
The power of Nod, eh?
Transforming the air
into deadly, acidic poison...
This Familiar, Meretseger,
belonged to Second Princess Mavia.
Did you think you were the only
one who'd consumed a family member?
I was humiliated during the Blazing Banquet,
but I took revenge by consuming
the traitor in my family.
What's the matter, Knight of the Sinful God?
Are you done already?
What?!
He's running away? No, he's retreating.
Impudent bastard.
Vatler, I will be the one to destroy him.
You have no complaint with that, do you?
The fanatics loyal to the Sinful God, Cain,
who seek to reenact the holy war...
To destroy them along
with the Sinful God has long been
the wish of the descendants
of the Warlord, including myself.
I have orders from our king
to annihilate them at all costs.
Oh? Do you want to fight me for it, then?
Certainly not.
Please do as you wish, Your Highness.
I still have another objective I must fulfill.
Hmph. Cunning bastard.
So what's your name?
Mine's Yuiri. What's yours?
Glenda!
Glenda? That's your name?
Yeah! Glenda!
Glenda...
It's here.
It's here? What is?
Attack Mage Haba, look!
An automata... no...
Is it a golem?
But... what is this creepy feeling?
Rosen Chevalier Plus, boot up!
Run now, while you can!
What's happening?
Is this... alchemy?!
I found you...
Glenda.
Take this!
Yuiri!
Run, Glenda!
Glenda...
Just what are you?
I've been waiting!
Glenda!
Get her.
No... I can't get to her.
Someone, please... save her!
Schneesturm Wolfin!
Regulus Aurum!
Are you all right, Yuiri-san?
Yukki!
So that's the golems' boss?
Fourth Progenitor...
Senpai!
Damn it! Regulus Aurum!
Its attacks aren't working?!
Just like with the Dark Oath Grimoire...
Wait!
Senpai! Wasn't that hand the one...
Yeah, sorta.
Anyway, Himeragi, where are
that girl and the dragon?
D-Don't look!
I am a War Dancer
of the Lion King Organization.
My name is Hikawa Shio,
Your Highness Iblisveil Aziz.
Then... Shio, you said?
Why don't you tell me what's going on?
What is it you people are after?
Why did the Holy War Faction appear here?
I... cannot answer that.
Oh? You refuse to answer my question?
I don't dislike a faithful dog,
but if you will not repay your debt
to the one who saved your life,
you will be disciplined—
The Lion King Organization's
goal is to seal Avalon.
Before we knew it,
the whole lake had frozen,
and then the magical beasts showed up.
Gajou! Should you be moving around?
I'll manage.
So, Prince, try not to pick on this
hard-working young lady too much.
The Netherworld Revenant, Akatsuki Gajou?
You're just as impertinent as I had heard.
Very well, you'll do. Explain.
What is Avalon?
A relic of the holy war...
Ostensibly, at least.
It's a god-killing weapon
that the Devas sealed away.
I see.
So they tried to seal the holy war relic
with the magic of Dodekatos.
That means this ice field
is the work of Alrescha Glacies.
If this Avalon were merely
a god-killing weapon,
perhaps it really could have been sealed.
But then... what was it
that they actually sealed?
A relic...
The first thing that word brings to mind is
some sort of treasure or prized possession.
The thing that's been sleeping
down there is no weapon.
Most likely,
it's a ritual item or sacred vessel
capable of granting the qualification
to succeed the Sinful God.
That would explain why
it's been so well-guarded.
Guarded?
Does that mean the dragon
we saw was guarding it?
A dragon? You saw a dragon?!
Y-Yes, but only for a moment...
Are you talking about an actual dragon?
I'd think if one of those showed up,
it'd be pretty easy to find.
And there are still a lot
of JSDF guys in this area.
JSDF... Of course! That's it!
Akatsuki Gajou!
Asagi.
Stay in the tank with Lydianne
for the time being.
You don't want to cause trouble
for the local authorities.
Yeah, there's no way we could
make any excuses for this tank...
All yours, then!
Who are they?
That's Major Azama of the JSDF.
He was the commander of this operation.
I see.
I mean, the Special Attack Mage Regiment...
seemed to go down awfully easily.
It couldn't be!
Attack Mage Hikawa,
who are these people?
Is Shamaness Akatsuki injured?
Yes.
Is he a demon?
I'd like you to tell me all
about him in detail later.
Taking care of the wounded comes first.
Let's start with her.
Please give Akatsuki Nagisa-san to us.
Unfortunately, I cannot follow that order.
Don't move, Major Azama.
So Nagisa's safe for now, then?
Asagi and the rest, too?
Yeah, and your dad and grandma, as well.
I don't care about my dad...
But that's a relief.
Tell Asagi and the rest that it'll take
a bit longer before we can join them.
Right, you got it.
That's great to hear, Senpai.
Yeah.
I'm sorry!
I was supposed to be guarding
your sister, but I lost her,
and she ended up in danger...
Y-Yeah... But she turned out to be okay.
No, this was a failure on my part.
I'm truly sorry.
Hey, Himeragi, is she really
from the Lion King Organization?
Yes, she's a year older than me.
She was a very promising Sword Shaman cadet.
I see.
Oh, it's just... for someone
from the Lion King Organization,
she seems to really have her act together.
Excuse me?
Yuiri!
Good for you, Glenda!
They gave you some clothes!
Yuiri!
Hey, who's that girl?
I don't know much about her, either.
She only just told me earlier
that her name is Glenda.
Yuiri, they're here again.
You are Attack Mage Haba
of the Lion King Organization, yes?
I am First Lieutenant Ueyanagi of the JSDF
Special Attack Mage Regiment, 2nd Company.
Major Azama has ordered us
to act as an escort
after receiving a report of an attack here.
We will henceforth assume command here.
Give Glenda to us, Attack Mage Haba.
Yuiri...
But...
You refuse to obey us?
Wait just a minute.
You seem like you're in quite a hurry,
but would you answer one thing for me first?
Glenda only just shared her name,
and only with the person she likes most.
So how did you know it?
Until you can explain that,
we're not letting you have her.
I sensed something was off from the start.
It didn't make sense for the
JSDF to conduct this mission
on the premise that civilians would be hurt.
Plus, despite operating under such a plan,
the JSDF's elite,
the Special Attack Mage Regiment,
turned out to be surprisingly weak.
Was that because
the Attack Mage Regiment wasn't suitably
equipped to deal with magical beasts?
There was no helping that.
No one could have predicted
the appearance of so many Houdas.
If that's the case,
what did you think would
appear, Major Azama?
No...
Knight of the Sinful God?!