Tunet de Foc și Tunet Sfâșietor...
Și tu ești... un Șaman Spadasin?
Eu sunt Preoteasa cu Șase Săbii...
Șamanul Spadasin al Umbrelor.
Preoteasa cu Șase Săbii?
De la Biroul Taishi?
Asta explică multe.
Cu alte cuvinte, faci
aceleași lucruri ca și mine...
ești un magician de atac care servește națiunea, urmând ordinele primite.
Eu lucrez pentru Organizația Regele Leu, în timp ce tu lucrezi pentru Biroul Taishi.
Eu sunt Kisaki Kiriha
și nu sunt inamicul tău.
Ți-ai dat seama de asta, nu?
Iartă-mă dacă nu te cred după ce m-ai lăsat așa cum sunt acum.
Ce încerci să faci?
Știi că guvernul nu e un monolit și nici viziunile sale nu sunt toate la fel.
Obiectivele unei persoane se schimbă odată cu funcția acesteia.
Dar nu trebuie să-ți faci griji.
Odată ce mi-am terminat
treaba, te voi elibera.
Dar, mai întâi, vreau să devii pentru o vreme
un recipient pentru puterea ei.
„Puterea ei”?
Această putere... Aparține
cumva Vrăjitorii Nopții?
Deci, Eguchi Yume este...
Cum... poți să...
Ce întrebare stupidă, Kirasaka Sayaka.
Biroul Taishi luptă pentru un singur motiv.
Să protejeze această țară... nu,
ci această lume.
Chiar dacă e nevoie să scufunde insula Itogami ca să reușească asta.
Oh...
Presupun că am adormit cu toții.
Bănuiesc că voi mai dormi puțin...
Hiina...
Yaze?
Hiina!
Hei, ești bine, omule?
Dar asta a cam fost vina ta, să știi...
La naiba, m-au prins cu garda jos...
Au folosit... controlul minții?
H-Hei... Yaze!
Nu, nu face asta...
Kojou, nu te apropia...
Stai, dar eu...
Nu te uita! Te rog, nu te uita la mine!
Ce?!
Nu!
Așteaptă!
Akatsuki...
Himeragi! Te-ai trezit?
Sincronizare perfectă!
Lui Yume i-a crescut o coadă!
Se mișca printre picioare ei!
Hei, Akatsuki...
Poate că e în școala primară,
dar nu e ceva neobișnuit ca fetele de vârsta ei să experimenteze astfel de transformări.
Sau, cel putin... asta cred eu...
Ce tot spui acolo?!
Vorbim de o coadă aici! O coadă!
Și nu cred că a fost o
transformare specifică terantropilor.
Nu sunt sigur ce anume,
dar ceva era diferit!
Yume în sus, Yume în jos...
Îți place chiar atât de
mult de acea fetiță?!
Ce?! Ce naiba tot spui acolo, Himeragi?!
Nu avem timp de astfel de glume!
Nu încerca să schimbi subiectul!
Nu uita că eu sunt
supraveghetoarea ta!
Dar tu îți petreci tot timpul făcându-ți griji pentru Sayaka și Yume...
Iar, pe timp de zi, ești mereu singur cu Aiba,
flirtând și cochetând cât e ziua de lungă!
Eu... nu sunt destul de bună pentru tine?
Eu... nu te pot satisface?
Ce? Nu, nu e asta...
I-It's not about whether
you can s-satisfy me or not!
You feel unfulfilled?
Înțeleg.
Atunci, ca supraveghetoarea ta,
nu-mi rămâne de ales decât să te omor și să-mi pun și eu capăt zilelor!
Lupul Viscolului!
Ț-Ți-ai pierdut mințile?!
Nu poți flutura chestia aia aici!
Ce naiba faceți la ora asta,
fără să-mi spuneți?
Asagi?!
Uh, we were just... I mean, you know...
Flirtezi cu Himeragi pe la spatele meu?
Deci chiar o placi pe ea
mai mult decât pe mine.
Ți-ai pierdut și tu mințile?!
Și eu dau tot ce pot...
Doar am făcut toate
acele lucruri rușinoase...
Destul, Aiba.
H-Himeragi?
Tocmai am scos-o de sub controlul minții.
Ar trebui să revină la normal acum.
Deci era controlată de
cineva ca să se poarte astfel.
Himeragi, și tu erai...
Da, și eu am fost... deci...
Doar ca să știi, acelea nu erau
gândurile mele adevărate!
Nu erau, ai înțeles?!
D-Da...
Kojou...
Știi, Kojou, adevărul este că și eu...
Himeragi, te rog...
Mă ocup.
Doamne, ce mai e și asta?
De ce se poartă toată lumea astfel?
Vai, cât de plictisitor.
And after I finally made it so
you could say how you really feel.
Dar controlul meu al minții nu a funcționat asupra ta, domnule. Cine ești tu, mai exact?
Kiriha a spus că aș putea controla pe oricine, chiar și pe Leviatan.
Leviatan?
Tu nu ești Yume, nu-i așa?
Cine ești?!
Și eu sunt Yume!
Doar că Yume îmi spune „Riru”.
Riru?
Suferi cumva de... tulburare
de personalitate disociativă?
Adică personalități multiple, nu?
Ceea ce înseamnă că eu sunt o personalitate creată de Yume
ca să se protejeze de o
experiență traumatizantă.
Nu greșești, dar nici nu ai dreptate.
O experiență traumatizantă?
Ei bine, Yume a fost hărțuită toată viața ei.
De ceilalți copii de la școală și de părinții ei.
De ce?
Nu este evident?
Yume e un sucub.
Nu există prea mulți sucubi,
dar sunt buni la controlarea oamenilor.
Pot pătrunde în mințile lor
și le pot amplifica dorințele.
Îți poți imagina o elevă de școală primară fiind atât de perversă?
Yume nu a vrut să recunoască acea latură a ei,
așa că și-a separat dorințele și puterile de sucub de ea și, astfel, am apărut eu.
Deci și Yume e un demon neînregistrat?
O urăști și tu pe Yume?
Evident că nu.
Ce?
Sunt un vampir, știi?
Am fost numit indecent și pervers de mai multe ori decât pot număra
în timp ce Himeragi și celelalte fete mă lăsau să le sug sângele.
O coadă nu e mare lucru!
Ba chiar cred că e drăguță!
Oh? Ești un tip destul de drăguț, nu-i așa?
Dintr-un oarecare motiv,
mă deranjează asta.
Stai, îți plac cumva fetițele?
Pe naiba!
Sunt destul de nervoasă acum,
deci presupun că voi face
ceea ce mi-a cerut Kiriha.
Stai, Yume!
Akatsuki, la pământ!
Ce era chestia asta?
Un talisman.
Dar acest talisman aparține...
Ai venit după mine, Kiriha!
Fata de la parcul cu creaturi magice!
Kisaki Kiriha.
Mă bucur să te cunosc, al IV-lea Străbun.
Dacă voi spune că sunt Preoteasa cu Șase Săbii de la Biroul Taishi,
sunt sigură că fata din
spatele tău va înțelege.
Biroul Taishi?
La fel ca Organizația Regele Leu,
e o divizie a Comisiei Naționale
pentru Siguranță Publică.
specializată în dezastrele magice.
Și ce caută o persoană ca ea aici?
Doar îmi fac datoria.
Și nu am nicio intenție
să mă lupt cu voi.
Deși, nu pot vorbi și în numele altora.
Akatsuki!
Kirasaka? Ce cauți aici?!
Să mergem, Riru.
Președintele Kusuki te așteaptă.
Bine!
Himeragi, te poți ocupa tu de Yume?
Eu voi face ceva în legătură cu Kirasaka.
Dar, Akatsuki, Kirasaka e...
Știu.
E controlată, nu?
Looks like she's got it worse
than the rest of you did earlier.
Foarte bine.
Akatsuki, te rog să ai grijă.
When Sayaka-san takes a fight seriously,
even I'm lucky to beat
her one out of five times!
La naiba!
Șamanul Spadasin al Umbrelor II
Akatsuki Kojou!
Ce fel de monstru ești?!
I'm not an experienced fighter!
Show some restraint!
Damn... Maybe I was too hasty.
But I basically just need
to overwrite her mind control
with magic that's stronger
than whoever's controlling her!
Apari, Natra Cinereus!
Damn! Did I overdo it?
Unde e Kirasaka?
Akatsuki Kojou!
Să nu mă urăști pentru asta, Kirasaka!
O voi lua pe Yume cu mine.
Uau!
Chiar nu înțelegi, nu?
There's absolutely no reason
for you to take Riru back, is there?
Even if you only directed Sayaka-san
to attack Senpai while she was brainwashed,
I believe that's more than enough
reason to see you as an enemy.
Kusuki Elysee is legally recognized
as Eguchi Yume's guardian,
and she is trying to return
there of her own free will.
Even the Lion King Organization
has no right to stop her.
You're right...
assuming that's what
Yume-chan actually wants!
You knew this spear's true identity?
The timing was just too perfect.
The Ricercare of the Taishi Bureau,
a spear that accumulates and amplifies
magical power before releasing it.
Yume-chan's succubus powers
were accumulated within that spear,
and that's what awakened Riru's personality
and brainwashed Sayaka-san, right?
Yes, that's right.
Though I never expected all that
stored power to be depleted in this way.
Yukina-oneesan!
Now I have a reason to stop you.
Or will you choose to leave here right now?
If you think you've won just by sealing
Ricercare's power, you are naïve!
Mist Leopard: Twin Moons!
Schneesturm Wolfin!
Blood... My own blood...
I thought you were just a little girl
with nothing going for you but your looks,
but now I see why you
are the Fourth Progenitor's observer.
It's a shame we've run out of time.
Out of time?
What is this pulse?
My shadow is mist, and yet not mist;
a blade, and yet not a blade.
Once cut by it, your anguished wails
will sing the melody of
disaster, as in a dream!
Yume-chan?
Riru?!
Please stop this.
Both of you, Kiriha-san and Yukina-oneesan.
It's all right now.
I'll end all of this myself.
Yume-chan, why...
Hey, you're awake.
A-Akatsuki Kojou?!
You're not hurt?
But I ran you through with Koukarin!
Oh, so you remember what happened
while you were being controlled?
A-Akatsuki Kojou, I... um...
It's fine.
I did it on my own,
and the blood I took
from you made up for what I lost.
How typical, Senpai.
I take my eyes off of you for a moment,
and you take Sayaka-san's blood?
Yukina?!
No, no! Taking her blood was...
an emergency procedure, you know?
Like, I had to do it to save her life!
I know that.
More importantly, Senpai...
I was unable to get Yume-chan back.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize things
had reached that stage.
How could this be?
Kirasaka, if you know
something, please tell us.
What does Kusuki Elysee
want to do with Yume?
Her role is to be a sacrifice.
A sacrifice?
Chairman Kusuki of Kusuki Elysee
intends to use Yume's power as the successor
of Lilith, the Witch of the Night
and strongest succubus in the world,
to control a biological weapon buried
at the bottom of the ocean.
A biological weapon?
Is it something like Nalakuvera?
No.
This one is a monster from mythical times.
It's not something any human can control.
So what is this monster?
You might be familiar
with its name, if nothing else.
Huh?
The sea monster that's
even spoken of in the Bible...
The Serpent of Envy, the strongest
being ever created by the gods...
Leviathan.
So that's LYL?
It's smaller than I expected.
This is but one part of Riru.
The control module, to be precise.
That's why it was possible
to make it so small.
How ironic that the world's most powerful
succubus, Lilith, is such a small child.
Chairman.
I've verified the position of the serpent.
It is roughly 40 nautical miles
southwest of Itogami Island,
at a depth of approximately 400 meters.
All according to our calculations, then!
I am grateful for your cooperation.
If I can successfully tame the serpent,
perhaps I can repay my debt to you.
For crying out loud... I wake up
to find a huge hole in the yard,
plus Kirasaka-san is suddenly here,
and you tell me that
Yume-chan's been taken away?
And now we're dealing
with a giant biological weapon?
Gimme a break already!
Why is it always like this?!
I'm sorry, Asagi... but we have to hurry.
Yume's life depends on it.
I know, I know! That's why I'm—
There it is! Look, this must be Leviathan.
Huh?
Wait, where?
All of this, from here to here.
What?! That's enormous!
A bit over 4,000 meters, it looks like.
They call it the world's strongest
magical beast for good reason.
And the chairman of Kusuki Elysee
is trying to tame this thing?
Yes, using the power of Lilith
that slumbers within Eguchi Yume.
And this was probably instigated by...
The Taishi Bureau.
But aren't they a federal organization?
Why would they do that?
I don't know.
Hey! What're you whispering about?
Oh, uh, just... yeah!
Just wondering why Kusuki Elysee wants
to try to control Leviathan.
That's pretty easy to imagine.
The chairman, a man named Kusuki,
has invested in TrueArc.
TrueArc?
They call themselves
an environmentalist group,
but they're actually a terrorist organization
that conducts sabotage under
the pretext of saving magical beasts.
The head of Kusuki Elysee, a company
that buys and sells magical beasts,
invested in a group like that?
You know how these types are.
They probably both believe
they're in the right.
If someone who backs such extreme
measures to protect magical beasts
gets a hold of the most powerful
biological weapon in the world,
there'll be some trouble.
What a load of bullshit!
This Kusuki bastard wants to sacrifice Yume
for his own self-serving
idea of what's right?!
Seriously, creeps like these
are out of control.
"LYL"?
A control module
for Leviathan and... "Yotaka"?
I get it. So the actual operations
are being done at the lab.
A-Aiba-san, did you break
into Kusuki Elysee's computer?
Kojou!
Yume-chan is already
headed toward Leviathan!
Kusuki's with her!
But if I can take over this "LYL"
system in Kusuki Elysee's lab,
I can block their plans.
"Riru"?
An AI made by porting part
of Yume-chan's personality
into a computer in order
to draw out her succubus powers.
You might call it a virtual alter ego.
A personality called "Riru"
that helps Kusuki...
Asagi, can you take down this "Riru" system?
This laptop doesn't have a lot of power...
But with enough time, I think I can.
Do it, then!
Hang on, Kojou!
Where are you going,
after dumping a task like that on me?!
Wait, Akatsuki Kojou!
You're not thinking of...
I'm going to get Yume back.
This is my job, in case you forgot!
Then, help me!
I need a way to go after a submarine!
How do you expect me to—
If I may...
Are there any extra boats at Kusuki Elysee?
I think there was a high-speed craft...
But I'm not sure
if it could catch up to them.
Then, let's get moving right away!
You're coming with us, Himeragi?
Of course I am.
I'm your observer, remember?
Besides...
It's my fault we couldn't
get Yume-chan back last time.
Okay. I'm counting on you.
Right!
U-Um, this was supposed to be my job...
Whoa! Where'd that giant hole come from?!
Hey! What the hell's going on?!
Nothing! Go back to sleep!
Just wait, Yume.
You're not Lilith or Riru.
I won't let them make
a sacrifice out of you!
Foarte curând...
The iron hammer of justice will come
down upon the conceited human race.