Înțeleg...
Deci poți rămâne pe insula
Itogami fără să-ți faci griji, nu?
Asta e grozav, Yume.
Da!
Și mulțumită băiatului
nepoliticos de colo,
am și pe cineva care
să aibă grijă de mine.
Hei...
Deci, așteaptă-mă, bine?
Ce? Pentru ce să te aștept?
Mi-ai... promis, nu-i așa?
Că mă vei face fericită
pentru tot restul vieții...
Voi da tot ce pot în tot ce voi face!
Stai, nu la asta mă refeream prin...
Ce? Nu vorbeai serios?
Dle polițist! Avem un escroc aici!
Hei! Yaze!
Doamne... Ce naiba face?
Dar tu, Yukina?
Ce încerci să faci?
Dacă vrei să-i spui ceva lui Kojou,
doar mergi la el și spune-i.
Dar nu pot da busna pur
și simplu în restaurant...
De ce nu?
I don't think that's
anything to worry about.
Do you, Kanon-chan?
I... sort of understand
how Yukina-chan feels.
Really?
I mean, that's fine, though.
E destul de amuzant să
te văd astfel, Yukina.
Ei bine...
Îmi cer scuze că v-am implicat în asta.
E în regulă.
Mereu mi s-a părut distractiv
să-i privesc împreună astfel.
Vai, e așa de cald.
Voi merge să-mi iau ceva de băut.
Vino cu mine, Kanon.
Tu vrei ceva, Yukina?
Ei bine... Eu vreau un ceai verde cu gheață.
Bine, am înțeles!
Excuse me, little miss middle schooler.
Banca aceea este liberă?
Oh, da, este. Vă puteți așeza.
Mulțumesc.
Vai, ce bine.
So, what is a middle school girl
like you to Akatsuki Kojou, huh?
Poftim?!
Well, you've been giving
Kojou a hell of a death glare.
I thought maybe you were...
you know, jealous or something.
Am dreptate?
Nu!
D-Doar îl supraveghez!
Nu sunt geloasă deloc!
Supraveghezi... Supraveghezi, nu?
Is that what you call
stalking a one-sided crush?
Poftim?!
"Observing"! I love it!
Ah, to be young again!
Damn, that's so bittersweet!
Why are we even discussing this?!
Actually, first of all, who are you?!
Gajou?!
Oh, hei, Nagisa.
Chiar ești tu!
Ce cauți aici, tată oribil ce ești?!
Tată?
S-Sunteți tatăl...
lui Akatsuki?!
Eu sunt tatăl lui Kojou și
Nagisa, Akatsuki Gajou.
Încântat de cunoștință.
E așa de cald...
Hey, Natsuki-chan, today—ow!
Don't call your teacher "chan" when she's
already irritable from this stinking heat, idiot.
Today is New Year's Eve, right?
Yes, that it is.
So why am I stuck here taking
supplementary lessons right now?
Ask a certain idiot who failed his
make-up exam due to his unexcused absence.
Astarte.
Accept.
Are you being snarky?!
By the way, Akatsuki...
Where is your father right now?
He's not on Itogami Island.
I mean, not that he ever is,
but right now, he's visiting
the mainland with my sister.
What?
Well, actually, about... a week ago?
He just suddenly showed up
and said he was taking Nagisa
to see our grandma in Tanzawa.
Tanzawa... hmm...
I see.
Hang on, Natsuki-chan...
Do you know my dad?
Unfortunately.
Akatsuki Gajou made
a nuisance of himself many times
while I was working my other job.
He did come in handy
on rare occasions, though.
Your attack mage job?
What the hell was that old jerk doing?
Can you contact him?
I'm not sure.
The area around Lake Kannawa,
where my grandma lives,
has really spotty cell service.
Why do you ask, though?
Did you have business with him?
No, I was just a bit curious,
for whatever reason.
We are aliens...
Himeragi?
Y-Yes?
I'm leaving a change of clothes here.
They're Nagisa's, but they should work.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you for letting me use the bath.
Sorry to make you help
with the end-of-the-year cleaning.
Well, I had to.
If you'd been left to do it all alone,
it wouldn't have been done
before the year ended.
Damn it. What was my stupid mother thinking,
with her "If you want New Year's money,
you gotta clean! Hee hee!" line?
It's not like she cares about New Year's.
She works through it like every other day.
I'll get the New Year's soba ready.
You can have your bath in the meantime.
Minamiya-sensei said that?
Yeah. She seemed concerned
about my dad and Nagisa.
Come to think of it, it's been
a week now since they left.
Have you heard anything from Nagisa-chan?
Nope.
You haven't, either?
No.
I see... Not even a word to you...
Hey, Kojou. I came to see ya.
What're you doing here at this hour?
What're you talking about?
We said we'd all do the first
shrine visit of the year together.
Crap! Sorry, I totally forgot!
Where's everyone else?
They should be here soon.
There.
What are you guys wearing?
W-Well, it's New Year's.
We thought it'd be nice
to dress up for a change.
Do we look okay, Onii-san?
But it's crazy to wear long sleeves like
that in this island's climate!
Current Temperature
Are you okay?!
W-We're fine.
As long as we can get some water...
Here's some water for everyone.
Please help yourselves.
Yukina-chan?
Fitting in quite naturally
at Kojou's place, aren't you?
Oh, um... Nagisa-chan
is away visiting family,
so I was helping with his end-of-the-year
cleaning and New Year's soba.
Look at you two, fresh out of the bath
and smelling like the same shampoo...
Wait! You didn't actually get in together—
The hell are you saying?!
There's a child here!
Man, that hurt!
It was just a little joke to lighten things up!
Anyway...
Himeragi and I are gonna get ready now,
so sit tight for a bit.
Oh, right... The air conditioner...
I just turned it down.
Thanks, Himeragi.
They're just like newlyweds.
Motoki, this heat is making me
irritable enough as it is.
Why don't ya go to his room
to change with him, then?
It's from Nagisa. She finally—
This is...
A magic circle?
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Happy New Year!
Hey, Kojou, why are you making that face?
We don't know for sure
that anything happened to Nagisa-chan.
I know! I'm not worried or anything!
Yeah, right.
Itogami Shrine
Happy New Year
Well, go ahead and say a prayer.
They say prayers offered
at this shrine are granted.
Fortunes
One more try!
Onii-san...
Want to trade for mine?
I-It's fine!
If you're at your lowest now,
that means it can't get any worse!
Yeah. Maybe the unluckier you are,
the luckier Nagisa-chan will be!
She's not gonna end up telling us this
was just fireworks, is she?
I really doubt that,
but digital data can be
altered in all sorts of ways.
You shouldn't dwell on it so much.
Hey, Himeragi...
If this is a magic circle,
do you know what kind
of effect this type would have?
I'm sorry. Sayaka-san might
know, but I can't say I do.
Kirasaka?
Actually, this does look like...
...Sayaka-san's Koukarin, yes.
Is there anyone else
who has a bow like that?
No, they're difficult to use.
I've heard Sayaka-san
is the only one who's mastered it.
But...
I've also heard that there is
a mass-produced model
that's been simplified
to make it easier to use.
It's only a rumor, though.
I'll ask her myself.
Who's he calling?
Sayaka-san.
She knows a lot about
that type of magic circle.
How does he know Kirasaka-san's number?
No idea...
She's not answering.
In fact, it's telling me
this number isn't in use.
Then Sayaka-san's cell phone—
Hey, Himeragi!
Is there any other way
to get in touch with her?
Hey!
I know you're worried about Nagisa-chan,
but don't grab a girl like that!
Sorry, Himeragi. I wasn't thinking.
It's okay.
I'm worried about Nagisa-chan, too.
I guess I have no choice.
What do you mean?
L-Listen, Kojou...
My parents are out tonight,
so no one's home.
Want to come over?
H-Huh?
There! That's Nagisa-chan
and your dad, right?
The security cameras, huh?
I get it.
This'll tell us where they're going.
Right, yes... Of course this
is what she meant.
About what?
Nothing! Never mind!
Her dad rented a car at the airport...
using an alias.
Why an alias?
The car left Haneda on the Metropolitan
Expressway, bound for Tokyo...
But they stopped briefly
just before Shibuya.
Shibuya?
There's a record of them shopping
at a second-hand clothes shop in Harajuku.
They also stopped to eat cake.
Then they checked into a hotel, and...
What is this place? A strip bar?!
Wait, with Nagisa?!
No, he's alone.
That piece of shit!
They spent the next day
at an amusement park,
and they booked a hotel on the grounds.
Is there any point in tracing all this stuff?
Oh, it looks like they finally
got serious the next day.
Finally?
The date matches the one
on Nagisa-chan's message.
That's weird.
Do you see it, Mogwai?
Yeah.
Weird? What's weird?
They're moving around too smoothly.
It's New Year's, and they haven't
gotten caught in traffic once.
It's almost as if all the other cars
are avoiding the route to Kannawa.
Couldn't it just be a coincidence?
Did someone put up
a barrier to repel people?
But it would take a major organized effort
to put up a barrier on this scale.
I get it. I figured out the trick.
The Self-Defense Force is behind it.
They're heading toward Kannawa Lake
under the pretense of offering aid
in the wake of snowfall and landslides.
The Self-Defense Force?
But the group that's really
pulling the strings is SDC,
also known as Sorcery Disaster Control.
SDC?
No... But why...
Himeragi?
What's wrong?
Excuse me!
Hey, Himeragi! Where are you going?!
Wait, Kojou!
Thanks, Asagi! You were a big help!
I owe you dinner or something!
Jeez, what's going on?
Hey, Himeragi! What's gotten into you?
Don't follow me!
I need to know for sure.
Know what for sure?
SDC is one of the dummy organizations
under the Lion King Organization.
The Lion King Organization?
What's this about? It's called
Sorcery Disaster Control, right?
So does that mean Nagisa
was involved in a magic-related disaster?
Or they involved her in one...
Which is why I need to go find out for sure.
At that antique shop?
The one where Cat-sensei
and that Kirasaka puppet were?
I thought it was in this area...
The barrier spell has changed.
Even I can't decode it now.
If that's what they want...
Himeragi?
Senpai, please stay back here.
Schneesturm Wolfin!
That was a bit overboard...
It's an emergency!
Looks like the shop's closed.
I guess it would be, since it's New Year's.
Whoa, Himeragi!
Don't try to stop me!
Forget it! Just calm down!
Let go!
There's no point in going inside
when no one's in there!
But...
If no one has told you anything,
that must mean the Lion King Organization
is deliberately keeping us out of the loop.
That would explain Kirasaka's deal, too.
How can you be so calm right now?!
The Lion King Organization may have
involved Nagisa-chan in something terrible!
I wouldn't say I'm all that calm.
But...
Organizations always have different
factions vying for all the power.
So if there's a side to the Lion
King Organization that you don't know,
it's nothing you need
to feel responsible for.
Senpai...
Besides, there's no way
Kirasaka would ever betray you.
You're right...
I understand... so, Senpai...
I'd appreciate it if you'd let go of me now.
Where do you think you're touching, anyway?
Oh, sorry!
No, it's fine. It was
my fault to begin with.
But I guess we still don't know what
the Lion King Organization's up to, huh?
So we're stuck.
You seem troubled, Fourth Progenitor.
Kisaki Kiriha!
I'm sorry to interrupt
when you were so boldly embracing
on a street filled with love hotels
on the first day of the new year.
Wha— I-It's not like that!
We weren't embracing!
What the hell do you want with us, anyway?!
You want to know what
the Lion King Organization
is doing at Lake Kannawa, don't you?
I'm willing to tell you.
Of course, once you find out,
you may regret it.
Island Departure Exam Room
Okay, this will sting a little.
It's such a hassle going
through this every time.
I know it's necessary,
since we're in a demon district, but...
You're one brave little miss,
going all the way to
the mainland to help Kojou out.
I'm not doing it for him, okay?!
My sister's on the mainland,
and I want to see her again, too.
I just thought I'd check
in on Nagisa-chan while I'm there.
Oh?
Just shut up, would you?! It's time to go!
Gate 4, right?
We've got trouble. It's the Island Guard.
What?
They're after you, without a doubt.
You'll be fully surrounded
in one minute and forty seconds.
You've gotta be kidding!
You can get out to the taxiway
via a staircase sixty meters ahead.
Then it's all up to luck.
Damn it! Why is this happening
on the first day of the new year?!
You're sure you want to go with me?
I'm your observer, remember?
If you're leaving the island via illegal means
with help from Minamiya-sensei,
of course I'm going with you.
We'll be committing a crime, though.
You're pointing that out now?
Good point.
Asagi's house is huge,
too, but this is crazy.
Happy New Year.
We already went through
the New Year formalities!
And why are you naked?!
No, Astarte-san!
You shouldn't run around like that!
Sorry...
W-Were you in the bath?
How long do you have to stare at them?
Senpai, you are such...
an indecent person!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Barging into someone's home
and making a molester of yourself
on the first day of the new year?
You're still on my case about that?
I think I've more than paid my dues already.
What else are you here for, then?
To hound me for New Year's money?
You're close.
I want to go to the mainland. Help me out.
Then you need to go to
the appropriate office and get a visa.
But you'll need to be registered
as a demon before it'll be approved,
which would expose your identity.
That's why I came to ask you for help.
It'd be easy for you to get me off the island
without all the inspections, right?
Even if I could do that,
I don't see why I'm obligated
to do that for you.
Even if I told you
someone's life depends on it?
Don't go poking around in the
Lake Kannawa matter, Akatsuki Kojou.
No matter how much you're
worried about your sister.
You know about it?
Then please, Natsuki-chan!
You have to help me!
I refuse.
Why?!
Do I need a reason to stop my student
from breaking the law?
Fine. I get it.
Senpai?
It's okay, Natsuki-chan.
Sorry to ask that of you
without considering your position.
Senpai!
Hold it, Akatsuki. Where are you going?
To ask someone else.
No.
Natsuki-chan!
How many times must I tell you not to
address your teacher with "chan"?
Senpai!
Akatsuki Kojou...
I won't allow you to get to the mainland.