That took longer than I thought.
Wonder if the old woman's still alive...
We're only late because you
wanted to go to that amusement park
and wouldn't take no for an answer.
Hey, that was just a dad trying
to do something nice for his family.
Nagisa, sorry, but could
you wait here for a minute?
Sure, but why, Gajou-kun?
The old woman might be pissed
'cause we made her wait.
I'll go in first and calm her down.
Oh, yeah.
Gotta send Kojou-kun a message
to let him know we made it.
Oh, that's right... This place...
Come on out.
If you don't...
Mock space-severing?!
That's Der Freischütz...
no, it's Rosen Chevalier Plus, isn't it?
Freikugel Plus?!
Damn! That thing's power is...
Shit... I'm paralyzed?
It drowned out the whistling
signal arrow's sound?!
How can sound magic be defeated
by such primitive means?
Sheesh. A kid like you shouldn't be
waving that deadly thing around.
I'll have to punish you.
W-Wait!
Yuiri!
You bastard!
Sheesh.
This wouldn't have happened if you weren't
waving murder weapons around, kid.
Are you in any position to
talk down to others, amateur?
Damn it.
This really ain't my day.
Kojou-kun
Error sending message
An error occurred while sending this message. It
may have timed out due to instability in the server or network connection.
Hey, Yuiri-chan!
Is breakfast ready yet?
Don't address me as if we know each oth—
Wait, why are you topless?!
So I can work out.
Wanna join me so you can feel good, too?
Feel... good?
Stop trying to seduce Yuiri, you animal!
Shio-chan?
Ooh!
Mine!
Huh? What's wrong?
Shut up!
Huh, the Self-Defense Force is on the move?
So it's time, then.
If they're working with the
Lion King Organization,
it must be Narashino's Special
Attack Mage Regiment.
It'd be led by one of the Three Saints...
and I'm guessing they're after Avalon
at the bottom of Lake Kannawa?
H-How did you know that?
JSDF military rations, type 1.
I actually love the pickled daikon
and chicken with rice in these.
I see you are as impertinent as ever, Gajou.
Who is it you take after, I wonder?
Hisano-sama!
Finally showed yourself, eh,
you old snake-hag yokai?
Who are you calling a yokai? Such insolence.
Gajou, how much do you remember
about your children,
Kojou and Nagisa?
Your memories have indeed been devoured.
An aftereffect of the Blazing Banquet...
the Fourth Progenitor's resurrection.
What the hell do you know, you old hag?!
Hikawa Shio, you will continue to
observe him until the ritual is over.
Haba Yuiri, you will come with me.
Yes, ma'am.
Did you say... "ritual"?
Hey! What are you guys
planning to use Nagisa for?!
The very same thing you tried to do, Gajou.
We will kill Avrora Florestina...
completely, this time.
This feels great.
Hot springs really are the best.
Nothing beats a morning bath.
Too bad Yukina-chan and the
other girls couldn't come along.
I bet Kojou-kun's worried, too.
Where'd my phone go, anyway?
And Gajou-kun still isn't back...
Grandma was all gung-ho about relaxing
with a bath to start the new year,
but it's kinda lonely when
I'm the only one here.
Oh, right... Last time I was here,
I got in with Kojou-kun.
I guess there's no way we could do that now...
Ouch...
I-I'm so sorry!
Forgive me! I'm so sorry!
H-Huge...
I'm so ashamed that you
had to see me like this.
R-Really, it's no problem...
M-My name is Shirona.
Kuraki Shirona.
May I join you?
Oh, sure! Feel free!
So you're not actually
here all the time, huh?
That's right. I'm only staying here for now.
The waves...
Um...
Would you like to touch them?
Huh? I can? Are you sure?
Yes, if it would make you happy.
Th-Then... don't mind if I do!
Th-This is...
They're so soft!
And yet, they have such elasticity!
It's like they're sucking my
fingers right in! They're amazing!
That was a close one.
I could feel myself starting
to fade for a second.
A-Are you quite satisfied?
Yeah! Thanks a lot!
So... that means it's my turn now.
Huh?
Wait... Shirona-san!
No, no. You don't get to do
all the touching by yourself.
Sh-Shirona-san, not there...
This could prove to be quite
a fun body to play with.
And how about here?
Shirona-san... s-stop!
Shirona-san... are you...
No need to be afraid.
I am as a demon, but not a true demon.
In fact, I am closer to what you are,
Avrora the Twelfth.
No...
What's the status on Avalon?
Its activation has already
progressed to the critical stage.
The density of the magic at the surface
is 774 times the standard value.
Its effects on the surrounding ecosystem may
reach crisis levels within just a few days.
We will bring the matter
under control before then.
Isn't that correct,
Akatsuki-sensei?
Yes, of course.
Since ancient times, every time the
Houda has shown signs of awakening,
Kamioda Shrine has been there to silence it.
Houda?
Is that the name of the thing
sleeping within Avalon?
So say the ancient texts of Kamioda Shrine.
It is because I know how to calm this beast
that the Lion King Organization has
allowed me to assist in this operation.
Is this not so, Shirona?
Of course, that must indeed be the case.
Lady Kuraki...
Long time no see, Major Azama.
Nice to see you are well.
Kuraki... of the Three Saints?
Frankly, it surprises me
that you would choose such forceful means.
Unlike the other Saints,
I do not work for the government.
I will do what it takes to eliminate
the threat of a holy war.
Threat of a holy war...
The weapon of mass destruction?
What are your thoughts, Haba Yuiri?
Huh? Y-You're asking me?
Well... I don't think it's
exactly a "threat"...
You don't?
I-It's just a feeling... a really
vague hunch that I have...
But I don't think Avalon
itself is the calamity.
It's just... sort of sleeping...
So, well...
Shirona, would you take
her there in my place?
Oh? Interesting idea.
Very well. I shall.
Huh? In your place, Hisano-sama? What?!
Well, then... Is everything
ready, Major Azama?
Yes.
Then let us begin
the ritual to kill what was
once the Fourth Progenitor.
Wake up, Nagisa-san.
Shirona-chan?
Huh? What is this?! More of
what we were doing before?!
Please relax. We are in Lake Kannawa.
I have separated your consciousness from you
and brought it here.
My... consciousness?
Your body is on Lake Kannawa's altar.
No... That's not me!
Correct.
She is the former Fourth Progenitor,
Avrora Florestina...
Avrora the Twelfth.
I do believe you know her quite well.
What are you going to use her for?!
What is that?
A barrier to seal the calamity
that sleeps beneath Kamioda.
The people in the Self-Defense
Force call it "Avalon."
A barrier? But...
Yes, it has begun to activate.
Which is why it must be silenced at any cost.
That is the purpose of this ritual.
Ritual?
The Fourth Progenitor's bloodline
was divided into twelve beings.
Avrora Florestina was an artificial vampire
created to seal away one of those twelve.
In order to stop the calamity,
she will be presented as an offering.
She is already dead.
Your power only keeps her consciousness
here in the present age.
So, in that sense, it is not a sacrifice.
Also, by presenting her as an offering,
you will be freed from the fate of cutting
your own life short to keep her here.
No... Don't do it, Shirona-chan!
You can't do that!
That thing isn't a seal!
She's the one who's been watching over it!
You can't wake her up!
What... This is...
No...
Stop...
Avrora!
Don't!
Huh? She didn't just take
Yuiri-chan and not you
because Yuiri-chan is better
than you or anything, right?
That's not true.
My proficiency with spells
happens to be a bit higher,
but Yuiri was supposed to be
the one to get a Schneewalzer.
Oh, yeah? That's pretty incredible.
Yeah. Yuiri really is incredible.
You really like Yuiri-chan, don't you?
Wha— Where did you get that idea?!
Because you love her, it hurts to
think you aren't good enough for her,
so you want to work harder.
Right?
W-Well... yes, that's true, but...
Ugh! Why am I getting life advice
from an old man like you?!
Ah, I love it! How bittersweet!
You're adorable, Shio-chan!
Shut up!
A-Akatsuki Gajou?
Hey, Shio-chan... doesn't the
air in here feel strange?
This is...
Damn that old hag! Did she screw it up?!
Wait, how'd you get the shackle—
Restrict!
A spellgun?! Where did you—
What kind of power was that?!
Twenty years ago, I wandered into
some weird ruins in Central Asia.
All the guys on the research team who
went there with me were wiped out.
I was the only survivor, but half of me
is still there to this day.
Of course... Akatsuki Gajou,
the Netherworld Revenant...
I paid a hefty price for it,
but I can do neat tricks like this now.
Shio-chan, use your bow!
Blast 'em all away at once!
No need to ask me!
Authenticate! Freikugel
Plus: Proto III, unlock!
Registered archer Hikawa Shio authenticated.
Freikugel Plus active.
I, War Dancer of the High God,
as a dancer of the Lion, beseech thee!
Let there be light!
Wow. That's a War Dancer of the
Lion King Organization for ya.
Yuiri...
Getting older is truly a dreadful thing.
Shamaness Akatsuki! Are you all right?
I'm Lieutenant First Class Okiyama
Mikage of the 1st Company.
Major Azama is missing?
Yes.
Given the situation, he may
have been killed in action.
I have assumed the position
of acting commander for now.
I see.
I am sorry, Hisano.
I misjudged the true identity of Avalon.
That girl, Haba Yuiri, was absolutely right.
Avalon is not a seal at all.
It has been using us.
It has taken in the knowledge of every
priestess that has ever been offered to it,
all while awaiting the right moment.
So what it wanted wasn't the spiritual
power of those priestesses,
but their knowledge?
Why did this happen?
I'd say even the old hag
wasn't expecting this.
Sheesh.
Gotta get Nagisa back, at least,
even if I have to push my limits a tad.
Whoa, there!
You okay, Shio-chan?
I'm fine! I'm just fine,
so put me down right now!
You're so light. You eating enough?
Anyway, that aside...
Look. It's frozen right down to the bottom.
But how? Only a Progenitor's
Familiar would be capable of...
Oh? Then that's probably
exactly what happened.
So you're awake?
You are...
Remember me, Sleeping Beauty?
Why do you smile?
I have no words of apology for you.
Should you wish to scorn, resent,
and curse me, I shall willingly accept it.
Don't get the wrong idea.
No one's holding anything against you.
Not me, and not Kojou, either.
Is Nagisa okay?
The soul of the kind maiden is within me.
Akatsuki Gajou, was that...
Shio-chan, can you look after her for me?
Sure, I can do that,
but what are you going to do?
Can't you feel it in the air?
The air?
Is... something there?
It can't be...
What the heck was that power?
Wait... Nagisa-san?
She's gone? I have to get back to HQ—
They're acting like something's chasing them.
Huh?
Wh-Why are you naked?!
Mi?
Where am I?
That's right... We were attacked
by a girl in shrine maiden robes.
That strange power she had...
Both Himeragi and I were
powerless against it.
Oh, right! Himeragi—
Oh, Senpai... Good morni—
Senpai! Thank goodness you're awake!
H-Himeragi? Hey...
I see.
You fell asleep next to him after
watching over him all night,
and you're even giving him a glimpse
at your chest through your yukata.
It feels annoyingly like
some cheap romantic comedy,
but perhaps I could learn from it.
I suppose I should expect no less of a
Sword Shaman of the Lion King Organization.
Senpai! What are you doing in
the same futon as Kisaki-san?!
I have no idea! I just woke up here!
Oh, my.
Have you forgotten how you so thoroughly
rubbed my breasts with that right hand?
How cruel.
Senpai!
Y-Your... breasts...
I'm kidding.
That was a joke?!
Yes.
Do you even have any feeling
in your right hand?
Uh... Now that you mention it, no.
Your right arm was nearly torn off
because you were reckless enough to try to
stop an activated Schneewalzer bare-handed.
I'm sorry. This happened because
I let her take Schneesturm Wolfin.
You got it back, so what's the problem?
For now, just fix your yukata,
Himeragi Yukina.
Still...
I suppose I can say you held your
own well against Paper Noise.
Paper Noise?
Yes, the head of the Lion King
Organization's Three Saints.
She's one of the most powerful
attack mages in Japan.
I see. No wonder she was so strong.
By the way, Kisaki, where are we now?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Your room service has arrived!
I've brought your meal for you.
I'll give you a massage!
You guys?!
What are Vatler's maids doing here?!
Actually...
it was Lord Ardeal who saved us.
Ugh... So we're on his boat right now?
No, this isn't his boat.
This is a Japanese hot spring inn!
The Hakone hot springs!
Less than twenty kilometers
from Lake Kannawa.
It's close enough to walk
there if you wanted!