SA relic from the holy war?
Yes.
It may have been on a military plane
that crashed near Lake Kannawa long ago.
Lake Kannawa is a man-made lake.
A dam was built there over 40 years ago,
at the expense of an entire village.
What if that dam was built
to seal the relic away?
And what if that seal
was now about to be broken?
I see.
So it was the Taishi Bureau
that put these ideas in your heads.
Damn it! Why are you trying to stop us?!
There's a relic from the holy war
in the same area where
Nagisa's gone missing!
I don't know what's going on,
but we can't let Nagisa come
into contact with that relic!
Anything but that!
It's true.
Akatsuki Nagisa did break
the seal on a relic from the holy war.
She did?!
I guess you still have no memory of it, huh?
At any rate, I cannot allow you
to leave Itogami Island.
Just relax within my barrier
until things calm down.
Please, Natsuki-chan!
Lædingr, the chain forged by the gods, eh?
You do have such unusual
magical tools, Natsuki.
But they are no match for me.
Nina-san?! But how...
Kanon was concerned about you two.
Onii-san, Yukina-chan, this way!
Kanon-chan!
Senpai!
R-Right!
It does pain me to rebel
against my landlady in this way,
but your methods were
simply unacceptable, Natsuki.
If you wish to fight, here I am.
Thanks a lot, Kanase.
W-Well, I was worried
about Nagisa-chan, too...
It appears your negotiations
with Minamiya Natsuki failed.
Kisaki Kiriha!
I'm certain now.
Of what?
Minamiya Natsuki and the Man-made
Island Management Corporation
knew about the plan proceeding
at Lake Kannawa from the beginning.
They probably made a deal
with the Lion King Organization.
Does that upset you?
Do you have a more logical explanation?
Well...
Arguing about it here
won't give us any answers.
We just have to go there
in person and find out.
How gallant of you.
But without the assistance
of Minamiya Natsuki,
how do you intend to reach the mainland?
You can't make an omelet
without cracking some eggs.
We'll ask Vatler for help.
The Oceanus Grave II, then?
You may find that method
to be rather costly.
Well, what else can we do?
There's no other way!
You are not entirely out of options.
I've arranged one
of the Taishi Bureau's business jets.
These are fake ID cards.
Sadly, though, there isn't an extra for her.
You, girl! Stop right there!
If you don't comply, we will use force!
Hey! What the hell's going on, Mogwai?!
There must be some people who don't
want you leaving Itogami Island.
Oh, turn right at the next corner.
What?! It's a dead end!
No, this is the right way.
I figured this might happen, so...
I called in an escort for you.
You're... Tank?!
Indeed!
I am Lydianne Didier,
and I have come per
the request of Mogwai-dono!
Empress, head to parking
spot 40 on the south side!
I have a Didier Heavy Industries
cargo plane waiting there.
Hey, these IDs...
have Himeragi and me
classified as husband and wife!
How wonderful...
No, no, no, no, no!
Why the hell does it say
Himeragi is 29 years old?!
I'm not against older wives,
but that's pushing it!
It was the most suitable
fake ID card I could get.
Just try to act the age it gives you.
For the love of...
Okay, I guess there's
nothing we can do about that.
But what's your angle, Kisaki Kiriha?
Why are you guys doing all this for us?
To be mean.
What?!
The interests of the Taishi Bureau and the
Lion King Organization oppose each other.
So if they're doing everything in their power
to keep you away from Lake Kannawa,
how could I not take advantage of that?
It seems they haven't given
you any information at all.
If that bothers you,
you're welcome to leave right now.
I'll take over for you.
No. Whatever my superiors are planning,
I will continue to observe Senpai.
That is the duty I have been tasked with.
I see. Then I suppose
nothing more can be done.
Stop! Stop the car, please!
Now!
Whoa!
I told you I wasn't going to
let you go, Akatsuki Kojou.
I see. You didn't let Akatsuki Kojou leave.
You were just waiting for him
to go somewhere with fewer people,
Witch of the Void.
Correct, little girl.
If that idiot were to cut
loose in the middle of town,
it'd be a pain in the ass to clean up after him.
That said, it's not like I want to
play war with you lot, either.
Akatsuki Kojou, if you just come quietly,
no one will have to get hurt.
Like hell I can do that!
I'm going to save Nagisa!
After that,
you can give me supplementary lessons,
or throw me in the prison barrier, or whatever!
So right now, just let me do this!
No.
Why?!
If the thing at the bottom of
Lake Kannawa really is a holy war relic,
and you come in contact with it,
you won't come back unscathed.
Especially now, when you still
don't remember anything about Avrora.
Avrora?
What am I supposed to remember?!
Avrora sleeps within your sister.
Avrora Florestina, the one you killed...
a fragment of the Fourth Progenitor.
Senpai!
I can assure you of one thing.
What the Lion King wants
is Avrora's power, and nothing more.
They don't consciously wish
to put Akatsuki Nagisa in danger.
The opposite, in fact.
In order to fulfill their goal,
they'll probably fight
to the death to protect her.
I see.
So that's why you're helping
the Lion King Organization.
I guess I can still respect you, then.
And Himeragi...
The Lion King Organization
didn't betray you.
They just didn't tell you about all this
to make sure I wouldn't try
to pull anything.
Senpai...
I'm glad you told me all this, Natsuki-chan.
Now I definitely need to get to
the mainland, whatever it takes!
Are you saying you remember everything now?
No, if anything, I'm even more confused now.
But there's just one thing
that I'm absolutely sure of.
No matter how they try to rationalize it,
I won't let anyone use Nagisa
or the Avrora inside her
for their own selfish gains.
And if anyone tries to do that,
I'll crush them myself.
From now on, this is my fight!
No, Senpai.
This is our fight.
Himeragi...
Hey...
The you I'm looking at is a double
that you made with magic, right?
And if it is?
Then I don't need to hold back!
Come, Regulus Aurum!
Awaken, Rheingold!
The Fourth Progenitor's Familiar...
is being held down by force?
I won't let this go any further!
Stay out of this!
Senpai!
Onii-san!
What the hell happened?!
They're gremlins that screw
with electronic functions.
Island Guard attack mages must've sent them.
Isn't there anything you can do, Mogwai?!
'Fraid not.
Thanks to those gremlins,
all electronic functions in this area ar—
Mogwai?!
Oh, crap!
You!
Priestess of Cain, he awaits you.
Go to him.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Little miss!
Island Guard reinforcements
are on your tail!
Empress, the cargo plane is ready to depart!
Okay! Go, Tank!
All will proceed as my king has guided it.
We're done here. You still want to fight?
As I said, this is my fight, too.
An illusion?!
Amateur. How could you fall
for such a simple trick?
It's over.
Not yet, it isn't.
What're you playing at?
As the Six-Blade Priestess,
also known as the Black Sword Shaman,
it would disturb me if you lost so easily
to a Sword Shaman from the Organization.
Have it your way.
The end result won't change.
Big talk, for a witch.
I'll kill you!
Sorry, Kanase.
I didn't mean for you to get involved.
Don't worry about me.
It was my choice to come with you.
We'll get out of here somehow...
My strength...
I'm draining your magic out of you...
through that Familiar outside.
Natsuki-chan?! But how?!
We're inside my dream, after all.
I just made myself look my real age.
After all that fighting,
you dragged Kanase into your mess.
And after I kept your identity as
the Fourth Progenitor secret all this time...
It didn't matter.
I had a feeling you weren't
just an ordinary person, anyway.
I see.
Thanks, Kanase.
Tell me, Natsuki-chan.
Why are you going to such lengths to stop me?
I told you. If you go,
you're going to get hurt.
What is the Lion King Organization planning?
And is she really...
Is Avrora really sleeping within Nagisa?
The Lion King Organization isn't looking
to dig up the holy war relic.
What they're after is the seal.
A god-slaying relic that has slept
for so long at the bottom of Lake Kannawa,
a weapon of mass destruction,
is on the verge of awakening.
Their goal is to seal it away
for good this time.
That means you'd just be
in the way, Fourth Progenitor.
Because the god-slaying relic
might react to my magic,
causing it to awaken faster?
Exactly.
But that means...
If Avrora is inside Nagisa,
isn't she in danger, too?!
So why?!
Avrora Florestina knows the spell
that can seal the weapon of mass destruction.
You probably don't remember it,
but the twelfth Kaleid Blood
is a vessel meant to contain
and seal the soul of the Fourth Progenitor.
A vessel?
But if it does that,
what'll happen to Avrora's soul?
Nothing.
That girl is already gone.
The part of her that your sister
is gradually giving her life to keep here
is no more than a lingering thought.
It's only a single fragment
of a soul that is already lost.
Why didn't you tell me all
this in the first place?
If I had, would you have given up?
No.
That's why.
Relax. I'll make you forget all this
before you leave here.
Screw that!
You expect me to just sit back
and accept all this?!
Onii-san!
Damn it... My strength...
Honestly... I have such useless students.
Between those impudent girls outside
and you...
You're all a bunch of weaklings
who can't even touch me.
What do you expect to do against
a weapon of mass destruction?
This is only getting worse.
I'm sorry, Kisaki-san,
but could I ask you
to buy one minute of time for me?
One minute against that witch?
You'll be risking your life.
I know that.
Please do it anyway.
You...
If you go down as the loser
after putting me through all this,
I'll make you regret it,
Himeragi Yukina!
Execute Rhododactylos.
Astarte...
I hope you're prepared to be punished.
Apologize, Master.
I have to commend you on your way
with women, Akatsuki Kojou.
You even managed to get
a homunculus who can't defy her master
to take your side!
Miss Kanase.
Remove your clothes.
Huh?
Remove...
Hang on, Astarte!
What are you trying
to make me do to Kanase?!
Answer: blood donation.
All right.
Onii-san, please take my blood.
Kanase...
I knew that you were always
doing this with Yukina-chan.
That's how you saved me.
So this time, it's my turn.
You have to...
save Nagisa-chan, Onii-san...
Divine possession?
But the slightest mistake could cause her
to lose her personality...
She's willing to go
that far for Akatsuki Kojou?
You okay, Astarte?
Leave the rest to me.
So you've sunk your venomous
fangs into Kanase now,
you lecherous brat?
Yeah.
And now, another Familiar I couldn't
control before is about to wake up.
What did I tell you?
You can't use your Familiars here.
Yeah, that's true.
But I can use them outside!
I, Akatsuki Kojou, successor
to the blood of Kaleid Blood,
now release your constraints!
Come, first Familiar,
Mesarthim Adamas!
Is that...
the Fourth Progenitor's...
I, Sword Shaman of the High God, as a priestess of the Lion, beseech thee...
Snow?
No... they're crystals
created by divine vibrations.
Dawn light of exorcism, spirit wolf of snowy mist...
Grant me the divine might of thy steel,
that I may smite a hundred evil spirits!
This divine energy... I see.
This is why you were chosen
to be the Fourth Progenitor's observer.
Very well. We're even.
You mean... you're going to let us go?
I don't want you breaking Itogami Island
or the prison barrier any further.
Huh?!
I thought I'd give you
a little parting gift.
Parting gift... You don't mean...
Here.
I know you're planning to ditch the rest
of your winter supplementary lessons.
Turn those in, and you're off the hook.
You should be grateful.
Huh? Oh... That's what you meant...
What? Did you think I was
going to let you suck my blood?
Huh?
Hmph.
Just do your best to show up
to class on time after winter break.
Natsuki-chan...
Don't address your teacher
with "chan," idiot.
So you really did suck her blood?!
I didn't have a choice!
Besides, it was only Kanase,
not Natsuki-chan...
You tried to suck
Minamiya-sensei's blood, too?!
So you really do prefer small girls!
Hey, don't get the wrong idea!
She wasn't in her usual loli image!
She looked like a real woman teacher,
dressed her age,
with actual boobs like... Get it?!
A real woman teacher, you say?
With boobs, too? I see.
You really are an indecent person, Senpai!
No, you've got it all wrong!
I had no choice!
I swear, Senpai!
Just listen to me!
I don't care if you flirt, but...
We're not flirting!
Shouldn't you be leaving—
It seems the Witch of the Void
is more naïve than I thought.
No, I suppose that is her true nature.
Paper Noise...
You!
Your voice... Are you...
Pleased to meet you, Fourth Progenitor.
I am one of the Three Saints
of the current Lion King Organization.
My name is Shizuka Koyomi.
I am sorry, but per the collective
will of the Lion King Organization,
I have come to prevent you
from leaving this island.