Fenrir, an S-Rank monster capable
of destroying a major city by itself.
A village under constant
attack from this beast
has spent nearly all of their savings
to hire us, the Flaming
Dragon Fang, to defeat it.
Bandana!
Leave it to me!
Heal!
Do it, Leader!
Bandana, the swift Ranger.
Marlefiss, the Priestess.
And Golnova, the flaming Warrior.
After defeating Fenrir,
we, the Flaming Dragon Fang,
became a party of heroes.
My story is one you don't hear so often—
that of a powerless man
in a party full of heroes
who handles their chores on
a journey to save the world.
This tastes like shit.
Is this village incapable
of serving decent food?!
Hey, Kur!
Make me something to eat!
Yes, sir!
I'll prepare something right away.
Today's the last day we get
to eat Kur's cooking, after all.
Huh?!
Um, what do you mean by that?
Not the sharpest, are you?
It means you're fired.
Huh?!
Did I do something wrong?
More like, you haven't done enough.
You just do chores
and can't even defeat a slime!
Parties can only have four members.
That is the law of this world.
If we want to become even stronger,
we'll need to recruit a high-ranked mage.
That means we need to drop
someone from the party.
You might carry our bags for us,
but you're basically baggage yourself, Kur.
No way...
Please, Golnova!
Please let me stay in the party—
Shut up!
Turns out, my story is one
you hear all too often—
that of powerless man kicked out
of a party full of heroes
who now travels with nowhere to go.
The Unaware
ATELIER MEISTER
The Common Tale of How
the Guy In Charge of Chores
With Low Self-Esteem
Turned Out to Actually
Possess Incredible Skills
So this is Hello Work?
I'm so anxious.
But I need to earn money!
Pardon me...
Welcome to the Samaela Branch
of Hello, Hello Work Station!
Are you looking for work?
Or are you looking to hire?
U-Um... I'm looking for work.
In that case,
we'll start with an interview
and an aptitude test.
Could you start by telling me
your name and age?
Okay.
My name is Kurt Rockhans.
I'm 15 years old.
Kurt, you said? Where are you from?
Hast Village, in the Sheen Mountains.
I didn't know there was a village out there.
What kind of work have you done so far?
Uh...
I handled various chores for the
adventuring party Flaming Dragon Fang.
The one that was promoted
to SS-Rank the other day?
They fired me, though.
Even so, I'm sure it'll be quite
the feather in your cap!
People will look upon me favorably
just for handling chores there?
Golnova and the others really are incredible.
Now, let's move on to your aptitude test.
As you know, your aptitudes are
the talents granted to you by God.
Perhaps we'll be able to uncover
some hidden talents of yours.
Y-You think so?!
Aptitudes are rated from G-Rank,
meaning no talent at all,
all the way up to SSS-Rank, the highest.
While someone with a low aptitude for
swordsmanship may not be able to cut steel,
someone with a high aptitude could
split it in two with the same sword.
Maybe I have my own hidden talents?
They're all... G-Rank.
The results show that you have
no talent for any combat skill.
I'm sorry, but this will limit
the work you're capable of.
There's still trade work, though!
We haven't tested your aptitude for things
like blacksmithing or alchemy yet.
Though our technician is currently absent,
so you'll have to wait about a week.
Um, to tell you the truth,
I barely have any money left.
I see.
Then...
could you try lifting that sandbag there?
Sure.
Huh?
It felt like it drained a bit of my mana.
It's heavy!
Okay, that's good enough.
If you're that strong,
then you should be able to
handle construction work.
A frontier town in the
Margraviate of Taicone
is recruiting workers to
repair their city walls.
Would you like to work there?
Yes!
Then I'll prepare a letter
of introduction for you.
Thank goodness! I found work!
A temp worker?
Hm...
Well, we are shorthanded,
so we can't be picky.
Listen, boy. I'm only going to
say this once, so pay attention.
Yes, sir!
Make cement!
Then mend the walls!
Yes, sir!
Huh?
Do I not need to go through
the process of pouring mana
into the cement to strengthen it?
Um—
I'll come check on you in three hours.
Make sure you've gone through
at least half a barrel's worth by then!
Your pay's based on performance,
so you'll lose money if you slack off!
I guess pouring mana into it
is such common knowledge
that he doesn't even need
to explain that part?
I must seem pretty unreliable to him.
I'm surprised half a barrel is good enough.
But I'll give it my all
instead of taking it easy!
Wh-What the hell is this?!
I'm sorry!
I ran out of cement,
so this was as far as I could get!
You... ran out?
He repaired a whole third
of the huge western wall
in just three hours?
How did you even handle the upper parts?
I don't see any scaffolds or ladders.
I scooped up the cement, threw it into place,
and then rolled it out with this.
There's no way you could—
No, it's clear that you already have.
How much longer can you work here?
I was hoping to work here for about a week!
I see.
All right. That's enough for today.
Sorry, but this is all
I can pay you right now.
I'll transfer the rest of your pay
later through Hello Work.
Are you sure about paying me this much?
Of course.
Now take it.
He paid me so much after saying
it was based on performance!
All right, I'll do my best tomorrow, too!
Hey, what's going on here?!
What happened here?!
Seriously?!
I heard they finished repairs
on the west and north walls!
What?!
Is there any work left?!
Three days ago, there was only a portion
of the western wall done, right?
You don't need to come back after today.
Huh?
But it's only been three days—
The wall repairs were supposed to
provide work to those in poverty, too.
If you stay here any longer,
there won't be anything left for the others!
Huh?
You work too fast!
Too fast? Me?
At any rate!
The ability you demonstrated here
is on par with SS-Rank, if not SSS!
Get out of here and go
work in the royal capital!
S?
Here's the rest of your pay.
Later!
Did he want to get rid of me so badly
that he flattered me and paid me off?
It didn't work out, huh?
Oh, well.
Yes.
But what should we do now?
There's still a few more days
before our technician arrives.
Why can't you accept it?
No one will take on a job
with those conditions.
You won't know until you try!
Please keep my conditions as-is!
She's pretty.
We can't accept it,
no matter how hard you insist.
Kurt, please wait a moment.
Oh, sure.
It's your job to find someone!
What seems to be the matter?
I don't have time to—
This woman is looking to hire a miner.
However, she insists on paying
based on successful results
without any advance payment
for an unproven mountain.
Madam, if those are your conditions,
then I recommend you recruit investors
to develop a mine.
If I don't pay the taxes within a week,
then they'll impound the mountain!
That's a tough position to be in.
Um...
Would I be able to take on the job?
Huh?
Back in my village,
I used to help excavate in the mines!
Are you sure about this?
To be honest, you can't expect
to be paid for it, Kurt.
Hold on a second!
I want to hire someone like a brawny dwarf,
not a helpless child like him!
In that case, you'll need
to prepare 10 silver.
If I had that kind of money...
Whatever.
Uh, Kurt, was it?
You do have experience, right?
I do.
Fine.
Follow me.
R-Right!
Thank you so much, miss!
Honestly, Kurt is too nice.
With his adorable looks,
he'd be better off working
in the pleasure quarters...
Ah! Kirshell!
Kirshell!
Kirshell?
Kirshell, we've received a bank transfer.
Kirshell!
Oh, right!
I-I was just...
This is the construction work pay
to be deposited in Kurt's account, right?
Two...
Two hundred gold?!
Wha? Huh? How?
Kirshell!
Ow...
Are you okay?
Y-Yes.
What are these sandbags doing here?
We're returning them.
By the way, those aren't sandbags.
They're used to measure how much mana
a person possesses in their body.
They get heavier the more mana a person has,
but they generally don't react
to normal people.
It takes mana on the level of a royal
court mage to activate them,
so they're hard to use.
Huh?
Speaking of which, could you
move them outside for us?
Sure thing.
It's heavy, but not that heavy...
Kurt, who in the world are you?
We're here.
Huh? Um, there's only one tent.
It's big enough for two people to sleep in.
We're both sleeping in the same tent?!
Are you an incredibly restless
sleeper or something?
That's not it!
I can't share a tent with a
cute woman like you, Yulishia!
Wha?!
Cute? Me?!
You're kidding, right?!
I'm serious.
I've traveled the whole world,
and I've never seen anyone else
as beautiful as you, Yulishia.
Stop it! Don't say another word!
I've been adventuring since I was ten.
There's no way I'm cute!
Now, stop saying weird things!
Come on! Time to eat!
You cooked this, Yulishia?
This hardly counts as cooking.
I just boiled it.
It's been a long time
since anyone cooked for me,
so I'm happy!
Golnova and the others
never even ate with me.
It's so good!
R-Really?
I-I can't sleep!
I wonder if Yulishia's asleep?
Yulishia, you're too trusting.
I'm a man too, you know.
We'll be together for a week,
so I was planning to use this night to determine
if he's the kind of guy who'd assault me.
He's a good boy.
More importantly, he's cute.
I mean, he'll be fun to tease.
Did he sleep outside all night?
Huh? It's fixed?
With a new button, too?
Oh, good morning, Yulishia.
Did you fix my clothes for me, Kurt?
Oh, yes.
Seriously?!
Th-Thanks.
You're welcome.
This boy is definitely
working in the wrong place.
Let's head out once you're ready.
We need to earn ten gold
before the week is up, after all.
Right!
Um, so have you decided
where to start digging?
No, we'll just start digging
from somewhere nearby.
Huh?!
Uh, you won't find any ore
if you just dig at random.
Really?
That's right.
In that case, I'd like to take
a quick look around for something,
so please follow me!
Found it.
This is what we want.
When you split one of these...
Huh?!
Don't tell me that's a gemstone!
It's a crystal.
One this big should go for around three gold.
We've already hit a third of our goal?!
Phew.
I've finished looking into
the rocks around this area.
Amazing!
Uh, so the next step is to sell these, right?
Huh? No way.
R-Right.
Yeah, you did find all of them yourself.
All but the first one are too small
to be worth very much,
so we'll turn them into magic crystals.
Huh?
I thought there were fewer
than ten magic craftsmen
in the kingdom capable of
manufacturing magic crystals...
All done.
You're done?!
I'm pretty sure I heard that it takes at least
an hour to make even the smallest one!
A whole hour?!
I don't have much mana,
so I couldn't do that.
So real magic craftsmen are capable
of emitting mana for a whole hour.
I get the feeling we're not on the same page.
Are you really staying here, Kurt?
Yes. There are things I'd like to do here.
Don't push yourself too hard, okay?
I should be back tomorrow morning
after I sell the magic crystals.
Okay.
Take care, Yulishia!
Ah, damn it, he's just too damn cute!
You have magic crystals?
Do you have the proper documents
for crystals from abroad?
These were produced domestically, so I don't.
Domestically?
By which atelier?
Of course they'd ask that.
You're an adventurer serving
directly under the royal family?!
My apologies!
Could I use your teleportation stone?
I need to go to the royal capital.
I only used to serve under
the royal family, though.
Well, even if I told them the truth about
these crystals, it's not like they'd believe me.
Welcome!
Oh, it's you, Yulishia.
I'm actually here on business today.
I was thinking of having you
buy these from me.
Magic crystals, huh?
Their glow doesn't seem that strong,
so they're probably not worth much, though.
About 10 silver?
Around that much, yeah.
Huh? This is...
Hold on a moment.
Given how he made them,
I'm not surprised they don't go for much.
Yulishia, I can buy this
from you for 10 gold.
Huh? Why?!
This magic crystal has ten times the
usual amount of mana imbued in it.
Even though its glow is so dim?
It's not glowing very much
because it's been treated to prevent
the mana inside from leaking out.
I have 49 more of them.
Here, 500 gold.
But can I ask two things of you?
First of all,
don't sell these magic crystals
anywhere but my shop.
I doubt any other shops would
understand their proper value,
and our kingdom wouldn't want magic crystals
this strong out in regular circulation.
What's the other thing?
Tell me who made these.
That I can't do.
Why not?
Someone who can make
magic crystals this strong
should be working directly for the kingdom.
Or are you trying to monopolize them
for your own profit?
That isn't why.
I just don't want to share information
about them without their permission.
Yulishia, this is an order.
By the power vested in me as a royal court mage
with status equal to an Honorary Count.
I don't serve directly under
the royal family anymore.
I'm not obligated to obey your orders.
And yet you seem to have no issue taking
advantage of your old status when it suits you.
All right.
Then let me ask as a friend.
Please do everything you can to prevent
them from wandering off to another nation.
Also, please inform them
that we can offer them the directorship
of a royal magic technology research lab
with the title of Honorary Baron,
possibly Honorary Count pending the
proper permission from His Majesty.
Sure.
She paid me 500 gold and wants to make
Kurt a director and a Honorary Count?!
This doesn't make any sense!
I'm sorry. We've already closed for the day.
Oh, you're...
I want to ask you a few things about Kurt!
Huh?!
Just who in the world is Kurt?
I'm sorry. We have a duty to protect
the confidentiality of our clients.
Huh? Kurt was a part of
the Flaming Dragon Fang?
Yes.
And yet he's G-Rank across the board.
He was fired from his job repairing
castle walls after three days,
but his payment was...
Two hundred gold?!
They said he finished repairing both the
northern and western walls by himself.
No wonder they had to let him go.
All right. Thank you.
Also, please deposit this
into Kurt's account, as well.
What's this?
It's 499 gold.
Huh?!
Also, I'm ordering you as an adventurer
directly serving under the royal family.
You are hereby forbidden to divulge
any information about Kurt.
I understand.
Oh, Yulishia, welcome back.
Uh... What is this?
I built it while you were away in town.
Incidentally, Kurt,
what are your thoughts on constructing
an entire house in a single night?
Huh?
People did it all the time in my hometown,
so it's nothing special, right?
There's no way that's normal!