I am autonomous Al
robot Cleo-Neo Zero.
Things ought to go fine this time.
Entering test mode.
Commencing verification
test number 18.
Trajectory confirmed.
Proceeding to target.
That's it, Cleo-Neo Zero!
Keep going!
All systems nominal.
Gwah!
Owowow..
Cleo-Neo Zero, are you okay?!
I am Cleo-Neo Zero.
Oh, good.
Yeesh, can't believe
took a fall for a robot...
Are you all right?
That was quite a nasty fall!
So, about that body of yours...
are you hurt?
Ahaha...
No, I'm okay.
That's good.
It's very noble to risk your
safety on behalf of a robot,
Akutsu Eita.
Agatsuma Makina,
how do you know my—
We're classmates, right?
Ah... y-yeah, right.
Thanks for your concern!
And that was more than
enough of an experience
for a big ol' robot-obsessed
nerd like me to fall in love..
Ep. 01: Makina is Discovered as a Robot
Makina, Makina! When can we play badminton?
Some other time!
Miss Agatsuma's got
such a bright disposition...
not like an introverted bookworm like me.
That conversation we had earlier
was our first and probably last.
We just live in different worlds...
Today's lecture is on the ethics of A.I.
need to stay focused on my future!
And with that,
I hope you all have something
of a better understanding
of the coming age of A.I. robots
I'm offering a position in my lab to whichever
one of you can make the best A.I. robot
using only your own skills.
I need an assistant... whatever it takes...
You're beautiful...
So beautiful...
Wouldn't people rather
see your true form?
I prefer to stay out of the public eye.
Huh, did something happen?
I'm home, ma'am!
Apparently there was an
explosion in the neighborhood.
Did anything happen to you, Eita?
No.
Thank goodness you're safe.
I promised your
mother I'd look after you.
I'm fine!
There's someone here...
It's a girl!
You finally came home.
Miss Agatsuma?!
Just 'Makina' will do.
Akutsu Eita, head and
member of the Robotics Club,
has experience participating
in drone competitions,
resides alone in this
apartment, no friends,
far removed from any family,
lacking in local acquaintances..
How do you know so much about me?
And above all else...
a big mecha nerd willing to risk
his own safety on behalf of a robot.
Huh? What's this?
Specs for a humanoid robot?
I've never seen a design like this.
I'm guessing those are actuators?
But with modern technology,
would this even work?
If you can tell that much
just by looking, then you pass.
I pass...?
You'll be my first mission target!
Y-Your body!
I believe this is called..
"finding out someone is a robot."
You can see the state I'm in.
Think you could help me out?
I'll totally... make it worth your while..
Makina!
I don't believe it.
Makina, my classmate,
the girl I secretly pined for...
is a machine?!
I should...
call the police...
This is incredible.
To think this is real...
With the manual as my guide,
I fumbled about with the unfamiliar
designs as I did my repairs.
There aren't any wires.
I guess these sockets use ball joint gears, then?
That's it for the internals.
Reconstructing the skin
will take roughly eight hours.
All there is to do now is wait.
Where did this technology come from?
I stayed up reading
the manual all night long.
My classmate was like something
ripped from the pages of science fiction...
Whoa, what's this?!
Ah, good as new!
Looks like we
picked the right guy!
And my outer covering is back
together without so much as a scratch!
Dang I am I high-spec!
Umm, Makina? B-Begging your pardon,
but c-c-could you please p-put some clothes on?!
Wait, have you been up all night?
Yeah, I was all caught up
in your design specifications.
You read all of it?
All the parts of it that I could, anyway.
Then I guess I don't need to
explain what I really am to you.
You're a f-fully autonomous A.I. robot...
I think 'ultra high-performance
future-tech android' sounds better...
wouldn't you agree?
A-A-Android! Ohhh, yes!
I am a sexual love robot,
an android agent designed to
seduce and manipulate my targets.
Why would someone make one of those?!
- Y'know, I'm not really sure.
- Huh?
Hey, relax.
My current mission is just to
engage in everyday student life.
And yet for SOME REASON,
when I got home from school yesterday,
the whole place went up with a
bang as soon as I opened the door!
Wait, that fire was at
your place, Makina?!
—People were coming, and I
couldn't let them see I was a robot,
so I needed to lay low and find
someone who could do repairs on me.
I needed someone I knew
who had robotics skills,
and who lived alone,
so I came here in order to
make you my first mission target.
L-Listen, can you PLEASE
just put on some clothes?!
The ones I had
were blown to shreds.
Besides, clothing would
just get in the way right now.
Huh?!
Boy, are you dense. It's like I said:
I've made you my first mission target.
I mean, I've seen the
way that you look at me.
I-It's not like that!
You like me...
don't you?
Um:..
Well... I meannn...
So c'mon, let's have sex.
Right now.
Whaaaaaaa?!