Dammit! Why?!
I can't produce my fire!
Marlefiss!
Hurry up and heal me!
I already am!
But I'm not putting out my usual power?!
Hey, newbie! Can't you use fire magic?!
You said you could use it!
Tsk! Useless idiot!
What was that?!
Cut it out already!
This isn't the time for that!
This party is already done for.
They want me as the director of a
royal magic technology research lab?
They'll treat me like a noble?
Yeah.
How did something that incredible happen?
The person I had appraise your magic crystals
serves as a royal court mage as a hobby.
Are you sure she's not deceiving you?
Well, I know it's hard to believe,
but what do you think?
I'm sorry.
It certainly is a good offer,
but please turn it down for me.
Huh?
I can't imagine myself working in
a role that puts me above others,
and part of me still wants to go back
to Flaming Dragon Fang.
Besides...
My current job is working here after all!
Kurt...
The magic crystals you went and sold
weren't enough to pay your taxes, right?
Oh, well, I sold them for quite a bit,
but I didn't make those myself.
I just took one gold as a handler's fee
and deposited the rest into your account.
You didn't need to worry about me like that.
Yes, I do.
If I accepted such a hefty sum,
I would be crushed under the guilt.
Huh?
I-It's nothing!
But that's why I'd like you
to keep digging up ore.
Leave it to me!
I found what looks like it might
be a good vein yesterday too!
You're a huge help.
But Kurt, you haven't slept, right?
I'm fine. I got six hours of sleep.
Six hours?
Yes.
Even though you built that log house?
Five hours to fell the trees,
three hours to process them,
four hours to put it together...
Huh? Did I sleep too much?
Back when I was with Flaming Dragon
Fang I only got around four hours.
That leaves...
They said the one in charge of
chores had to wake up earlier
and go to sleep later than everyone else.
Umm, I promise to make up for how much I rested!
Huh?
This is where you think you found a good spot?
Yes.
I don't see anything out of the ordinary?
That's true.
Though considering the
topography of the mountain,
there should be an ore deposit beneath here.
But please don't dig
any deeper than 50 meters.
50?
Okay, I'll be heading elsewhere.
You won't be digging with me?
No. I plan to dig around the area where
we found that large crystal yesterday.
All right. I'll leave that to you then.
Yes! I'll be heading out.
I found it!
This is a topaz?
It's rather big!
I bet this would go for around three gold!
I bet I could ask Kurt to turn it
into a magic crystal for free.
Then I'd have plenty to reach my goal!
No, don't!
I shouldn't be trying to use
that innocent boy for free!
I wonder what Kurt is up to.
Knowing him, he's probably
made a whole mining tunnel.
I expect that much...
but see!
It's bright?
We don't need lamps due to luminous moss?
Well, that's within expectations!
Even so, this space is huge!
It's three times bigger than I thought!
But this is Kurt we're talking about!
So that's within expectations too!
Oh, Yulishia!
I was just thinking of heading over to you.
I'm afraid to ask, but how'd it turn out?
I'm sorry.
All I've mined have been useless rocks,
and I've only mined tiny
fragments of the ore I'm after.
I see, I see. That's goo—
That's a shame.
Are those the useless rocks?
Yes.
They look like rather pretty stones.
I'm able to mine a lot of them though,
so they're not very valuable.
They're called mythril.
Mythril?!
You know about it?
We harvest so much of it in my
village that we threw it away.
Do I know about it?! That's a far more
valuable ore than gold or even platinum!
And he throws it away?!
This is unexpected.
Are you saying that it's valuable around here?
Is it hard to acquire in the city or something?
It's an extremely rare ore throughout
the world. And yet he...
Wait. Then what is the ore you
said you were after earlier?
Orichalcum.
Orichalcum?!
The legendary ore known
as the metal of the gods.
I can't believe there's something
like that in this mountain.
Huh? You can generally mine it anywhere.
There's no way that's true.
You can often find it after digging
about 7km into the ground.
7km?
You dug down 7km in 8 hours and came
all the way back up to the surface?
Yes.
Well, this is you we're talking about.
By the way, what about the shaft?
It would be dangerous to
leave it, so I filled it in.
You even refilled it within 8 hours?
Nothing's going to surprise me anymore.
I see.
You dug right through the mountain.
This new tunnel looks convenient.
Should I fill it back in?
You don't need to fill it.
I finished the mining in two
days and we returned to Samaela.
That tunnel was positioned to connect the
city of Samaela to Lord Taicone's town.
Lord's Town
Yulishia's Mountain
Samaela
Royal Capital
Frontier Town
Apparently Yulishia agreed to permit
those with the traveling merchants guild
to pass through it
in return for them paying
a maintenance fee.
She told me the profit from
that would cover her taxes.
Kur!
Oh, Bandana?!
How have you been?
What are you doing here?
Is Golnova with you too?
Nuh-uh, I ain't a part of Flaming
Dragon Fang anymore either.
Huh?
A bunch of stuff happened.
I can't eat trash like this!
Sir, please stop!
Shut it!
Ah, Sir, your bill?!
Obviously I ain't paying!
S-Sir?!
Somebody! Please call the guards!
How was eating at that popular restaurant?
I worked hard to get them
to squeeze in a reservation.
Bandana!
We still have that smoked meat
Kur made before he left, right?
It's all gone now.
You ate it all, Leader.
Then go fetch Kur!
Make him cook food for us!
If he fights back, then I don't
care if you have to hurt him a bit!
Sure thing. You got it.
Just leave it to me.
Anyway, I'll need to borrow
the teleportation crystal.
Hmph.
The culprit fled into this area!
Be alert!
Yes, sir!
Guess he would get arrested
after making such a commotion.
Marlefiss lucked out,
being summoned away by the church.
Now Flaming Dragon Fang is truly finished.
Well, I'll pay you a visit in
prison if I feel like it, Leader.
I'll leave out all of that and
say I was simply fired too.
I wouldn't want my surveillance
target involved in that mess too.
I can't believe you were fired too, Bandana.
It's definitely impossible for me to
return to Flaming Dragon Fang then.
Why are you so set on that party anyway?
Because I owe Golnova a lot, and I admire him.
Admire him, huh?
He certainly did serve as an excellent front.
Oh yeah! Kur, if you're going to Hallo Work,
then that means you're looking for work, right?
Yes.
Perfect!
I actually have an acquaintance who's short
on hands and struggling in their workshop.
Could you go give them a hand?
A workshop, huh?
There are only 15 Atelier Meisters with
official permission from the country.
One of those incredible
people is in trouble.
If you'd go to them, it would be a huge help.
You think I'd be useful?
Have more confidence!
I'm recommending you!
All right, I'll do my best!
Then here's a map.
Take care.
Yes, thank you so much.
I'll head out, then!
Good grief. Being the Great Sage's
apprentice isn't an easy task.
The workshops known as Ateliers are facilities
that primarily produce and sell medicines,
magic swords, magic devices and so on.
The head of an Atelier with official
permission is known as an Atelier Meister,
and they're granted special rights with
regards to development and distribution,
along with being treated as
equal to a Viscount in standing.
I never knew there was an
official Atelier in this city.
But is this really the place?
It looks like a normal person's home.
This is definitely it.
W-Welcome.
Is such a young girl the Atelier Meister?
Umm, are you unfamiliar with elves?
Elves?
Oh, no, I'm sorry, that wasn't it.
My name is Kurt.
Are you the Atelier Meister?
No, I'm the Atelier Meister's
assistant, Michelle Lalacotta.
I came here to help on Bandana's recommendation.
Ah! Someone's actually come to help us?!
I'm so glad!
P-Please come inside for now!
What?!
I'm sorry.
Uhh, I'd like to ask you
to help clean up in here.
I haven't been able to get to
it for three whole weeks now.
I see.
I've been called in to help with housework.
I guess it was too much to hope
they'd let me work in the atelier.
I understand.
I'm sorry. I'm bad at cleaning up.
Michelle! Come help me!
Yes! Coming!
I'm sorry. My master is calling me.
Sure!
All right!
Time to work!
That took a whole 30 minutes.
I wonder what I should do next?
If I recall, Michelle went this way?
Yes, come in?
Pardon me.
Umm, where's Michelle?
Huh?
Umm,
and you are?
U-Uhh, my name's Kurt!
I started working here today!
I see.
Lady Ophelia has gone down into the basement.
Oh, right!
Thank you so much!
Huh?
That mark on your stomach?
Is that?
Yes.
It's a curse.
I knew it.
May I take a closer look at it?
Sure?
May I touch it?
That's fine.
Looks like there's no pain when I touch it.
More specifically, the curse has eaten away
at her so much she can't feel any pain.
I imagine her organs are rather damaged as well.
That would make eating...
Oh. I-I'm sorry.
Good.
She still has a proper appetite.
I'll prepare something
light for you to eat, okay?
I just now realized...
I was touching a naked woman's body quite a lot!
God, please forgive me.
Phew.
How much is it worth?
50,000 gold.
That's outrageous.
It is outrageous.
Both mythril and orichalcum.
I can't believe they're real.
Mimico, what do you think would
happen if word got out about him?
If he's lucky, he'd be kidnapped.
Worst case, assassinated.
How has such a monstrous young boy
managed to remain hidden all this time?
I heard he was fired from Flaming Dragon Fang.
Flaming Dragon Fang?
I heard their leader's a wanted man now.
Huh?
So what are you planning
to do with that boy now?
I'm hoping to get him set
up as an Atelier Meister.
Having his actions limited to some degree
would be much better than him
standing out all over the place.
Then I plan to have him
employ me as a bodyguard.
Mhmm.
The real question is how
to get him to accept that.
He has no awareness of his real capability.
Worse, he undervalues himself far too much.
It's definitely going to be a struggle.
Umm, are you Lady Ophelia?
Yes.
I'm sorry. I used your kitchen
without asking your permission.
No, that's fine.
Porridge?
Yes.
The girl in the room in back
said she was feeling hungry.
You've met that girl?
Yes. Is that a problem somehow?
Somewhat.
You mustn't speak of that girl to anyone.
Can you promise that?
Yes.
Umm, should I do anything else?
That's plenty for today.
Could you come around the same time tomorrow?
Huh?!
This much?!
Please, don't be modest and take it.
You've done enough work to earn it.
Thank you so much.
That isn't good.
I can't believe I allowed her to
make contact with an outsider.
Even if I am doing this to slow
the progression of the curse,
I've grown narrow sighted.
I need to focus.
You can't be opening the curtains like that.
It would be bad news if anyone
were to see you, right?
I'm sorry, Teacher.
My, your clothes are slightly loose.
You have to wear them properly.
I'm sorry.
I'm not used to putting them on myself.
That makes sense.
You've always had someone taking care of you.
Yes, Teacher.
I'm sorry.
It's been smelling so good for a while now.
Wait just a moment while I taste for poison.
There's no need for that.
That man made it, right?
That man? You only met him briefly, right?
My intuition could tell he's okay.
Besides, my body's already in
tatters from the curse, you know.
There's no need to use poison
to kill me at this point.
Please, Teacher.
I have no idea who cast this curse on me,
so I've had to suspect
everyone as I lived my life.
But today at least, I'd like
to trust somebody all the way.
All right.
Take your time eating it.
It smells nice.
It must have some herbs in it.
It tastes very good.
It's heartwarming too.
Is it? I'm glad to hear that. Well, then I'll—
Lise?!
Oh no! It was poisoned after all?!
How could I be so careless!
Damn you!
I-I'll get you an antidote at once!
Teacher!
I-I'm fine.
You're fine?! Lise, look at
how much you're sweating!
I'm cured!
Cured?!
Teacher, look.
The curse is fading?!
What's the meaning of this?
She's healing too fast for a broken curse.
This can't...
My apologizes!
I never expected the curse to be broken!
I'll recast it.
They will not wait any longer.
Huh?
They have decided to resort to other means.
Lady Liselotte needs to die post haste.
Is Mimico in?
Ophelia?
I'm sorry for calling so late.
I came to discuss something important.
Yulishia might be an idiot, but
you can definitely trust her.
If this is about some incident,
you can get her involved.
Hey! Don't go deciding that!
Yulishia? The former adventurer working
directly under the royal family?
I am the Atelier Meister,
Ophelia. And this is...
Why?! Why, why, why is the third princess,
Lady Liselotte, in a place like this?!
Your Highness, I heard that you had fallen ill.
I'm sorry, Mimico.
She wasn't actually sick.
She was placed under a powerful curse.
A curse?!
But why?
Someone tried to assassinate her.
Huh?!
Lady Liselotte is the only child
born between His Royal Majesty
and Princess Françoise, the woman he married
from the Gurumaku Empire to our East.
Her very existence is a symbol
of peace between our two nations.
Meaning someone's trying to destroy
those peaceful relationships.
Yes.
With our war against the
nation to the north now over,
I'm sure there are those who would
like to spark a new conflict.
Your Highness.
I'm so glad you're safe.
Yes. Mimico...
You came to me to identify
who cast the curse, correct?
I was hoping we could rely on your power.
My loyalty lies with His Royal Majesty
and her now departed Highness, Françoise,
so I offer it to you, their daughter, as well.
However, Your Highness, it was
a powerful curse, wasn't it?
I'm surprised you were able to break it.
Yes!
That's all thanks to a man
who called himself Kurt!
Huh?
Ku—
K-Kurt?!